<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/code/pfs.css"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A catalogue containing variety of ancient and modern English     books in divinity, history, philology, philosophy, [double brace] law, physick, mathematicks &amp;c. together with Bibles, Testaments, Common     prayers ... will be exposed to sale ... the 30th day of November 1685 / by   Edward Millington ...</title>
            <author>Millington, Edward, d. 1703.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 216KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 29 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2016-02">2016-02 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A31241</idno><idno type="EEBO-CITATION">9101375_42445</idno>
  <idno type="VID">42445</idno>
  <idno type="EEBO-PROQUEST">2248501919</idno>
  
            <idno type="STC">Wing C1255</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R25748</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">09101375</idno>
            <availability><p>This keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above is co-owned by the
    institutions providing financial support to the Early English Books Online Text Creation
    Partnership. This text is available for reuse, according to the terms of <ref target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"> Creative Commons 0 1.0 Universal
    licence</ref>. The text can be copied, modified, distributed and performed, even for commercial
    purposes, all without asking permission.</p></availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt><relatedItem type="facs" target="https://data.historicaltexts.jisc.ac.uk/view?pubId=eebo-e"/>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A31241)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 42445)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1279:9 or 1710:16)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A catalogue containing variety of ancient and modern English     books in divinity, history, philology, philosophy, [double brace] law, physick, mathematicks &amp;c. together with Bibles, Testaments, Common     prayers ... will be exposed to sale ... the 30th day of November 1685 / by   Edward Millington ...</title>
                  <author>Millington, Edward, d. 1703.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[3], 52 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[London? :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1685.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>This item appears at reel 1279:9 and reel 1710:16.</note>
                  <note>Imperfect: p. 51-52 of copy at reel 1279:9 cropped; copy at reel 1710:16 defaced; both have loss of text.</note>
                  <note>"Catalogues are given by Mr. Nott in Pall-Mall, Mr. Timothy Goodwin at the Maidenhead in Fleet-street, Mr. Joseph Wats at the Half-Moon, and Mr. Samuel Smith at the Princes Arms in St.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of originals in the Bodleian Library and the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,363 texts created during Phase 1 of the project have been released into the public domain as of 1 January 2015. Anyone can now take and use these texts for their own purposes, but we respectfully request that due credit and attribution is given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Full documentation of the original data capture process is available from the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.
   All versions of the texts are now archived and freely available for download. See <ref target="https://textcreationpartnership.org/faq/#faq05">the TCP Download FAQ</ref>
   for detailed information. The TEI P5 versions are also freely available from the <ref target="https://github.com/textcreationpartnership">TCP Github repository</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp" matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)" replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char" matchPattern="(.+)" replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term type="topical_term">Catalogs, Booksellers' --  England --  London.</term>
               <term type="topical_term">Booksellers and bookselling --  England --  London.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2014-04 </date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-05 </date>
            <label>John Pas </label>Sampled and proofread </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-05 </date>
            <label>John Pas</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited </change>
         <change>
            <date>2015-03 </date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion </change>
      <change><date>2021-05 </date><label>lb</label>TEI P5 conversion </change></revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:42445:1"/>
            <p>A CATALOGUE CONTAINING Variety of Ancient, and Modern ENGLISH BOOKS IN
<list>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Divinity,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>History,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Philology,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Philosophy,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Law,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Physick,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>
                     <hi>Mathematicks,</hi>
                  </item>
                  <item>&amp;c.</item>
               </list>
            </p>
            <p>Together with Bibles, Testaments, Common Prayers, Singing Psalms, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the best Prints in all Volumes; Will be exposed to Sale (by way of Auction or who bids most) at <hi>Petty-Canon</hi>-Hall in <hi>Petty-Canon</hi>-Alley on the Northside of St. <hi>Paul</hi>'s Church-yard, entring into <hi>Pater-Noster-Row,</hi> the 30th day of <hi>November</hi> 1685.</p>
            <p>
               <hi>By</hi> Edward Millington <hi>Bookseller.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>Catalogues are given by Mr. <hi>Nott</hi> in <hi>Pall-Mall,</hi> Mr. <hi>Timothy Good<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>win</hi> at the <hi>Maidenhead</hi> in <hi>Fleet-street,</hi> Mr. <hi>Joseph Wats</hi> at the <hi>Half-Moon,</hi> and Mr. <hi>Samuel Smith</hi> at the <hi>Princes Arms</hi> in St. <hi>Paul</hi>'s Church-yard, Mr. <hi>Southby</hi> at the <hi>Harrow</hi> in <hi>Cornhil,</hi> Mr. <hi>Ladyman</hi> near the Barrs at <hi>Ald<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate,</hi> Booksellers, at the several <hi>Coffee-houses</hi> in <hi>Cambridge</hi> and <hi>Oxford.</hi> 1685.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="to_the_reader">
            <pb facs="tcp:42445:2"/>
            <head>TO THE READER.</head>
            <p>THis Collection of English Books in all Vo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lumes, and of most Sciences will be exposed to Sale by Auction, with Duplicates of se<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veral valuable Books, Bound and in Quires, with these Printed in the Catalogue, as also most sorts of Bibles of the best Prints; together with Testaments, Common Prayers and Singing Psalms, Book of Homilies, 39 Articles, and Canons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> which Proposal in this way of Sale, so manifestly beneficial to the Purchasers, will we hope be very acceptable, because it hath not yet been Essayd by any, and hath in its first appearance a seem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing tendency to further the knowledge of ignorant Peo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple in the best things at the easiest rate, and may upon Charitable Gentlemen, and Reverend Clergymen have this probable effect, that the Cheapness of these so ab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>solutely necessary Books so disposed of, may invite them to bestow some Numbers among their poor Neigh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bours or Parishioners, who are not able to purchase what they are capable of reading to their benefit. In
<pb facs="tcp:42445:2"/> short what might be further said on this occasion would exceed the bounds of an Auctionary Preface, therefore in Convenient time preceding this Sale, Notice shall be given of the days of Sale for the aforesaid Bibles, Testaments, Service Books, Singing Psalms, Book of Homilies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> At which time or days, Proposals shall be made, of the Conditions and Method of selling them, Apparently advantagious and sufficiently Beneficial to the respective Buyers.</p>
            <p>This Sale will begin on <hi>Monday</hi> the 30th day of <hi>No<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vember</hi> 1685. at <hi>Petty-Canon</hi>-Hall in <hi>Petty-Canon</hi>-Alley on the Northside of St. <hi>Paul</hi>'s Church-yard, entring into <hi>Pater-Noster-Row,</hi> from the hours of 9 in the Morning to 12 and from 2 to 6 in the Even<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ving till all the Books are Sould.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="notice">
            <pb facs="tcp:42445:3"/>
            <head>Conditions of Sale.</head>
            <p n="1">
               <hi>1.</hi> THAT he who bids most is the Buyer; and if any difference ariseth, the same Book or Books to be exposed again to Sale.</p>
            <p n="2">
               <hi>2.</hi> That the Books in this Catalogue (not otherwise expressed) are for ought we know perfect; but if any of them appear to be otherwise before they be taken away, the Buyer shall have his choice of leaving or taking them.</p>
            <p n="3">
               <hi>3.</hi> That the Money for the Book or Books so bought, is to be paid by the Buyer within one Month after the Au<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ction or Sale is ended, at the place of Sale; where upon payment thereof the Book or Books so bought shall be ready to be delivered within the Month aforesaid.</p>
            <p n="4">
               <hi>4.</hi> That every Person not known to some of the com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pany, do give in his Name and place of Abode (or earn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>est in part of the Books by him bought, if required,) to the end, that the Auction may be managed with honesty and justice to all, so as to prevent the inconveniences that have hitherto ensued by the forgetfulness of some, and design of others, in leaving several parcels of Books on the hands of the Ʋndertakers, to their prejudice, and to the abuse of others that they have out of vanity or humour outbid.</p>
            <p n="5">
               <hi>5.</hi> That these Books are to be seen together with the Bibles, Testaments, Common Prayers and Singing Psalms, Book of Homilies, <hi>39</hi> Articles, and Canons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> for one whole Week before the Auction begins, from Nine till Twelve in the Morning, and from Two till Six in the Afternoon, by any Gentlemen that please to repair to the above-mentioned place.</p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:42445:3"/>
            <list>
               <head>English in <hi>Folio.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>1 <hi>ALlestry (Rich.)</hi> Sermons <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>2 —Idem <hi>Lond.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>3 <hi>A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lens</hi> Doctrine of the Gospel <hi>London</hi> 1606</item>
               <item>4 Annals of King <hi>James</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> the First <hi>(Frankland) London</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Attorsoll (Will.)</hi> Commentary on Pa<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>lemon <hi>Ib.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>6 <hi>Artamenes</hi> or Grand Cyrus the fifth and last Volum <hi>Ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>7 Aphorismes Civil and Military, taken out of <hi>Fr. Guicciardine Ib.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>8 Bishop <hi>Andrews (Lancel.)</hi> Collection of Posthumous and Orphan Lectures <hi>Ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>9 —On the Commandements <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>10 <hi>Ambroses (Isaac)</hi> Works. <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>11 A Church Bible with Chronology <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>12 A Bible Fol. for a House, with Chronology and Index <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>13 A Common Prayer of Imperial Paper <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>14 —Of a second Edition smaller folio fine Paper, with 39 A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ticles <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>15 —Idem ordinary Paper <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>16 A Book of Homilies, with 39 Articles <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>17 —Idem large Paper <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>18 <hi>Adam</hi>'s large Map of <hi>England,</hi> Coloured and Pasted on Cloth to hang in a Room —</item>
               <item>19 Bishop <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ownrig</hi>'s <hi>(Ralph)</hi> Sermons <hi>L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>nd.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Bentivolio</hi>'s History of the Wars of <hi>Flanders Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s <hi>(Thomas)</hi> Theory of the Earth <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Boccatio</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Novels and Tales <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Catholick Theology <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>24 —Idem Gilt Leaves <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>25 —Christian Directory, or Body of Practical Divinity <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Bacon</hi>'s <hi>(Francis)</hi> Natural History <hi>Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>27 —His Resuscitatio <hi>Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Baker (Rich.)</hi> Chronicle of the Kings of <hi>England Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Du Bartu,</hi> Works, best Edition <hi>Lond.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Barnet</hi>'s <hi>(Gilbert)</hi> History of the Reformation, 2 Vol. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>31 — Memoirs of Duke <hi>Hamelton ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>32 <hi>Brady</hi>'s <hi>(Robert)</hi> Introduction to the old English History <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>33 —Compleat History of <hi>England</hi> 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>85</item>
               <item>34 Dr. <hi>Burlace</hi>'s History of the Irish Rebellion, until 1661 <hi>Lond.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>35 <hi>Brook (Fulk</hi> Lord) Works, <hi>viz.</hi> Treatise of Wars, <hi>&amp;c. L nd.</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>36 Bishop <hi>Bramhall</hi>'s Works <hi>Dublin</hi>
               </item>
               <item>37 <hi>Bartholin</hi>'s Anatomy, by Culpeper <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>38 <hi>Bonettus</hi> Guide to the Practical Physitian, <hi>English ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Burton</hi>'s Anatomy of Melancholy <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>40 <hi>Beaumont</hi> and <hi>Fletchers</hi> Playes <hi>ib.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Bayly</hi>'s Wall-Flower (A Romance) <hi>Lond.</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Biondi</hi>'s Civil Wars of <hi>Engl.</hi> beginning with <hi>Rich.</hi> 2. and ending w<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>th <hi>H.</hi> 6. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Cave (Will.)</hi> Lives of the Primitive Fathers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1667</item>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:42445:4"/>
               <item>44 <hi>Cogan</hi>'s <hi>(Henry)</hi> Illustrious Bassa <hi>Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Charas (Moses)</hi> Royal Pharmacopaea <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Crook</hi>'s <hi>(Helkiah)</hi> Anatomy <hi>Lond.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Cudworth</hi>'s Intelectual Systeme of the Universe <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Calderwood</hi>'s <hi>(David)</hi> History of <hi>Scotland</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>49 <hi>Clelia</hi> a Romance <hi>(Scudery) Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Charnock</hi>'s <hi>(Stephen)</hi> Works in 2 Vol <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Cowley</hi>'s Works <hi>(Abraham)</hi> the eighth Edition <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>52 —Works 2d Part <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>53 Compleat Ambassador (Sir <hi>Dudly Digges) Lond.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Cambridge</hi> Concordence 1682</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Clark</hi>'s Marrow of Ecclesiastical History <hi>Ib.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>56 —His Marrow or Lookingglass for Saints and Sinners Vol. 2. <hi>Ib.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>57 <hi>Cradock</hi>'s Harmony of the four Evangelists <hi>Ib.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>58 —Apostolical History <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>59 <hi>Cary</hi>'s Cronology <hi>(Robert) Ib.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Castle</hi> of Knowledge, <hi>Rob. Record Ib.</hi> 1556</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Cotgrave (Randal)</hi> Dictionary of the French and English Tongue <hi>Ib.</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>62 Compleat Ambassador written, by Sir <hi>Dudl. Diggs Ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Cumber (Tho.)</hi> Works Companion to the Temple, or a Help to Devotion, <hi>&amp;c. Ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Clark</hi>'s Examples, or Looking-Glass for Saints and Sinners <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>65 <hi>Chillingworth</hi>'s Defence of the Protestant Religion <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>66 <hi>Caryl</hi> on <hi>Job.</hi> Vol. 2. <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>67 <hi>Causin</hi>'s Holy Court <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>68 <hi>Cassandra</hi> (the Romance) <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>69 <hi>Cesar</hi>'s Comentaries, by <hi>Edmonds</hi> with Cuts <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>70 <hi>Curia Politice,</hi> or the Apologies of several Princes <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>71 <hi>Churchil</hi>'s Remarks on the Lives of the Kings of <hi>England</hi> to 1660</item>
               <item>72 Catalogue of all the Books in the University of <hi>Oxford</hi> Library <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Glavel</hi>'s Catalogue of all Books Printed in <hi>London,</hi> from the fire of <hi>London</hi> 1666 to <hi>Trinity</hi> Term 1685 (Inclusive) 1685</item>
               <item>74 Dr. <hi>Charlton</hi>'s Description of Animals Lat. and Engl. <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>75 <hi>Digby</hi> (Sir <hi>Kel.</hi>) of Bodies <hi>Paris</hi>
               </item>
               <item>76 <hi>Davenant (Will.)</hi> Works <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>77 <hi>Davilas</hi> History of <hi>France Savoy</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>78 <hi>Dagdale</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Civil Wars of <hi>England,</hi> from 1640 to 1660 <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>79 —<hi>Origines</hi> Judidiciales <hi>Ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>80 —Baronage of <hi>England</hi> 2 Vol. Royal Paper <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>81 —Idem Ordinary Paper <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>82 —Copy of all Summons of the Nobility to Parliaments from K. <hi>Henry</hi> 3d. to 1685</item>
               <item>83 <hi>Dixon</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Nature of the two Testaments, <hi>Ib.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Dallington</hi>'s Aphoirsmes Civil and Military <hi>Ib.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Day</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Commentary on the Epistle to the Romans <hi>Ib.</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>86 —His Commentary on the Prophet Isaiah <hi>Ib.</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>87 <hi>Drayton</hi>'s <hi>(Mich.)</hi> Polyolboin, with <hi>Selden</hi>'s Notes with Figures <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>88 Sir <hi>Dadly D<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>gges</hi> his Compleat Ambassador <hi>Ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>89 <hi>Daniel (Sam.)</hi> and <hi>Jo. Trussels</hi> Collection of History of <hi>England Ib.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>90 <hi>Dabartas</hi>'s Works translated by <hi>Jos. Sylvester Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>91 Summary on <hi>D<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>bartas</hi> his Works <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>92 <hi>Daille</hi> 47 Sermons on the <hi>Colossians ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="3" facs="tcp:42445:4"/>
               <item>93 <hi>Evelyn</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Discourse of Forest Trees <hi>Lond.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>94 — Idem 1670</item>
               <item>95 Eposition of <hi>Genesis</hi> and <hi>Exodus,</hi> by <hi>Geo. Hughes</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Esiana</hi> A new Romance, form'd by an English hand <hi>Ib.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>97 <hi>Esops Fables</hi> English Lat. French with Cuts, by <hi>Barlow ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>98 Duke of <hi>Espernon</hi>'s Life, being a Continuation of <hi>Davilas</hi> History <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>99 <hi>Farindons (Anthony)</hi> Sermons 3d Vol. <hi>Ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Foules</hi> History of Romish Treasons <hi>Ib.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>101 — Of Pretended Saints <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>102 <hi>Forsters (Sam.)</hi> Miscellanies <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>103 <hi>Favins (Andrew)</hi> Theater of Honour <hi>Ib.</hi> 1623</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Frost</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Select Sermons <hi>Cambridge</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Franklands</hi> Annals of King <hi>James,</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> the First 681</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Flud</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Mosaical Philosophy <hi>Lud.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>107 Five Decades of Epistles of War, by <hi>Fra. Markham Lond.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Franks</hi> 51 Sermons <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>109 <hi>Felthams</hi> Resolves, Divine, Moral, Political <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>110 <hi>Gils (Alexander)</hi> Exposition on the Creed <hi>Ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>111 <hi>Gurnal (Will.)</hi> Christian Armour <hi>Ib.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Gadbury</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Doctrine of Nativities <hi>Ib.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>113 —His Collection of Nativities in 150 Genitures <hi>ib.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Gouge (Will.)</hi> on the <hi>Hebrews Ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Guicciardine</hi>'s <hi>(Fr.)</hi> Aphorismes, Civil and Military <hi>Ib.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Guillim</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Display of Heraldry, the best Edition with Figurs <hi>Ib.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>117 —Another with the Terms of Hawking and Hunting <hi>Ib.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Gells</hi> Remains on several select Scriptures <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>119 Dr. <hi>Grew</hi> of Vegetables (with Cuts) <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>120 Holy Bible for Churches, with Chronology <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>121 —With Common Prayer, Index, <hi>&amp;c. ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>122 A Common Prayer for Churches, of Imperial Paper <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>123 —Idem Ordinary <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>124 History of the Caribbe Islands <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>125 —Of the Cardinals of <hi>Rome ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>126 —Of the late Wars in <hi>Denmark ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>127 <hi>Heaths</hi> Chronicle of the late Wars in <hi>England ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>128 History Of <hi>Don Quixot ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>129 <hi>Hobbs</hi> Translation of Thucidides, with Cuts <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>130 History of <hi>Appian</hi> of <hi>Alexandria ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>131 History of the University of <hi>Oxford,</hi> part English, part Latin <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>132 <hi>David Logans</hi> Cuts of all the Colledges in <hi>Oxford ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>133 Homilies to be read in Churches, with the 39 Articles <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>134 — <hi>Idem</hi> Great Paper <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>135 History of the Bible in Brass Cuts <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>136 Dr. <hi>Hortons</hi> one Hundred select Sermons <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>137 — On the <hi>Romans ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>138 —On the 4th, 42d, 51st, and 63 Psalms <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>139 <hi>Hutchinson</hi> on <hi>Job ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>140 <hi>Heylins</hi> Cosmography <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>141 —History of the <hi>Presbeterians ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>142 —Of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:42445:5"/>
               <item>143 History of <hi>Montluc,</hi> Marshal of <hi>France Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>144 <hi>Hammond</hi>'s Sermons, Large Paper <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Herbert</hi>'s Travels <hi>Lond.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>146 Life of King <hi>Henry</hi> the Eighth <hi>Lond.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Hall</hi>'s Paraphrase on the Old and New Testament <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>148 <hi>Hales</hi>'s Origination of Mankind <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Heylin</hi>'s Tracts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>150 Bishop <hi>Hacker</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Century of Sermons <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Hal<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Four Books of Government and Obedience <hi>Ib.</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>152 — <hi>(Thomas)</hi> his Commentary on the 3d and 4th Chapt. of the 2d to <hi>Timothy Ib.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Hieron</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Sermons, with his Help to Devotion <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>154 <hi>Hart</hi>'s <hi>(Ja.)</hi> Diet of the Diseased, in three Books <hi>Lond.</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>155 Harmony on the Four Evangelists, by <hi>Sam. Cradock Ib.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>156 <hi>Howels</hi>'s <hi>(James)</hi> Survey of the Seignorie of <hi>Venice Ib.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>157 Home of Mourn ng <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>158 <hi>Hammond</hi>'s Tract, 2 vol. in Defence of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>159 — Parley of Beasts 1660</item>
               <item>160 <hi>Hooker</hi>'s Ecclesiastical Polity, compleat <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>161 <hi>Heylin</hi> on the C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>eed <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>162 History of <hi>Lewis</hi> the Eleventh, by <hi>P. Matthieu,</hi> englished by <hi>Edw. Grimestone</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>163 — History of the <hi>Irish</hi> Rebelion, by Dr. <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rlace Lond.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>164 — of <hi>Venice</hi> from the beginning to 1612. <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>165 — of K <hi>James</hi> and K. <hi>Charles</hi> the First, by Dr. <hi>Frankland Ib.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>166 — History of the Wars of <hi>Flanders,</hi> by <hi>Card. Bentivoglio Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>167 — of <hi>Henry</hi> VII. by L. <hi>Bacon,</hi> with <hi>G<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>odwin</hi>'s <hi>Henry</hi> VIII. <hi>Edw.</hi> VI. and Q. <hi>Mary</hi>
               </item>
               <item>168 — <hi>Baker</hi>'s Chronicle of <hi>England,</hi> (the last Edition) 1684</item>
               <item>169 — <hi>Davila</hi>'s H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>story of the Civil Wars of <hi>France Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>170 — <hi>Foule</hi>'s History of the <hi>Romish</hi> Treason and Usurpation <hi>Ib.</hi> 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>81</item>
               <item>171 — <hi>Knox</hi>'s History of <hi>Ceylon</hi> in the <hi>East-Indies,</hi> with Figures <hi>Ib.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>172 — <hi>Pacata Hibernia, I eland</hi> appeased and reduced <hi>Ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>173 — Sir <hi>Walther Raleigh</hi>'s History of the World <hi>Ib.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>174 — <hi>Jo. Schoffer</hi>'s History of <hi>Lapla<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>d,</hi> with Figures <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>175 — <hi>Arth. Wilson</hi>'s Life of King <hi>James</hi> the First <hi>Lond.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>176 — <hi>Bulstr W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>atlock</hi>'s History of the <hi>English</hi> Aff<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>irs, from 1625. to 1660. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>177 — <hi>Phil. de Comines</hi> his History, with Annotations <hi>Ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>178 — Lord <hi>Edward Herbert</hi>'s Life and Reign of <hi>Henry</hi> the Eighth <hi>Ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>179 — <hi>Procopius</hi> History of the Wars of <hi>Justinian Ib.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>180 — <hi>Prud. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>e Sandovals</hi> C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>vil-Wars of <hi>Spain Ib.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>181 Jesuits Morals, by a Doctor of <hi>Sorbon</hi> in <hi>Paris Ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>182 History of the <hi>Irish</hi> Rebellion from 1641. to 1680. <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>183 Journal of S. <hi>Amour</hi> Doctor of <hi>Sorborne Lond.</hi> 1664.</item>
               <item>184 B shop <hi>Jewel</hi>'s D<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>fence of the Apolog<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 15<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>7</item>
               <item>185 <hi>Ingelo</hi>'s Bentivolio and Urania 1682</item>
               <item>186 <hi>J<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>sephus</hi> in <hi>English ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>187 <hi>Ibrahim,</hi> or the Illustrious <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ssa</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>188 <hi>Knox (Rob.)</hi> Historical, Relation of <hi>Ceilon,</hi> an Isl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>nd in the <hi>East-Indies Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Kellet</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> of the threefold Supper of Christ <hi>Ib.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>190 <hi>Kendal (Geo.)</hi> Doctrine of the Reformed Churches concerning Redemption <hi>Ib.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>191 <hi>Knight</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Concordance to the Holy Scripture <hi>Ib.</hi> 1610</item>
               <item>192 <hi>K<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rsey (Jo.) Algebra</hi> expounded, in 4 Books, 2 volumes <hi>Ib.</hi> 1673</item>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:42445:5"/>
               <item>193 <hi>Lee</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Temple of <hi>Solomon Lond.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>194 <hi>Lomatius (Jo. Paul)</hi> Treatise of Arts, curious Painting, Carving, <hi>&amp;c. Oxon.</hi> 1598</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Lucan</hi>'s P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>arsalia (with his Life) Translated by Sir <hi>Geo. Gorges Lond.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>196 <hi>Littleton</hi>'s <hi>(Adam)</hi> Sermons <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>197 <hi>Ligons</hi> History of the <hi>Barbadoes Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>198 Archbishop <hi>Laud</hi> against <hi>Fisher Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>199 <hi>Leybourns</hi> Compleat Surveyor <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>200 — Art of Dyalling <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>201 <hi>Ludolphus</hi> History of <hi>E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>hiopia Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>202 Dr. <hi>Ligh foots</hi> Works Vol. 2 <hi>Ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>203 Mariner, Magazine <hi>Ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Mercators</hi> Atlas, with Mapps <hi>Ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Machiavel</hi>'s <hi>(Nicholas)</hi> Works <hi>Ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>206 — His <hi>Florentine</hi> History <hi>Ib.</hi> 15<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>5</item>
               <item>207 <hi>Morice (Vill.)</hi> Treatise of the Lords Supper <hi>Ib.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>208 Military Instructions for the Cavalry, according the Modern Wars <hi>Camb.</hi>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>644</item>
               <item>209 <hi>Markham</hi>'s Five decades and Epistles of War 1622</item>
               <item>210 Bishop <hi>Morton</hi>'s 8 Books of the Institution of the Mass of Christ <hi>I<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>211 <hi>Mountagus</hi> (Bishop <hi>Rich.</hi>) Acts and Monuments of the Church before Christ <hi>Ib.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>212 <hi>Mead</hi>'s <hi>(Joseph)</hi> Works</item>
               <item>213 Sir <hi>Jonas Mores</hi> Maps of the Fenns, Coloured and pasted on Cloth for to hang in Rooms</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Maimbourg</hi>'s History of the <hi>Crusade,</hi> by Dr. <hi>Nalson</hi>
               </item>
               <item>215 <hi>Nalsons (John)</hi> Tryal of Ki<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <hi>Charles</hi> the First <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>216 —Collections of Great Affairs of State, Vol. 2. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>217 New world of English words or a general Dictionary, by <hi>E. Philips Id.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Nanis</hi> History of <hi>Venice,</hi> by Sir <hi>Honywood</hi>
               </item>
               <item>219 Earl of <hi>Northamptons</hi> Defensative against the Poyson of supposed Prophcies 1620</item>
               <item>220 <hi>Owen (John)</hi> on the <hi>Hebrews,</hi> concerning the Priesthood of Christ <hi>Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>221 —Discourse concerning the Holy Spirit <hi>Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>222 —Concerning the Messiah <hi>Lond.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Phillips (Edw.)</hi> English Dictionary <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>224 Mistress <hi>Katherine Philips</hi> Poems <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>225 <hi>Parr</hi>'s <hi>(Ethn.)</hi> Works on the Romans, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> the third Edition <hi>Ib.</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Plutarchs</hi> Morals, Englished by <hi>Phll. Holland Ib.</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>227 <hi>Prynne</hi>'s <hi>(William)</hi> History of King <hi>John, Hen.</hi> 3. and <hi>Edw.</hi> the First <hi>Ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Pool</hi>'s <hi>(Matt.)</hi> English Synopsis▪ or Annotations upon the Holy Bible, Vol. 2. <hi>Ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>229 —Second Volume Alone</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Petavius (Dionysius)</hi> Geographical Description of the World <hi>Ib.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>231 Bishop <hi>Pearson (Jo.)</hi> On the Creed <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>232 <hi>Pareys</hi> Chirurgery <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>233 <hi>Pharamond</hi> (A Romance) <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>234 <hi>Parthanissa</hi> (Romance) <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>535 <hi>Priorata</hi>'s History of <hi>France Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>236 Dr. <hi>Pocock</hi> on <hi>Micha</hi> and <hi>Malachi Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>237 Sir <hi>Will. Petteys</hi> Maps of <hi>Ireland,</hi> Survayed by himself <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>238 Picture of King <hi>James</hi> the Second, by <hi>David Logan Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>239 —King <hi>Charles</hi> the Second, by <hi>Robert White Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>240 —Queen <hi>Mary,</hi> by <hi>Vanderbanck Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>241 —Queen Dowager, <hi>Idem Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>242 —Of <hi>Hugo Grotius,</hi> Graved in <hi>Holland Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:42445:6"/>
               <item>243 Mathematical Collections and Transactions, by <hi>Galileus Lond.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Mayer</hi> on the Pentateuch 1653</item>
               <item>245 <hi>Jackion</hi>'s Collection of his Works 1653</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Melvil</hi>'s (Sir <hi>James</hi>) Memoires of the Affairs of <hi>Sotland</hi> in the Reigns of Q. <hi>Elizabeth, Mary,</hi> and K. <hi>James</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>247 Dr. <hi>Pells Tables</hi> of 10000 Squarenumbers</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Rameseys</hi> Introduction to Astrology <hi>Lond.</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>8</item>
               <item>249 <hi>Rathborn</hi>'s Surveyor</item>
               <item>250 <hi>Rushworths</hi> Historical Collections, 3. Vol. Compleat <hi>Ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>251 —Tryal of the Earl of <hi>Strafford Ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>252 <hi>Rea (Jo.) Flora, Ceres</hi> and <hi>Pomona Ib.</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>253 <hi>Robert</hi>'s <hi>(Francis)</hi> Key of the Bible <hi>Ib.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>254 <hi>Robert</hi>'s <hi>(Lewis)</hi> Maps of Commerce <hi>Ib.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>255 <hi>Record</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Castle of Knowledge <hi>Ib.</hi> 1556</item>
               <item>256 <hi>William Cunnington</hi>'s Cosmographical Glass <hi>Ib.</hi> 1559</item>
               <item>257 <hi>Rogers (Rich.)</hi> Commentary on the whole Book of <hi>Judges Ib.</hi> 1615</item>
               <item>258 Bishop <hi>Reynolds</hi> Works, compleat in one Volume <hi>Ib.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>259 <hi>Riverius (Laza.)</hi> his Practice of Physick, in 17 Books <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>260 Royal <hi>Pharmacopaea,</hi> Galenical and Chymical, by <hi>Mos. Charras Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>261 <hi>Ricaut</hi>'s <hi>(Paul)</hi> Lives of the Popes and Bishops <hi>Ib.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>262 <hi>R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>olanus</hi> Anatomy with Figures <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>263 <hi>Reynolds</hi> of Murther (with Cuts)</item>
               <item>264 <hi>Rycaut</hi>'s History of the Turks, from 1623, to 1637</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Selden</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Office of Lord Chancellor of <hi>England Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>266 —His Titles of Honour <hi>Ib.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>267 <hi>Sander</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Physiognomy, and Chiromancy <hi>Ib.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>268 <hi>Sprig</hi>'s <hi>(Joshua) Englands</hi> Recovery <hi>Ib.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>269 <hi>Sturmy</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Mariners Magazine <hi>Ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>270 <hi>Scheffer</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> History of <hi>Lapland</hi> (with Cuts <hi>Theatre Oxford</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>271 <hi>Sleidane</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Commentaries <hi>Lond.</hi> 1560</item>
               <item>272 Scriveners Course of Divinity <hi>Ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>273 <hi>Selden</hi>'s <hi>(John) Janus Anglorum Ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>274 <hi>Speed</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Maps of Great <hi>Britain</hi> and <hi>Ireland Ib.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>275 <hi>Sylva Sylvarum,</hi> or a natural History in 10 Centuries, by Lord <hi>Bacon Ib.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>276 Short view of the late Troubles in <hi>England,</hi> by Sir <hi>William Dugdale Oxon.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>277 <hi>Sanderson</hi>'s (Bishop <hi>Robert</hi>) Sermons <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>278 <hi>Smith</hi>'s Defence of the Christian Religion <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>279 <hi>Sanson</hi>'s Geographical Description of the World with Mapps <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>280 Sir <hi>Philp Sidney</hi>'s Arcadia with the rest of his Works <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>281 <hi>Strada</hi>'s History of the Low Country Wars <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>282 <hi>Sandy</hi>'s Travels (with Cuts) <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>283 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s <hi>Origines Britanica Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>284 —Sermons <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>285 —Rational Account of the Protestant Religion <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>286 <hi>Systema Agricultura,</hi> or Mistery of Husbandry discovered <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>287 <hi>Snape</hi>'s Anatomy of a Horse with Curious Figures <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>288 <hi>Shakspear</hi>'s Playes 1685</item>
               <item>289 <hi>Silhen</hi>'s Minister of State <hi>Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>290 <hi>Sprigg</hi>'s History of Sir <hi>Thomas Fairfax</hi>'s Action in the Parliament Army</item>
               <item>291 <hi>Towerson (Gab.)</hi> on the Lords Prayer and Ten Commandements <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:42445:6"/>
               <item>292 —On the Ten Commandements <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>293 —On the Creed</item>
               <item>294 <hi>Tindale</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Translation of the Bible, want beginning <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>295 <hi>Turner (Will.)</hi> Herbal in two parts with a discourse of English Bathes <hi>Collen</hi> 1561</item>
               <item>296 Treatise of the Sacrament, by <hi>W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ll. Morice</hi> (Lettred) <hi>Lond.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>297 <hi>Tavernier</hi>'s <hi>(Jo. Bapt.)</hi> Travels 2 parts one Vol. with figures (Let.) <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678 &amp; 1680</item>
               <item>298 — Travels into <hi>Turky, Persia.</hi> &amp;c, Vol. the second <hi>Ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>299 Sir <hi>James Turner</hi>'s Millitary Essays of the Ancient <hi>Grecians, Romans</hi>
               </item>
               <item>300 View of the Soul in several Tracts to Dr. <hi>Jo. Tillitson,</hi> Dean of <hi>Canterbury Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>301 <hi>Van Helmonts (Jo. Baptista)</hi> Works <hi>Lond.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>302 <hi>Varenius</hi> and <hi>Sanson</hi>'s Cosmography and Geography <hi>Lond.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>303 View of the Late Troubles in <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>Will. D<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>gdale Oxon.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Ʋsher</hi>'s Body Divinity with Figures</item>
               <item>305 <hi>Veslingius</hi> Anatomy</item>
               <item>307 <hi>Wing (Vincent) Harmonicon Coeleste Lond.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>308 —<hi>Astronomia Instaurata Lond.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>309 <hi>Webster (John)</hi> of Witchcraft <hi>Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>310 —<hi>Idem</hi> Large Paper</item>
               <item>311 <hi>Wilson</hi>'s <hi>(Arthur)</hi> Life of King <hi>James</hi> the First <hi>Lond.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>312 <hi>Willoughby (Fran.)</hi> of Birds, with their Cuts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>313 <hi>Whitlock</hi>'s <hi>(Bulstrod)</hi> Memorials of <hi>English</hi> Affairs, from 1625 to 1660 <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>314 <hi>Wilson</hi>'s Christian Dictionary <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>315 Dr. <hi>(Tho.) Willis</hi> Works <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>316 Bishop <hi>Wilkin</hi>'s Real Character <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>317 Dr. <hi>John Wallis Algebra Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>318 Sir <hi>George Wheeler</hi>'s Travels in <hi>Greece,</hi> with Cuts <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>319 <hi>Gouge (Tho.)</hi> Works <hi>Lond.</hi> 1267</item>
               <item>320 Bishop <hi>Gauden</hi> Tears, Complaints and Prayers of the Church of <hi>England Ib.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>321 Wars of <hi>Italy,</hi> from 1613 to 1644, by <hi>Capriata ib.</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Hutchinson</hi> on <hi>John ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>323 Journal of Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi> by Sir <hi>S. Dews ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>324 <hi>Cotgrave</hi>'s English▪ and French Dictionary 1650</item>
               <item>325 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s History of the Reformation, First part <hi>ib.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>326 <hi>Card Petron</hi>'s Reply to King <hi>James</hi> 1630</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>Law Books <hi>Folio.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>327 <hi>WInch</hi>'s <hi>(Humphry)</hi> Reports <hi>Lond.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>328 <hi>Plowden</hi>'s <hi>(Edmond)</hi> Commentaries <hi>ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>329 Laws and Acts of Parliament made in <hi>Scotland Edenb.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>330 Collection of all the Statutes now in use the Kingdom of <hi>Ireland Dublin</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>331 <hi>Anderson</hi>'s Reports large Paper <hi>Lond.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>332 <hi>Hen. Scobell</hi>'s Collection of Acts in the Years 1648, 1649, 1650, 1651 <hi>ib.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>333 <hi>Henry</hi> the Seventh (and year Book) with <hi>Brooks</hi> notes <hi>ib.</hi> 1597</item>
               <item>334 <hi>Ferd. Pulton</hi>'s Collection of Statutes <hi>ib.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>335 <hi>Crooke</hi>'s Reports, vol. 3. <hi>ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>336 —<hi>Charles</hi> the First <hi>ib.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>337 <hi>Cooke</hi>'s Reports English <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>338 —<hi>Idem</hi> French Vol. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. <hi>ib.</hi> 1609</item>
               <item>339 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s Records of the Tower <hi>ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:42445:7"/>
               <item>340 <hi>Cawleys</hi> Laws made against Jesuits <hi>ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Lanes</hi> Reports in the <hi>Exchequer ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Bulstrode</hi>'s Reports Compleat <hi>ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>344 <hi>Bowman</hi>'s Songs for one, two, or three voyces to the Thorowbass collected out of <hi>Cowley</hi> and others <hi>Oxor.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Porta</hi>'s Natural Magick <hi>Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Pemble</hi>'s Works <hi>Oxford</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>9</item>
               <item>347 <hi>P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>in</hi>'s Chronological vindication of the Jurisdiction of our English Kings Tom 2d from the Invasions of the Popes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>348 — <hi>Idem</hi> Large Paper <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>Law <hi>Quarto.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>349 <hi>GOdolphin</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Orphans Legacy, or a Testamentary Abridgment <hi>Lond.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>350 <hi>Fulbeck</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Pandectes of the Law of Nations <hi>ib.</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>351 —His parallel of the Civil Law, Canon Law and Common Law <hi>ib.</hi> 1601</item>
               <item>352 <hi>Jo. Skene</hi>'s exposition of the Terms and diffi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ult words in the Law <hi>ib.</hi> 1641</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>Law <hi>Octavo.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>353 TOuchstone of Preced', relating to Judicial proceedings at Common Law <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>354 —Another of the same, by <hi>G. F.</hi> of <hi>Graies-Inn ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>355 Young Clerks Guide Compleat, 4. parts <hi>ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Ridley</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) View of the Civil and Ecclesiastical Law <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>357 Terms of the Law Explained <hi>Lond.</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>358 <hi>Kitchin (Jo.)</hi> of Courts in French <hi>ib.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Hen. Finch</hi>'s Lawer a Discourse thereof in 4 Books <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>b.</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>360 Mr. <hi>Plowden</hi>'s Abridgment <hi>de touts les Case</hi> Reports <hi>ib.</hi> 1607</item>
               <item>361 <hi>Manley</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Abridgment of the 2 last Volumes of Lord <hi>Cook</hi>'s Reports <hi>ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>362 <hi>Ed. Trotman</hi>'s Epitome <hi>undecim Libr. Relationum</hi> Edw. Cooke <hi>ib.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>363 —<hi>Idem</hi> Gallice <hi>ib.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Andr. Horne Mirror des Justices ib.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>365 <hi>Gu. Fleetwood Index Annalium Ed.</hi> 5. <hi>Rich.</hi> 3. <hi>Hen.</hi> &amp; 8th 1597</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Jo. Wilkinson</hi>'s Office and Authorities of Coroners and Sheriffs 1641</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>English <hi>Quarto.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>1 <hi>AInsworth</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Annotations on <hi>Genesis, Exodus, Levit. Numbers,</hi> &amp;c. 3 Vol. <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>2 —His Annot. on <hi>Genesis Levit.</hi> and <hi>Psalmes,</hi> 2. Vol. <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>3 <hi>Attersoll</hi>'s Pathway to <hi>Canaan,</hi> or an Exposition on the 20 of <hi>Numbers Cambr.</hi> 1609</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Abbot</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Defence of <hi>Perkins</hi> reformed Catholick <hi>Lond.</hi> 1911</item>
               <item>5 Arraignment of the whole Creature <hi>ib.</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>6 Answer to the Censure of K. <hi>James</hi> his Apology <hi>ib.</hi> 1609</item>
               <item>7 <hi>Attwell</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Faithful Surveyor <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>8 Antapologia or an answer to Mr. <hi>Goodwins,</hi> &amp;c. Appologetical Narration <hi>Lond.</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>9 Abridgement of the <hi>Lincoln</hi> Ministers Book delivered to K. <hi>James ib.</hi> 1605</item>
               <item>10 Apology for sundry proceedings by Jurisdiction Ecclesiastical <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>11 <hi>Apuleius</hi> Golden Asse, and also the <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>sse overladen <hi>ib.</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Ames (Will.)</hi> on <hi>Peter ib.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Austin</hi> of Fruit Trees <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>14 Anatomical Account of the El<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>phant <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>15 Address to the Free-Men and Free-Holders of the Nation, 3d part <hi>Lond.</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>3</item>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:42445:7"/>
               <item>17 Bible black Letter, want in the end</item>
               <item>18 Bishop <hi>Bancrofts</hi> survey of the pretended Holy Discipline <hi>Lond.</hi> 1595</item>
               <item>19 <hi>If Barrow</hi>'s Treatise of the Popes supremacy <hi>Lond.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Balls (Jo.)</hi> Friendly tryal of the grounds tending to separatio 1640</item>
               <item>21 Treatise of 4 Monarchies, and Christs twofold Kingdom <hi>ib.</hi> 164</item>
               <item>22 —His answer to Mr. <hi>Can</hi> touching separatior <hi>ib.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Beza</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Sermons on the 3 First Chapters of <hi>Canticles Oxon.</hi> 1587</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Bayne (Paul)</hi> Commentary on Colossians <hi>Lond.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Byfield (Nic.)</hi> Sermons on the 1st of <hi>Peter,</hi> and on the Sabbath, 2. Vol. <hi>ib.</hi> 1626</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Brinsley</hi>'s True Watch, the Third Part <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>27 —His Commentary on <hi>Ezekiels</hi> Vision <hi>Lond.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Bernard</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> 3 Fold Treatise of the Sabbath <hi>Lond.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>29 —His Key to the opening of the Revelations <hi>ib.</hi>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>617</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Bolton</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Directions for a comfortable walking with God <hi>ib.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>31 —Discourse of Happiness <hi>ib.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>32 <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rlow (Will.)</hi> Of Praedestination and Reprobation <hi>ib.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>33 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> 2d True defence of the Non-Conformists <hi>ib.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>34 —His true H story of the Councils enlarged and Defended <hi>ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>35 —His naked Popery, in answer to a Roman Catholick <hi>Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Burrough</hi>'s Heart-division, the Evil of our Times</item>
               <item>37 —His Gospel Remission <hi>ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Boughen (Edw.)</hi> Sermon of Confirmation <hi>ib.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Brightman</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Commentary upon the Revelations <hi>Amst.</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>40 Buckler of Faith against the Jesuits, by <hi>Peter du Moulin Lond.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Burton</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Questions concerning the Attributes of God <hi>Lond.</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Benefiel<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(Seb.)</hi> Commentary on <hi>Amos Lond.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>43 <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>oughton</hi>'s <hi>(Hugh)</hi> Revelation of the Holy Apocalyps 1610</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Bewi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>k</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Answer to the Quakers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Bastwick</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Church of <hi>England,</hi> a true Church against Montague <hi>ib.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Burgess</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Answer in Defence of three nocent Ceremonies <hi>ib.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Ball</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Pulpits Patronage <hi>ib.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Barns</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Needful Helps against desperate perplexity <hi>ib.</hi> 1624</item>
               <item>49 <hi>Brown</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Account of his Travels through <hi>Germany ib.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Bucaniers</hi> of <hi>America,</hi> Large Paper with Figures <hi>ib.</hi> 1784</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Burton</hi>'s learned Treatise of the Sabbath <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Binning</hi>'s (Capt. <hi>Tho.</hi>) Light to the Art of Gunery <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Bassus</hi> or Songs of sundry natures, in 3, 4, 5, &amp; 6 parts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1689</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Biggs</hi>'s <hi>(Noah.)</hi> Vanity of the Craft of Physick <hi>Lond.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>55 —His new Dispensatory <hi>ib.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>56 <hi>Barrough</hi>'s <hi>(Phil.)</hi> Method of Physick, wants Title <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>57 <hi>Boyle</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Certain Physiological Essays, and other Tracts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Bancker</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Introduction of Algebra <hi>ib.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>59 <hi>Davan</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> of the true ordering of a Common-wealth 1559</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Baldessar Castilio</hi>'s Courtier Englished, by <hi>Tho. Hobby Lond.</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Boyle</hi>'s Experiments touching Cold <hi>ib.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>62 —Spring and weight of the Air, 2. Vol. Compleat 1682</item>
               <item>63 —Continuation of Experiments of the weight of the Air 1669</item>
               <item>64 —Usefulness of Experimental Phylosophy <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>65 —Of natural Phylosophy, second part <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:42445:8"/>
               <item>66 Bible Compleat, with Chronology Large <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>67 —<hi>Idem</hi> Small <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>68 <hi>Barrow</hi> Of the Oath of Allegiance 1679</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Burrough</hi>'s on the Eleventh of <hi>Matthew Lond.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>70 —Of Earthly mindedness <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>71 Dr. <hi>Bates</hi> on the Attributes <hi>ib.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Brookes</hi>'s unsearchable Riches of Christ <hi>ib.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>73 —Cabinet of Choice Jewels <hi>ib.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>74 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Life of Faith <hi>ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>75 —Divine Life <hi>ib.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>76 —Crucif ing of the World by the Cross of Christ <hi>ib.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>77 —Reasons of the Christian Religion <hi>ib.</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>78 Dr. <hi>Beaumon<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s Observations on Dr. <hi>Mores</hi> Mystery of Godliness <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Broughton</hi> on <hi>Daniel</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>80 Sir <hi>Tho. Brown</hi> of Sepulchral Urns <hi>Lond.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>81 Brief Account of Antient Church-Government 1662</item>
               <item>82 <hi>Bastwick</hi> Against Mr. <hi>Wal. Montague</hi> Proving the Church of <hi>Engl.</hi> a true Church <hi>ib.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>83 <hi>Browning</hi>'s 6 Sermons of Publike Prayer <hi>ib.</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Blake</hi>'s Covenant Sealed <hi>ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Bentham</hi>'s Society of Saints <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>86 <hi>Burges</hi>'s Lawfulness of Kneeling at the Communion <hi>ib.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>87 Bishop <hi>Cozens</hi>'s Canons of the Holy Scripture <hi>Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Cradock</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Knowledge and Practice <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>89 —<hi>(Walther)</hi> Gospel Liberty in its extensions and Limitations 1648</item>
               <item>90 <hi>Jo. Calvin</hi>'s Institution of Christian Religion 1587</item>
               <item>91 —His Harmony on 3 Evangelists, with a Com. on <hi>John</hi> 1584</item>
               <item>92 <hi>Canterburian</hi>'s self Conviction 1641</item>
               <item>93 Common Prayer and Apocrypha for a <hi>Cambridge</hi> Bible <hi>Camb.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>94 Common Prayer of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> black Letter <hi>Lond.</hi> white Letter <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>95 <hi>Cartwright</hi>'s Reply to Archbishop <hi>Whitegift,</hi> 2 Vol. 1577</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Cleaver</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Exposition of the 10 Commandements <hi>Lond.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>97 —His Exposition of the whole Book of Proverbs <hi>Lond.</hi> 1615</item>
               <item>98 <hi>Cooper (Will.)</hi> Heaven opened, manifesting Salvation <hi>Lond.</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>99 —His holy Alphabet for <hi>Sions</hi> Scholars <hi>Lond.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>100 <hi>C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lling<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s Defence of King <hi>James</hi> against <hi>Bellarmine</hi>
               </item>
               <item>101 <hi>Cawdry</hi>'s <hi>(Dan.)</hi> Christian Sabbath Vindicated <hi>Lond.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Clagett</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Abuse of Gods Grace discovered <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>103 Considerations for the suppresing of Popery in <hi>England Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>134 Christs Victory over the Dragon, or Satans Downfal by <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Caryl</hi> On 22, 23, 24, 25, 26th Chapter of <hi>Job ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>106 —On the 32, 33, 34th Chapter of <hi>Job ib.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>107 <hi>Case</hi>'s Mount <hi>Pisgah,</hi> or a Prospect of Heaven <hi>ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Cooper</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Epitome of Cronicles <hi>Lond.</hi> 1559</item>
               <item>109 Courtier of Count <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ldessar Castilio ib.</hi> 1561</item>
               <item>110 <hi>Cumber</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> History in vindication of the Divine Right of Tythes <hi>ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>111 <hi>Chamber</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise against Judicial Astrology <hi>ib.</hi> 1601</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Cambden</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Remains concerning <hi>Brittanny ib.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Carlton</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Jurisdiction Regal, Episcopal and Papal <hi>ib.</hi> 1610</item>
               <item>114 Consolations for Grammar Schoolers <hi>ib.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Culverwell</hi>'s Elegant discourse of the Light of Nature <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1669</item>
               <pb n="11" facs="tcp:42445:8"/>
               <item>116 <hi>Carpenter</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Geography, in Two Books <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Collins</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Sector on a Quadrant <hi>Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>118 —Salt and Fishery <hi>ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Contareno</hi>'s <hi>(Gasp)</hi> Common-wealth and Government of <hi>Venice ib.</hi> 1599</item>
               <item>120 Civil and Ecclesiastical Rites of the <hi>Hebrews,</hi> by <hi>Tho. Goodwyn ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Clarindon</hi> against <hi>Hobs</hi>'s Leviathan <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>122 <hi>Coles</hi>'s Conferance against the Papists <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>123 Christian Policie <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>124 Dr. <hi>Charleton</hi>'s Enquiries into Human Nature <hi>ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Cradock</hi>'s Knowledge and Practice <hi>ib.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>126 <hi>Creeds</hi>'s Refuter Refuted, or Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi> Vindicated <hi>ib.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Culverwell</hi>'s Light of Nature <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Daille</hi>'s Treatise of the right use of the Fathers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Downe</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise of Justifying Faith <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>130 — his Defence of Justifying Faith <hi>ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Deering</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> 27 Lectures on the <hi>Hebrews Lond.</hi> 1576</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Dod's (Jo.)</hi> Exposition on the Ten Commandements <hi>ib.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>133 — his Seven Godly and Fruitful Sermons <hi>ih.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>134 — On the Lord's Prayer <hi>ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>135 Defence of the Innocency of the Three Ceremonies of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1619</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Dyke</hi>'s <hi>(Dan.)</hi> Mystery of Self-deceiving, with Two Treatises of Repentance 1633</item>
               <item>137 —Discovery of the Deceitfulness of Man's Heart 1633</item>
               <item>138 <hi>Deacon</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Doctrine of the Possession of <hi>Demoniacks Lond.</hi> 1610</item>
               <item>139 <hi>Dove</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise of the Conversion of <hi>Solomon ib.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Danaeus</hi>'s <hi>(Lamb.)</hi> Commentaries on the Twelve small Prophets <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1594</item>
               <item>141 —Another of the same, <hi>Englished</hi> by <hi>Jo. Stockwood i<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 1394</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Downame</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Christian Warfare, 3 volumes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>143 — his Divinity of God,</item>
               <item>144 — his Lectures on the Four First Chapters of <hi>Hoseah</hi> 1608</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Du barta</hi>'s Four Books, <hi>French</hi> and <hi>English,</hi> by <hi>William</hi> L'<hi>Isle Lond.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Digges</hi>'s <hi>(Leon.)</hi> Arithmetical Military Treatise called <hi>Stratioticos ib.</hi> 1579</item>
               <item>147 Dramatick Romance, Represented at <hi>A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>anjuez ib.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>148 Doctrine of Original Sin, by <hi>Nath. Stephens ib.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>149 Discourse of Sir <hi>John Smith</hi> concerning Weapons <hi>ib.</hi> 1590</item>
               <item>150 <hi>Dariot</hi>'s Judgment of the Stars <hi>ib.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Durham</hi> on the <hi>Song of Solomon ib.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>152 Dr. <hi>Donne</hi> of Self-Murther <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>153 <hi>Denison</hi> on <hi>Peter</hi> 2d Epist. <hi>ib.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>154 <hi>Drayton</hi>'s Muses, <hi>Elizium ib.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>155 Sir <hi>Ken. Digby</hi> of Bodies and of Mans Soul <hi>ib.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>156 <hi>Estey</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Expositions on divers parts of Scriptures <hi>ib.</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>157 <hi>Elton</hi>'s Complaint of a Sanctified Sinner answered <hi>ib.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>158 —On the Ten Commandements <hi>ib.</hi> 1687</item>
               <item>159 <hi>Edwards</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> of the particular Visibility of the Church, <hi>&amp;c. ib.</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>160 — his Treatise of the Civil Power in Ecclesiasticals, <hi>&amp;c. ib.</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>161 — of Suspension from the Lords Supper <hi>ib.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Eaton</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Hony-Comb of free Justification by Christ alone 1642</item>
               <item>163 Exposition of the Epistle to St. <hi>James,</hi> by <hi>Mayer Lond.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>164 Exposition on the Prophet <hi>Joel,</hi> by <hi>Edward Topsell ib.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>165 Explication of the <hi>Revelations</hi> of St. <hi>John,</hi> by <hi>Hugh Braughton</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:42445:9"/>
               <item>166 <hi>English</hi> Man's Treasure, or <hi>Vicary</hi>'s Chyrurgery, with many secrets <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>167 Elements of Armory 1610</item>
               <item>1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>8 Epitome of the whole Course of Physick, with Tables 1612</item>
               <item>169 — Another with the Examination of a Chyrurgian 1612</item>
               <item>170 <hi>English Arcadia,</hi> continuing Sir <hi>Phillip Sidney</hi>
               </item>
               <item>171 <hi>Ephemerides,</hi> beginning 1652. ending 1658. by <hi>Vincent Wing Ib.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Enchiridion Medicum,</hi> containing the Epitome of Physick <hi>Ib.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>173 Essays of Natural Experiments, made in the Accademie <hi>Del Cunento,</hi> with Cuts <hi>Ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Falkner</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Treatise of Reproaching and Censure <hi>Ib.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Fenton</hi>'s <hi>(Rog.)</hi> Tr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>atise of Usury, in Three Books <hi>Ib.</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Fletcher</hi>'s <hi>(Ph.)</hi> Way to Blessedness <hi>Ib.</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>177 — his Treatise, or Comment on the First <hi>Psalm Ib.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Ferrarius</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> of the good ordering a Common-wealth <hi>Ib.</hi> 1559</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Fisher</hi>'s <hi>(Ambr.)</hi> Defence of the <hi>English</hi> Liturgy <hi>Ib.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Flavel</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Hurbandry Spiritualized <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Featly</hi>'s <hi>(Dan.)</hi> Romish Fisher caught in his own Nett <hi>Ib.</hi> 1624</item>
               <item>182 Bp. <hi>Fisher</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Exposition of the Seven Penitential <hi>Psalms Ib.</hi> 1508</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Froysel</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Sermon concerning Grace and Temptations <hi>Ib.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>184 Familiar Epistles, by <hi>Ant. de Guevara Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>185 <hi>P. F</hi>'s Purple Island, with Piscatory Eclogs, <hi>&amp;c. Cambr.</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>186 Five Pious and Learned Discourses, by <hi>Rob. Shelford Ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>187 Form of wholsome Words, by <hi>Jo. Stoughton Lond.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>188 Faithful Surveyor, be <hi>Geo. Attwell Cambr.</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>189 Four-fold state of <hi>Adam,</hi> or History of <hi>Adam,</hi> by <hi>Hen. Hollard Lond.</hi> 1606</item>
               <item>190 Farewell Sermons, by the Non-Conformist <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>191 <hi>Grew (Ob.)</hi> Meditations upon the Parable of the Prodigal Son <hi>Ib.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>192 <hi>Gouge (Will.)</hi> of Gods Three Arrows, Plague, Famine and Sword <hi>ib.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>193 —his Whole Armour of God <hi>ib.</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>194 —his Spiritual Furniture for the Christian Soldier 1616</item>
               <item>195 <hi>Gurnal</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Christian in Compleat Armour <hi>ib.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>196 <hi>Gibben</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Qu<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>stions and Disputations on <hi>Genesis ib.</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>197 — his Exposition of the hard places in Scripture <hi>ib.</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>198 <hi>Goodman (Godfr.)</hi> Fall of Man, or the Corruption of Nature <hi>ib.</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Greenhill</hi>'s Exposition on the Five First Chapters of <hi>Ezekiel ib.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>200 — his Exposition on the Eleven First Chapters of <hi>Ezekiel ib.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>201 Dr. <hi>Gauden</hi>'s Binding of the Covenant and Covenanters <hi>ib.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>202 <hi>Giffard</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Sermons on the <hi>Revelations ib.</hi> 1599</item>
               <item>203 <hi>Gostwick</hi>'s Anatomy of <hi>Ananias Camb.</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>204 Grecian Story, an Historical Poem <hi>Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Godolphin</hi>'s Orphans Legacy <hi>ib.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>206 — <hi>Repertarium Canonicum ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>207 <hi>Guido</hi>'s Questions in Chirurgery <hi>Lond.</hi> 1579</item>
               <item>208 — Another of the same, with a Table <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>209 <hi>Golding</hi>'s <hi>(Arth.)</hi> Translation of <hi>Ovids Metamorphosis</hi> 1587</item>
               <item>210 <hi>Guevara</hi>'s <hi>(Ant. de)</hi> Familiar Epistles <hi>ib.</hi> 1577</item>
               <item>211 Gentlemans Accademy, or the Book of S. <hi>Albans ib.</hi> 1595</item>
               <item>212 <hi>Fra. Rous</hi>'s Seven Books of the <hi>Attick</hi> Antiquities <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Goodwyn (Tho.)</hi> Of the Civil and Ecclesiastical Rites of the <hi>Hebrews</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>214 —his Exposition of the <hi>Roman</hi> Antiquities <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>215 — his Parallel of <hi>English</hi> and <hi>Roman</hi> Offices <hi>Lond.</hi> 1625</item>
               <pb n="13" facs="tcp:42445:9"/>
               <item>216 <hi>Glanvil</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.) Scepsis Scientifica,</hi> against <hi>Tho. White Lond.</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>217 <hi>Gunter</hi>'s <hi>(Edmund)</hi> Works Compleat, 3d Edition <hi>ib.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>218 — Another with a new Treatise of Fortification <hi>ib.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>219 <hi>Gadbury (Jo.)</hi> Ephemerides of the C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>lestial motions for Ten Years <hi>ib.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>220 — <hi>Idem</hi> for Twenty years from 1682. to 1701. <hi>ib.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Gore</hi>'s Way to Prosper, several Sermons <hi>ib.</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>222 <hi>Gale</hi>'s Court of the <hi>Gentiles Oxon.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Grey</hi>'s Compleat Horse Man and Expert Farrier <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Gouge</hi>'s Surest and safest way of Thriving <hi>ib.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>225 <hi>Gregorie</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Works <hi>ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Hill</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Treatise of Life Everlasting <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1601</item>
               <item>227 <hi>Harrison</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Censures of the Church revived <hi>Lond.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Harris</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> his <hi>English</hi> Concord against <hi>Becanus</hi> examined <hi>Lond.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Heylin</hi>'s <hi>(Pet.)</hi> Parable of the Tares expounded and applied <hi>ib.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Huish (Alex.)</hi> Lectures upon the Lords-Prayer <hi>ib.</hi> 1626</item>
               <item>231 <hi>Holland</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> History of <hi>Adam ib.</hi> 1606</item>
               <item>232 <hi>Hocker</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Souls Vocation, or effectual Calling by Christ <hi>ib.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>233 — his Souls Exaltation <hi>ib.</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>234 —<hi>(Rich.)</hi> Discourse of Justification <hi>Oxon. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>b.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Harris</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Sermons on several occasions <hi>Lond.</hi> 1626</item>
               <item>236 <hi>Herbert (Percy)</hi> certain Conceptions or Considerations <hi>ib.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>237 <hi>Hal<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Saints <hi>Peter</hi>'s Prophesie of these last days <hi>ib.</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Horn</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Brazen Serpent, or Gods grand design <hi>ib.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Hammond</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Collection of Replies and Vindications <hi>ib.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>240 —Dispatcher Dispatcht, in defence of his Book of Schism <hi>ib.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>241 Historical Vindication of the Divine Right of Tythes, by <hi>Tho. Comber ib.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Harris</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Sermons being a Supplement to his Works <hi>ib.</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Holyday</hi>'s Motives to a Good Life, in Ten Sermons <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Holyoake</hi>'s Doctrine of Life, or of Mans Redemption <hi>Lond.</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>8</item>
               <item>245 History of the <hi>Irish</hi> Rebellion, by Sir <hi>John Temple ib.</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>246 History of Tythes, by <hi>Jo. Selden</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>247 Historical Narration of the Judgment of the <hi>English</hi> Divines about Election 1631</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Hitchcock</hi>'s Politick Plat for the Honour of the Prince <hi>Lond.</hi> 1380</item>
               <item>249 History of the <hi>Bucaniers</hi> in <hi>America,</hi> with Figures <hi>ib.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>250 History of <hi>Adam,</hi> or the Fourfold State of Man <hi>ib.</hi> 1606</item>
               <item>251 <hi>Hayward</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Jo.</hi>) Life and Reign of King <hi>Henry</hi> the Fou<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>th 1599</item>
               <item>252 <hi>Heydon</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Christ.</hi>) Defence of Judicial Astrologie <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>253 <hi>Howel (Ja.)</hi> Familiar Letters Domestick and Foreign <hi>Lond.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>254 History of the Imperial Estate of the Grand Seigreurs <hi>ib.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>255 History of the Seven Champions of Christendom <hi>ib.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>256 — Of the Destruction of <hi>Troy ib.</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>257 —Of <hi>Montileon</hi> Knight of the Oracle <hi>ib.</hi> 1649</item>
               <item>258 — Of <hi>Palmarin de Oliva ib.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>259 King <hi>Jame</hi>'s Pious directions for Students in Divinity <hi>ib.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>260 <hi>Jacob</hi>'s <hi>(Henry)</hi> of the Victory of Christ in our Redemption 1600</item>
               <item>261 <hi>Jus Divinum Ministeri Evangelici ib.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>262 Institution of Christian Religion, by <hi>John Calvin</hi>
               </item>
               <item>263 Dr <hi>Jacomb</hi>'s Sermons on the Eighth of the <hi>Romans ib.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>264 — <hi>Idem</hi> of a large Paper</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Jackson</hi> on the Pentateuch and H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>stori<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>al Bo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ks, 2 vol. <hi>ib.</hi> 1643</item>
               <pb n="14" facs="tcp:42445:10"/>
               <item>266 <hi>Jorden</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Discourse of the Suffocation of the Mother <hi>Lond.</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>267 Jewel of Health, or the Art of Distillation, by <hi>Georg. Baker</hi> 1576</item>
               <item>268 Introduction to Algebra, by <hi>Thomas Brancker</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>269 —Another with a Table of odd Numbers 1668</item>
               <item>270 J<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>wel for Gentry or a Dictionary for Hunting, Hawking, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>271 Irish Rebellion historically related, by Sir <hi>Jo. Temple</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>272 —Another of the same, with the Cruelites and Massacres 1646</item>
               <item>273 <hi>King</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Lectures on <hi>Jonas</hi> delivered at <hi>York</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>274 <hi>Knewstubs</hi> Lectures on the 20th of <hi>Exodus</hi> 1579</item>
               <item>275 <hi>Ley</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Sunday a Sabbath 1641</item>
               <item>276 —The Oath Imposed by the 6th Canon of the late Synod 1641</item>
               <item>277 Bishop <hi>Lucy</hi>'s Treatise of a Minister 1670</item>
               <item>278 —His answer to Mr. <hi>Hobbs</hi> his Leviathan 1673</item>
               <item>279 <hi>Luther</hi>'s <hi>(Mart.)</hi> Commentaries on the 15 Psalms of Degrees 1637</item>
               <item>270 —His select and chosen Sermons 1581</item>
               <item>281 —On the <hi>Galathians</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>282 Bishop <hi>Laney</hi>'s five Sermons 1669</item>
               <item>283 <hi>Lisle</hi>'s ancient Monuments in the <hi>Saxon</hi> Tongue 1638</item>
               <item>284 <hi>Lock</hi>'s <hi>(H.)</hi> Ecclesiastes otherwise called the Preacher 1579</item>
               <item>285 <hi>Langley</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Persecuted Minister 1656</item>
               <item>286 <hi>Leigh</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Observations on the Hebrew words of the Old Testament 1642</item>
               <item>287 —<hi>Critica Sacra</hi> on the New Testament 1646</item>
               <item>288 <hi>Lemot</hi>'s Recantation Sermon, on <hi>Rom.</hi> 5.2. 1675</item>
               <item>289 <hi>Leybourn</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Geometrical exercises for young Seamen 1669</item>
               <item>290 <hi>L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>pez. (Od.)</hi> Report of the Kingdom of <hi>Congo</hi> in <hi>Africa</hi> 1597</item>
               <item>291 <hi>La Stratonica,</hi> or the Unfortunate Queen 1651</item>
               <item>292 <hi>London</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Catalogue of the most Vendible Books in <hi>England</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>293 <hi>Lilly</hi>'s (Christian Astrology 1659</item>
               <item>294 <hi>Lisle</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Four Books of <hi>Du-Bartas,</hi> with a Commentary 1637</item>
               <item>295 <hi>Low</hi>'s Chyrurgery 1654</item>
               <item>296 <hi>Le Febure</hi>'s Compleat Body of Chymistry 1670</item>
               <item>297 Bishop <hi>Morley</hi>'s Several Treatises on several occasions 1683</item>
               <item>298 <hi>Mayer</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Exposition of the Epistle of St. <hi>James</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>299 —His English Catechisme 1621</item>
               <item>300 <hi>Mede</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Works on divers Texts of Scripture 1648</item>
               <item>301 <hi>Montagu</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.) Diatribae</hi> on <hi>Selden</hi>'s History of Tythes 1621</item>
               <item>302 <hi>Moulin</hi>'s <hi>(Pet. du)</hi> Buckler of Faith 1631</item>
               <item>303 —His Confession of the Reformed Churches in <hi>France</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Morton</hi>'s Two Treatises of the state of the Kingdom of <hi>Israel</hi> 1596</item>
               <item>305 Man of Sin or a Dicourse of Popery 1677</item>
               <item>306 Mysterie and power of Godliness, by <hi>Henry Vane</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>307 Mysterie of self deceiving, <hi>Daniel Dike</hi> 1617</item>
               <item>308 <hi>Mot.</hi> (Sir <hi>de la</hi>) Abominations of the Church of <hi>Rome</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>309 Dr. <hi>More</hi> on <hi>Daniel</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>310 —On the <hi>Revelation</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>311 <hi>Montague</hi>'s Devout Essayes second par<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 1654</item>
               <item>312 <hi>More</hi>'s principles for young Princes <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>313 <hi>Moxon</hi>'s <hi>(Jos)</hi> Tutor to Astronomy, and Geography 1659</item>
               <item>314 <hi>G. Markham</hi>'s way to get Wealth 1683</item>
               <item>315 —Master piece revived with an Appendix 1681</item>
               <pb n="15" facs="tcp:42445:10"/>
               <item>316 <hi>Mulcaster</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Positions for the trayning up of Children <hi>Lond.</hi> 1581</item>
               <item>317 Dr. <hi>Monardus</hi>'s Treatise of rarities in the <hi>West Indies</hi> 1577</item>
               <item>318 <hi>Masterson</hi>'s Arithmetick 1592</item>
               <item>319 <hi>More</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Confutation of Judiciary Astrology 1681</item>
               <item>320 —His Exposition upon <hi>Daniel</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>321 <hi>Mascal</hi>'s <hi>(Leon.)</hi> of the Government of Cattel 1620</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Napier (Jo.)</hi> Discovery of the Revelation of St. <hi>John Edenb.</hi> 1591</item>
               <item>323 <hi>Nash</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.) Quaternio,</hi> or fourfold way to Happiness <hi>Lond.</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>324 Naked Popery, or the naked Falshood, by <hi>Rich. Baxter</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>325 Bishop <hi>Nicholson</hi> on the Church Catechisme 1671</item>
               <item>326 <hi>Nova Francia,</hi> or a Description of New <hi>France Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>327 <hi>Nicolis</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Lapidary, or History of precious Stones <hi>Camb.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>328 <hi>Norwood</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Doctrine of Triangles <hi>Lond.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>329 <hi>Newton</hi>'s Help to Calculation 1657</item>
               <item>330 <hi>Ovia</hi>'s <hi>Metamorphoses</hi> Englished, by <hi>Arch. Golding.</hi> 1567</item>
               <item>331 Dr. <hi>Owen</hi> against Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> of Schisme 1681</item>
               <item>332 <hi>Philips</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Certain godly and learned Sermons 1605</item>
               <item>333 <hi>Parr</hi>'s <hi>(Elnath.)</hi> Exposition of the Romans 1618</item>
               <item>334 <hi>Perkins</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Commentary on the <hi>Galatians Camb.</hi> 1617</item>
               <item>335 <hi>Parker</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Revindication in the behalf of Dr. <hi>Drayton Lond.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>336 <hi>Poclkington</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Dead Vicars plea 1637</item>
               <item>337 Psalms in English Metre. White Letter <hi>Camb.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>338 Preaches Guard and Guide <hi>Lond.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>339 Parable of the Sower and of the Seed, by <hi>(Taylor)</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>340 Pilgrimage of Kings and Princes 1653</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Pomarius Valentinus (Petrus)</hi> Epitome of the Art of Physick 1612</item>
               <item>342 Passions of the mind in General, by <hi>Tho. Wright</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>343 <hi>Perrott</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Jo.</hi>) Government of <hi>Ireland</hi> from 1584 to 1588 1626</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Person</hi>'s <hi>(David)</hi> Varieties or Survey of Excellent matters 1635</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Purple</hi> Isl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>nd, or the Isle of <hi>Man,</hi> &amp;c. <hi>Camb.</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>347 <hi>Prynne</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Antipathy of the English Lordly-Prelacy <hi>Lond.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>348 —His pacifick examination of the Common Prayer 1661</item>
               <item>349 <hi>Power</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Experimental Philosopy in 3 Books 166</item>
               <item>350 Politick, Moral, and martial Discourses, by <hi>Jac. Heraualt</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>351 Positions for the Trayning up of Children 1581</item>
               <item>352 <hi>Prideaux (Matth.)</hi> Introduction for Reading of Histories <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>353 <hi>Pointz</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Rob.</hi>) Vindication of Monarchy <hi>Lond.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>354 <hi>Pitiscus (Barth.)</hi> Trigonometry, or the Doctrine of Triangles <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>355 P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ilosophical Discourse for the preserving of Health 1622</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Querer por Querer,</hi> a dramatick Romance 1671</item>
               <item>357 <hi>Rhegius</hi>'s <hi>(Ʋrb.)</hi> Dialogue of Christs Sermon going to <hi>Emaus</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>358 Reply to a Confernce between B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>shop <hi>Laud</hi> and Mr. <hi>Fisher</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>359 Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> unveiled, by <hi>Henry More</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>360 Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> Revealed, by <hi>Jo. Napier Edinb.</hi> 1593</item>
               <item>361 —Another with certain Oracles of <hi>Sybilla</hi> 1593</item>
               <item>362 <hi>Rogers</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Protestant Church existent <hi>Lond.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>363 —<hi>(Nehemiah)</hi> The true Convert 1620</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Ramsden</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Gleanings of Gods Harvest 1630</item>
               <item>365 <hi>Randall</hi>'s <hi>(Josh.)</hi> 23 Sermons on the Sacrament 1610</item>
               <item>366 —<hi>(Joh.)</hi> 39 Lectures of the Church 1631</item>
               <pb n="16" facs="tcp:42445:11"/>
               <item>367 <hi>Rutherford</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Plea for <hi>Pauls</hi> Presbytery in <hi>Scotland Lond.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>368 —Of the Government of the Church of <hi>Scotland</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>369 <hi>Roger</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Practical Catechisme 1632</item>
               <item>370 —<hi>(Rich.)</hi> 7 Treatises directing to true Happiness 1630</item>
               <item>371 Reply to the Relation of a Conference between <hi>Laud</hi> and <hi>Fisher</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>372 <hi>Reeve</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Christian Divinity 1631</item>
               <item>373 Rest of the 2d Reply of <hi>Tho. Cartwright</hi> concerning Church power 1577</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Rous</hi> Greek Ant<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>quities <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>375 <hi>Rogers</hi> on the 39 Articles of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>376 <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>oborough</hi> of Justification 1650</item>
               <item>377 Rights of the Kingdom, or Custom of our Ancestors <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>378 Reasons proving the Lawfulness of the Oath of Allegiance 1611</item>
               <item>379 Report of the Kingdom of <hi>Congo,</hi> a Region of <hi>Africa</hi> 1597</item>
               <item>380 <hi>Rosse (Alex.)</hi> The Earth no wandring Star 1646</item>
               <item>381 <hi>Record</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Castel of Knowledge 1596</item>
               <item>382 Remains concerning <hi>Brittain,</hi> by <hi>William Cambden</hi>
               </item>
               <item>383 Reformed Common-wealth of <hi>Bees,</hi> and of <hi>Silkworms</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>384 Relation of the Siege of <hi>Vienna,</hi> with Cuts 1684</item>
               <item>385 <hi>Reading</hi>'s A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>tidote against Anabaptism against Bishop <hi>Taylor</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>386 Dr. <hi>Reeves</hi>'s <hi>Englands</hi> Restitution in several Sermons 1661</item>
               <item>387 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Impartial account of the History of Separation 1682</item>
               <item>388 —His <hi>Origines Sacrae,</hi> or a rational account of Christian Faith 1680</item>
               <item>389 <hi>Stoughton</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Introduction to the Body of Divinity 1640</item>
               <item>390 —His choice Sermons on select Occasions 1650</item>
               <item>391 <hi>Sh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lford</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Five pious and learned Discourses <hi>Camb.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>392 <hi>Sclater</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Exposition with notes on the 2d of the <hi>Thessalonians Lond.</hi> 1627</item>
               <item>393 —His Key to the Key of Scripture, or notes on the <hi>Romans</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>394 —His Sermons experimental for a wounded Spirit 1638</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Swinnock</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Door of Salvation opened 1671</item>
               <item>396 —Fading of the Flesh and flour sh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ng of Faith 1662</item>
               <item>397 Seven Treatises guiding to true Happiness, by <hi>Rich. Rogers</hi> 1627</item>
               <item>398 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.) Irenicum,</hi> or Weapon Salve for the Churches wounds 1662</item>
               <item>399 <hi>Shaw</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.) Origo Protestantium,</hi> or an answer to a Popish Manuscript 1677</item>
               <item>400 <hi>Symonds (Will.) Pisgah Evangelica,</hi> by the method of the Revelation 1606</item>
               <item>401 —of the mutations of the Church, from 97 to 1603 1606</item>
               <item>402 <hi>Stephens</hi>'s <hi>(Nath.)</hi> Doctrine of Original Sin 1658</item>
               <item>403 Dr. <hi>Sutton</hi>'s Lectures upon the eleventh Chapter to the <hi>Romans</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>404 Saints society delivered in 15 Sermons</item>
               <item>405 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(Sa.)</hi> exposition on the sixth Chapter of <hi>Hoseah</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Shute</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Judgment and Mercy, or the Plague of Frogges 1645</item>
               <item>407 <hi>Squire</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Exposition of 2d Chapter to the <hi>Thessalonians</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>408 <hi>Stoughton</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> 13 Sermons preached at <hi>Aldermanbury London</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>409 Sermons or Meditations on <hi>Joell,</hi> by <hi>Edw. Topsell</hi> 1599</item>
               <item>410 <hi>Sympson</hi>'s <hi>(A.)</hi> Exposition of the seven poenitential <hi>Psalms</hi>
               </item>
               <item>411 <hi>Saxon</hi> Treatise concerning the Old and New Testament 1613</item>
               <item>412 <hi>Symonds</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Vindication of King <hi>Charles</hi> the First, or the Subjects Duty 1648</item>
               <item>413 <hi>Smith</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Joh.</hi>) Certain discourses of the forms and Effects of divers Weapons 1590</item>
               <item>414 <hi>Smith</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) Common-wealth of <hi>England</hi> 1594</item>
               <item>415 <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ubbs</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Justification of the present War against the <hi>Hollander</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>416 Suppressing of Popery in this Kingdom considered 1677</item>
               <pb n="17" facs="tcp:42445:11"/>
               <item>417 <hi>Selden</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> History of Tythes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>418 —Another with the practice of payment 1618</item>
               <item>419 <hi>Stirrup</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Description of the Universal <hi>Quadrat</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>420 —His Compleat Diallist 1650</item>
               <item>421 <hi>Swan</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.) Speculum Mundi,</hi> or a Glass representing the Face of the World 1670</item>
               <item>422 —His <hi>Redde Debitum</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>423 <hi>Sadler</hi>'s Rights of the Kingdom, or Customs of our Ancestors 1682</item>
               <item>424 <hi>Stray</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Voyages &amp; Travels, with Figures 1684</item>
               <item>425 <hi>Soranzo</hi>'s <hi>(Laz.)</hi> History of the <hi>Ottoman</hi> Empire 1603</item>
               <item>426 <hi>Street</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> New Theorie of the Celestial motions 1661</item>
               <item>427 —His Genuine use and Effects of Guns 1674</item>
               <item>428 School of <hi>Salern</hi>'s Regiment of Health 1649</item>
               <item>439 <hi>Swammardam</hi>'s Hist. and Anat. of the <hi>Ephemeron,</hi> a Fly that lives but 5 Hours 1681</item>
               <item>430 <hi>Sheringham</hi>'s Kings supremacy Asserted 1682</item>
               <item>431 Suppliment to the Morning Ezercises at Criplegate <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>432 <hi>Symons</hi>'s four Sermons 1642</item>
               <item>433 <hi>Swadling</hi>'s Jesuite the Chief of State Heretiques 1647</item>
               <item>434 <hi>Sarson</hi>'s <hi>Cronologia Vapulans,</hi> on 1 <hi>Tim.</hi> 1.15. 1645</item>
               <item>435 <hi>Elius Sejanus</hi> his Life or the Powerful favorite 1628</item>
               <item>436 <hi>Sedgwick</hi>'s Humble Sinner Resolved 1660</item>
               <item>437 <hi>Sedgwick</hi>'s <hi>(Obed.)</hi> Anatomy of Sin 1660</item>
               <item>438 —Fountain opened 1660</item>
               <item>449 <hi>Swinnock</hi>'s Christian Mans Calling Vol. 2. 1668</item>
               <item>440 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s Collection of several Treatises 1675</item>
               <item>441 <hi>Senault</hi>'s Christian Man 1650</item>
               <item>442 <hi>Stubbs</hi>'s further Justification of the present War against the <hi>Netherland</hi>'s 1673</item>
               <item>443
<list>
                     <item>Legends no Histories 1670</item>
                     <item>Against Mr. <hi>Glanvill</hi> and the Royal Society 1670</item>
                     <item>Censure of the History of the Royal Society 1671</item>
                  </list>
               </item>
               <item>444 Dr. <hi>Tenison</hi>'s Discourse of Idolatry and Superstition 1678</item>
               <item>445 Two Treatises of Reproaching and Censure, by <hi>W. Falkner</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>446 <hi>Topsell</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Times Lementation, or an Exposition on <hi>Ioell</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>447 <hi>Twisse (Will.)</hi> Of the Morality of the fourth Commandment 1641</item>
               <item>448 <hi>Taylor (Tho.)</hi> Christs Victory over the Dragon 1633</item>
               <item>459 —His Exposition of St. <hi>Peters</hi> Sermon to the Gentiles <hi>Camb.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>450 —Of the Parable of the sower, and of the Seed <hi>Lond.</hi> 1621</item>
               <item>451 —His way to true Happiness 1617</item>
               <item>452 —His <hi>Japhats</hi> first perswasion in <hi>Sems</hi> Tent <hi>Camb.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>453 —<hi>(Jer.)</hi> Of the Sacred Order and Office of Episcopacy <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1642</item>
               <item>454 —Dissuasive from Popery <hi>Lond.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>455 True watch, the third Part, by <hi>John Brinsly</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>456 <hi>Twisden</hi>'s Historical vindication of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>457 <hi>Thornedike</hi>'s <hi>(Herb.)</hi> Just Weights and Measures 1680</item>
               <item>458 <hi>Turnbull</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Exposition of the Epistle of St. <hi>James</hi> 1606</item>
               <item>469 Times Lamentation, or an Exposition on <hi>Joell</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>460 Treatise of the Nature and Definition of justifying Faith <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>461 Treatise of the mysterie of self Deceiving 1616</item>
               <item>462 The totall summ, in Defence of the Catholicks against <hi>Chillingworth</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>463 Third part of the true Watch by <hi>Jo. Brinsly</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>464 True History of Councils enlarged and Defended 1682</item>
               <pb n="18" facs="tcp:42445:12"/>
               <item>465 Treatise of Original sin, by <hi>Nat. Stephens</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>466 <hi>Temple</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Jo.</hi>) History of the Irish Rebellion 1646</item>
               <item>467 —Another with an account of the Massacres 1646</item>
               <item>468 Treasure of <hi>Evonymus,</hi> or a Book of Distillations <hi>Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>469 Treatise of Magistracy 1647</item>
               <item>470 Treatise of the Passions of the minde in General, by <hi>Tho. Wright</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>471 Treatise of the Training up on Children, by <hi>Rich. Mulcaster</hi> 1581</item>
               <item>472 <hi>Thorne</hi>'s Souls solace in times of Trouble 1643</item>
               <item>473 <hi>Thomson</hi>'s Antichrist Arraigned 1681</item>
               <item>474 <hi>Trap</hi> On the Pentateuch 1650</item>
               <item>475 <hi>Viri<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s <hi>(Pet.)</hi> Exposition of the Lords Prayer <hi>Lond.</hi> 1582</item>
               <item>476 —His Christian Disputations 1579</item>
               <item>477 <hi>Vane</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Hen.</hi>) Mystery and power of Godliness 1655</item>
               <item>478 —His Retired mans Meditation 1655</item>
               <item>479 <hi>Villegas (Alph.) Flos Sanctorum,</hi> or Lives of Saint</item>
               <item>480 <hi>Venner</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.) Via recta ad vitam Longam</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>481 <hi>Virgill</hi>'s <hi>Aeneids</hi> English verse 1607</item>
               <item>482 <hi>Vicar</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.) Englands</hi> Parliamentary Chronicle 2 Vol. 1644</item>
               <item>483 —His God in the Mount, or <hi>Englands</hi> Remembrancer 1641 1586</item>
               <item>484 <hi>Vigo</hi>'s Whole Book of Chyrurgery</item>
               <item>485 <hi>Valera</hi>'s <hi>(Cypr.)</hi> Lives of the Popes, and their Doctrine 1600</item>
               <item>486 Unfortunate Queen a Romance 1651</item>
               <item>487 <hi>Wotton</hi>'s <hi>(Ant.)</hi> Defence of Perkins Reformed Catholick 1606</item>
               <item>488 Bishop <hi>Whitgift</hi>'s Answer to Libel intituled an admonition to the Parliament 1572</item>
               <item>489 <hi>White</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Way to the true Church 1608</item>
               <item>490 <hi>Watson</hi>'s Ten quodlibetical questions 1602</item>
               <item>491 <hi>Westfield</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.) Englands</hi> Face in <hi>Israels</hi> Glass 1646</item>
               <item>492 <hi>Weemse (Jo.)</hi> Pourtracture of the Image of God in Man 1632</item>
               <item>493 —His Christian Synagogue 1623</item>
               <item>494 Way to Happiness a Comment on the 1st Psalm, by <hi>Phin. Fletcher</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>495 <hi>Wright</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Passions of the minde in General 1630</item>
               <item>496 —Another with sundry new Discourses 1630</item>
               <item>497 Way to get Wealth, by <hi>Gerv. Markam</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>498 <hi>Wing</hi>'s <hi>(Vincent) Ephemerides</hi> from 1659 to 1671 1658</item>
               <item>499 <hi>Waller</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Essays of natural experiments made in <hi>Tuscany</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>500 <hi>Wright</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Certain Errours in Navigation 1610</item>
               <item>501 <hi>Webster</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Metalographia, or H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>story of Mettals 1671</item>
               <item>502 Great quantities of variety of Sticht Books Twelve in a Bundle</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>English in <hi>Octavo.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>1 <hi>Agrippa (Hen. Corn.)</hi> Vanity of Arts and Sciences <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>2 Art of speaking, by <hi>M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ssieurs du Port Royal</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>3 Antient and modern Rites of Funerals, in use in the World 1683</item>
               <item>4 Addresses to the Non-Confomists, beginning with the Anabaptists 1676</item>
               <item>5 Accidence in Questions and Answers 1683</item>
               <item>6 Answer to Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Church-History of Bishops, by <hi>Morice</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>7 Accont of the Ceremonies and proceedings in the Conclave at <hi>Rome</hi> 1677</item>
               <pb n="19" facs="tcp:42445:12"/>
               <item>8 An account of a Late Voyage to <hi>Athens</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Addison</hi>'s <hi>(Lanc.)</hi> West <hi>Barbary,</hi> or the Revolutions of <hi>Fez</hi> and <hi>Morocco Oxon.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>10 Assertion for true and Christian Church-policy 1604</item>
               <item>11 —Another of the same wants Title</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Ashwell</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Discourse of the Sacrament 1663</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Abbot</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Milk for Babes, with three Sermons <hi>Lond.</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>14 Assembly of Divines Confession of Faith examined 1651</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Adam</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Main principles of Christian Religion 1677</item>
               <item>16 Animadversions on Mr. <hi>Ferguson</hi>'s Interest of Reason in Religion 1676</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Ainsworth</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Communion of Saints 1615</item>
               <item>18 —Of Fellowship in this present Life 1640</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Arnand</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Mystery of Godliness 1671</item>
               <item>20 Arguments for the <hi>Jews</hi> admission into <hi>England</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>21 St. <hi>Agnes</hi> Virgin and Martyr her Life, by <hi>L. Sherling</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Answorth</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Marrow of the Bible 1652</item>
               <item>24 Anatomy of Popery or a Catalogue of Popish Errors 1673</item>
               <item>25 Answer to Doctor <hi>Sherlock</hi>'s knowledge of Christ, by <hi>Edw. Polhill</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>26 Accomplisht Ladies Delight, in Preserving Cookery, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>27 —Another with the Compleat Cooks Guide 1677</item>
               <item>28 Animadversions on two late Books concerning Marriage, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>29 Archery Revived, or the Bow-mans Excellency 1676</item>
               <item>30 Art of Measuring or the Carpenters new Rule described 1669</item>
               <item>31 Advice to the Conforming, and Non-Conforming Ministers and people 1673</item>
               <item>32 <hi>Abraham</hi>'s Humble Intercession for <hi>Sodom,</hi> by <hi>Sam. Whiting</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>6</item>
               <item>33 Arcadian Princes, or the Triumph of Justice, by <hi>R. Braithwaite</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>34 <hi>Allein</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Allarm to unconverted Sinners 1675</item>
               <item>35 —Catechisme 1674</item>
               <item>36 —His Life and Death 1673</item>
               <item>37 —His Remains, <hi>viz.</hi> his Art of Dyingwell 1674</item>
               <item>38 —Godly fear 1674</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Adams (Tho.)</hi> Principles of the Christian Religion 1677</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Ames (Will.)</hi> Substance of Christian Religion 1659</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Amiraldus (Moses)</hi> Of the State of good men after Death 16</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Allen</hi>'s Works in vind. of the Church of <hi>Engl.</hi> being several Treatises bound in 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>43 Annimadversions on <hi>Greek</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> Historians <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Amyrald</hi> concerning Religions 1660</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Arminius</hi>'s Just Mans Defence 1675</item>
               <item>46 Art of memory made Plain 1651</item>
               <item>47 Art of Oratory, or vulgar Errors in parctice Censured 1659</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Archer</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Every man his own Doctor with an Herbal 1673</item>
               <item>49 Astrological Judgment of Diseases, by <hi>Nic. Culpeper</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>50 Angling Improv'd, being a general discourse of Angling 1668</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Ashmole</hi>'s <hi>(Elias)</hi> Chymical Collections 1650</item>
               <item>52 Amorous Traveller, or the night Adventures 1671</item>
               <item>53 Accomplished Courtier 1658</item>
               <item>54 Bible with References <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>55 —<hi>Idem,</hi> with Notes <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>56 <hi>Barrow</hi>'s <hi>(Is.)</hi> Sermon on the Passion of our Blessed Saviour <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>57 —His duty and Reward of Bounty to the Poor 1630</item>
               <item>58 Bishop <hi>Bramhall</hi>'s Just vindication of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1654</item>
               <pb n="20" facs="tcp:42445:13"/>
               <item>59 <hi>Brambal</hi>'s Consecration of Protestant Bishops vindicated 1664</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Basire</hi>'s <hi>(Is.)</hi> Sacrilidge arraigned and condemned 1668</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Catechism and Sermon on <hi>Exodus</hi> 23.2. 1660</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Bodington</hi>'s <hi>Solomons</hi> Coronation, and Espousals 1662</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Brinsly</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Groan of <hi>Israel</hi> and spiritual <hi>Vertigo</hi> 1625</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Brathwate</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Anatomy of Mortality 1621</item>
               <item>65 —His Poems, Satyrs Ecclogues and Odes 1622</item>
               <item>66 <hi>Bilson</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Difference between Christian and Unchristian Rebellion 1586</item>
               <item>67 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Essays</item>
               <item>68 <hi>Brook</hi>'s Ark for all Gods <hi>Noahs</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Bogan</hi>'s Meditation of the mirth of a Christian Life 1635</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Byfeild</hi>'s Gospel Glory 1653</item>
               <item>70 <hi>Beesley</hi>'s Souls Conflict 1657</item>
               <item>71 <hi>Burrough</hi>'s Gospel Fear 1674</item>
               <item>72 Bishop <hi>Bramhal</hi>'s vindication 1673</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Boteler</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Sermon at the Funeral of the Lady <hi>Sybilla Anderson</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>74 —His Sermon at <hi>Edmund</hi> Earle of <hi>Mugraves</hi> Funeral 1659</item>
               <item>75 —His Sermon at <hi>Kingstone,</hi> upon Crowning the King</item>
               <item>76 —His no Home but Heaven 1664</item>
               <item>77 —His Collection of Sermons together 1660</item>
               <item>78 <hi>Boughen</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Exposition of the Chatechism of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Bulstrode</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Miscellany of divine Sentences 1657</item>
               <item>80 <hi>Ball</hi>'s grounds of the Christian Religion 33</item>
               <item>81 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s <hi>(Gilb.)</hi> Mistery of Iniquity unvaled 1673</item>
               <item>82 <hi>Beza</hi>'s <hi>(Th.)</hi> Summ of the Christian Faith <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>83 <hi>Brown</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Discription of the annual World 1641</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Burton</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Rowsing of the Sluggard, in seven Sermons 1634</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Brook</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Staff of Christian Faith 1577</item>
               <item>86 <hi>Byfiold</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Begining of the Doctrine of Christ <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>87 <hi>Bryan</hi>'s 13 Sermons 1675</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Benj.)</hi> Non-Conformity without Controversie 1670</item>
               <item>89 Book of the Revelations explicated by <hi>A. B. Peganius Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>90 <hi>Bale</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Image of both Churches <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>91 <hi>Blakie</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Collection of Sermons preacht at Morning Lectures 1573</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Bayly</hi>'s <hi>(Lewis)</hi> Practice of Piety 1676</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Barrett</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Gods Love to Man, in several Discourses 1678</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Bolton</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> True bounds to Christian Freedom 1656</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> 3 Disputations of the safe Religion 1657</item>
               <item>97 —his Treatise of Justifying Righteousnes in two Books 1676</item>
               <item>98 —his more proofs of Infant Church-membership 1671</item>
               <item>99 —his Certainty of Christianity without Popery 1672</item>
               <item>100 —his Satisfaction, which is the true Religion 1674</item>
               <item>101 —Directions to prevent Miscarrying in Conversion <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>102 <hi>Bogan</hi>'s <hi>(Zach.)</hi> Meditations of Mirth and Christianity 1653</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Bucolicks</hi> of <hi>(Bapt.) Mantuan,</hi> in 10 Eclogues 1656</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Bernier</hi>'s <hi>(Mr.)</hi> Continuation of the Memoires concerning the Mogol 1672</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Bosworth</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Chast and lost Lovers, with other Poems 1653</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Baldwin</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Treatise of moral Philosopy <hi>Ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>107 <hi>Boyle</hi>'s <hi>(R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>b.)</hi> Essay about the Origin and Vertue of Gems, with <hi>Steno</hi> of Solids 1672</item>
               <item>108 —his Experiments of Qualities, with other Trades 1676</item>
               <pb n="21" facs="tcp:42445:13"/>
               <item>109 —Essays of the subtilty of Effluviums 1673</item>
               <item>110 —Natural History of Humane Blood 1684</item>
               <item>111 —his Considerations touching the stile of Scripture 1668</item>
               <item>112 —History of mineral Waters 1685</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Bury</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Husbandmans Companion 1677</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Baker</hi>'s Arithmetick 1659</item>
               <item>115 Book of knowledge 1673</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Barratt</hi>'s Travels into the <hi>Abisins</hi> Country 1670</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Bridges</hi>'s Seven Sermons 1672</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Blagrave</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Supplement, or Enlargment to <hi>Culpepers</hi> English Physitian 1664</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Baker</hi>'s Arithmetick, with the Art of Decimals, by <hi>Hen. Philips</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>120 <hi>Begninus</hi>'s <hi>(Joan.) Tyrocinium Chymicum,</hi> Chymical Essays 1660</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Butts</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Dyets dry Dinner in eight several Courses 1599</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Butler</hi>'s Scale of Interest 1633</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Boteler</hi>'s Six Dialogues about Sea Services 1685</item>
               <item>124 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s <hi>(Gilb.)</hi> Abridgment of the History of the Reformation 1683</item>
               <item>125 —his passages of the Life and Death of the Earle of <hi>Rochester</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>126 <hi>Blount</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Glosograpy, or Dictionary of Hard Words 1681</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s Mistery of Iniquity unvailed in a Discourse against the Papists 1673</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Bright</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Treatise of Prayer, with occasional Observations 1678</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Barry</hi>'s <hi>(Ger.)</hi> Painters voyage into <hi>Italy</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Brown</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Compleat Treatise of preternatural Tumors 1678</item>
               <item>131 Bp. <hi>Barlow</hi> of the Danger of the Popish princiles and positions 1679</item>
               <item>132 Bishops Right to Vote in Parliament, stated and argued 1680</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Burlace</hi> of the Reduction of <hi>Ireland</hi> to the Crown of <hi>England</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>134 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Treatise of Justifying Righteousness 1676</item>
               <item>135 —his Poor-mans Family Book 1675</item>
               <item>136 —his Universal Concord 1660</item>
               <item>137 —his Directions and perswasions to a sound Conversion 1670</item>
               <item>138 —his Reformed Pastor 1657</item>
               <item>139 <hi>Bright</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Treatise of Melancholy 1586</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Busschoff</hi>'s <hi>(Herm.)</hi> Two Treatises of the Gout and Midwifry 1676</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Blancard</hi>'s <hi>(Steph.)</hi> Physical Dictionary explaining all its Terms 1984</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Barbett</hi>'s <hi>(Paul)</hi> Practice of Physick, with <hi>Deckers</hi> Notes 1675</item>
               <item>143 —his Chirurgical and Anatomical Works 1676</item>
               <item>144 <hi>Brown</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) Certain miscellany Tracts 1684</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Buschoff</hi>'s <hi>(Herm.)</hi> Treatise of the Gout, with <hi>Paul Barbets</hi> Chirurgery 1676</item>
               <item>146 Body of military mediciens experimented, by <hi>Raymundus Mindererus</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Bayle</hi>'s <hi>(Franc.)</hi> Discourse of the System of <hi>Des Cartes</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>148 <hi>Blagrave</hi>'s Supplement to <hi>Culpepers</hi> English Physitian 1674</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Boyle</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Essays of Effluviums, with new Experiments 1673</item>
               <item>150 —his Experiments about the Poracity of Bodies, in two Essays 1684</item>
               <item>151 —Occasional Reflections on several Subjects 1669</item>
               <item>152 —his Experiments and Considerations touching Colours 1670</item>
               <item>153 —his Tracts of Cosmical qualities of Things <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1761</item>
               <item>154 —his Essays to make Flame and Air pondarable <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>155 —his sceptical Chymist <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>156 —his Tracts of Flame and Air <hi>Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>157 —Some Considerations of the Style of Scriptures 1675</item>
               <item>158 —his Motives and Incentives to the Love of God 1678</item>
               <pb n="22" facs="tcp:42445:14"/>
               <item>159 —his Essay about the Origine and virtue of Gems 1672</item>
               <item>160 —his Experiments and Observations upon the Icy Noctiluca 1681</item>
               <item>161 —his excellency of Theology compared to natural Philosopy 1674</item>
               <item>162 —his Considerations about the Possibility of the Resurrection 1675</item>
               <item>163 —his Tracts against Mr. <hi>Hobbs</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>164 —his Tracts concerning Celestial Magnets, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>165 <hi>Brevent Saul</hi> and <hi>Samuel</hi> at <hi>Endor Oxon.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>166 <hi>Beverley</hi>'s Great Soul of Man <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Burnet</hi>'s Life of the Earl of <hi>Rochester</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Basil (Valintine</hi> of Natural and Supernatural things 1670</item>
               <item>169 Dr. <hi>Bates</hi> Great Duty of Resignation to the Divine Will 1684</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Cave</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Primitive Christianity in three Parts 1682</item>
               <item>171 —his Discertation concerning the Government of antient Churches 1683</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Cosin</hi>'s History of Popish Transubstantiation 1679</item>
               <item>173 Countries sense of <hi>Londons</hi> sufferings, by the Fire 1667</item>
               <item>174 Catholick medicines, for the Disease of Charity 1656</item>
               <item>175 Catholick Pill to purge Popery 1677</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Chibald</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Tryal of Faith 1522</item>
               <item>177 <hi>Clavis</hi>'s Apocaliptica, or the Revelation Kevealed, <hi>Hartlib</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Caryl</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Of the Nature and principles of Love 1673</item>
               <item>179 Considerations touching the style of the Holy Scriptures 1675</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Care</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> 39 Articles of the Church of <hi>England</hi> Compared 1682</item>
               <item>181 Church History of Bishops by <hi>Rich. Baxter,</hi> answered by Mr. <hi>Morice</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>182 Conference about Religion, between <hi>Edw. Stillingfleet, G. Burnet</hi> and Romanists 1616</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s <hi>(Charles)</hi> Moral Phylosophy of the <hi>Stoicks</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>184 <hi>Comenius</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Pattern of Universal Knowledge 1671</item>
               <item>185 —his natural Philosopy Reformed 1651</item>
               <item>186 <hi>Chetwind</hi>'s Centuries of Memorable passages and occurrences 1674</item>
               <item>187 Character of a weaned Christian 1675</item>
               <item>188 Conquest of <hi>China,</hi> by the <hi>Tarters,</hi> with an Account of their Religions 1671</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Chappel</hi>'s (Bp. <hi>Will.</hi>) Use of the Holy Scriptures discoursed 1653</item>
               <item>190 <hi>Case</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Imitation of Saints opened in practical Meditations 1666</item>
               <item>191 Continuation of the Memoirs of Mr. <hi>Bernier</hi> concerning the Great Mogol 1672</item>
               <item>192 Considerations concerning Free-Schools, as setled in <hi>England Oxon.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>193 Collection of select Discourses out of the eminent Witts of <hi>France</hi> and <hi>Italy Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>194 —Of diverse Miracles wrought by Popish Saints 1673</item>
               <item>195 —Of the Names of the Merchants in and about <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>196 <hi>Cassianus</hi> of <hi>Paris,</hi> his motives of his Conversion 1677</item>
               <item>197 Copy of Journal-Book of the House of Commons, for the Sessions of Parl. 1678 1680</item>
               <item>198 <hi>Clerk</hi>'s Guide in three Parts, to which is added a fourth part 1672</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Collins</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Country Gaugers <hi>Vade mecum</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Culpeper</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.) London</hi> Dispesatory, with additions 1683</item>
               <item>201 —his Astrologic<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>l Judgment of Diseases 1671</item>
               <item>202 —his English Physitian enlarged 1684</item>
               <item>203 —his Translation of <hi>Galens</hi> Art of Physick 1671</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Charras (Moys.)</hi> Letter concerning Object. made to his Observations of <hi>Vipers</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Cocker</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.) Englands</hi> perfect Schoolmaster for Spelling, Writing and Arithm. 1670</item>
               <item>206 Chirurgical and Anatomical Works, by <hi>Paul Barbett</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>207 <hi>Croft</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Terestial Paradice</item>
               <item>208 <hi>Calamy</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Godly-mans Ark, in divers Sermons 1658</item>
               <pb n="23" facs="tcp:42445:14"/>
               <item>209 Church Militant Historically continued till 1640. by <hi>Will. Vaughan Lond.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>210 Catalogue of Popish Errors in their Doctrine, or Anatomy of Popery 1673</item>
               <item>211 <hi>J. Collins</hi>'s Two Treatises on the Death of two Noble Ladies 1669</item>
               <item>212 Considerations how far Romanists may be trusted by Protestant Princes 1675</item>
               <item>213 Curious Distillatory, or the Art of Distilling 1677</item>
               <item>214 Conversion exemplified in the instance of a Gracious Gentlewoman 1669</item>
               <item>215 Compendium of the Fathers and School-men, by <hi>Dan. Tossanus</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise of the Covenant of Grace 1671</item>
               <item>217 Christ Exalted, and Wisdom Justified, by <hi>Rich. Eder</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Cuthrie</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Christians great Interest 1673</item>
               <item>219 Catholick Religion maintained in the Church of <hi>England Oxon.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>220 Cause and Remedy of the Distempers of the Times <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Camfield</hi>'s Comprehensive Rule of Righteousness 1671</item>
               <item>222 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s Covenant of Grace 1671</item>
               <item>223 —Gospel Conversation 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>6</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Cornelus Nepos</hi>'s Lives <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>225 Conference between a rich Alderman and a poor Country Vicar <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>226 Causes and Remedies of the Distempers of the Times 1675</item>
               <item>227 <hi>Crafts</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Lover, or Nuptial Love 1638</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Comber</hi>'s Companion to the Altar 1681</item>
               <item>229 —To the Temple. part 1st. 1679</item>
               <item>230 Dr. <hi>Charleton</hi> of the Wits of Men and Mistery of Vintners 1675</item>
               <item>231 Complaisant Companion, or new Jests, witty Reperties 1674</item>
               <item>232 <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#murp" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>loria</hi> &amp; <hi>Narcissus,</hi> a Romance, 3d and 4th parts 1658</item>
               <item>233 <hi>Crayge</hi>'s Arrainment of Anabaptism 1656</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Colvil</hi>'s Righteous Branch, on <hi>Isaiah</hi> II. 1673</item>
               <item>535 Choice Banquet of witty Jests 1671</item>
               <item>236 Christian Education of Children 1675</item>
               <item>237 Character of a weakned Christian 1675</item>
               <item>238 Catholick Medicines for the Diseases of Charity 1656</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Crofts</hi> of Nuptial Love</item>
               <item>240 <hi>Clark</hi>'s Looking-Glass for Persecutors 1675</item>
               <item>241 —Narrative of the <hi>Spanish</hi> Invasion and Gunpowder-Plot</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Capello</hi> and <hi>Bianco,</hi> a Novel, relating the Battle of <hi>Lepanta</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Chamberlain</hi>'s <hi>(Will.) Pharonnida,</hi> an Heroick Poem 1659</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Carew</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Poems, Songs and Sonnets, together with a Masque 1670</item>
               <item>245 <hi>Cleveland</hi>'s Poems, Orations, and Epistles 1659</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Cartwright</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Comedies, Tragi-Comedies, with other Poems 1659</item>
               <item>247 <hi>Cicero</hi> against <hi>Cataline,</hi> in Four Invective Orations, by <hi>Chr. Wase</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Cotton</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Rob.</hi>) Answer to the Reasons for Foreign Wars 1675</item>
               <item>249 Compleat Bone-Setter enlarged, with a Treatise of the Pestilence 1665</item>
               <item>250 Conversations, written in <hi>French</hi> by Monsieur <hi>Clerombault</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>251 Compleat Physician, qualified and degnified by <hi>Ev. Mainwaring</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>252 Collection of Poems on several occasions, by several Persons 1672</item>
               <item>253 Character of true Nobility and Gentility 1676</item>
               <item>254 <hi>Cook</hi>'s <hi>(James)</hi> Supplement to the Marrow of Chyrurgery 1655</item>
               <item>255 Collection of Miracles wrought by the Popish Saints 1675</item>
               <item>256 Comparison of <hi>Plato</hi> and <hi>Aristotle,</hi> with Opinions about them 1673</item>
               <item>257 — Between the Eloquence of <hi>Demosthenes</hi> and <hi>Cicero Oxon.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>258 <hi>Cambachius (Lud.)</hi> True Salt and Secret of the Philosophers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1657</item>
               <pb n="24" facs="tcp:42445:15"/>
               <item>259 Conquest of <hi>China</hi> by the <hi>Tartars Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>260 <hi>Cudmore</hi>'s <hi>(Dan.)</hi> Sacred Poems on the History of our Saviour 1657</item>
               <item>261 <hi>Clark</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Natural History of <hi>Nitre</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>262 <hi>Clidamus,</hi> or the <hi>Sicilian</hi> Tale 1639</item>
               <item>263 Charity Commended, or a Catholick Christian Instructed 1667</item>
               <item>264 <hi>Case</hi>'s Imitation of the Saints 1666</item>
               <item>265 Dissertation concerning Ancient Church Government, by Dr. <hi>Cave</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>266 Domestick Devotions for the use of Families 1643</item>
               <item>267 Defence and Continuation of the Discourse of the Knowledge of Christ 1675</item>
               <item>268 Devotions for the use of Families and particular Persons 1683</item>
               <item>269 Discourse of the period of Human Life, with the Defence 1677</item>
               <item>270 — Discourse of the period of Humane Life alone 1677</item>
               <item>271 <hi>David</hi>'s Troubles remembred 1631</item>
               <item>272 Discourse of the excellency of Heavenly Substance 1673</item>
               <item>273 Discourse of Receiving the Lord's-Supper <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>274 Degenerate Plant, a Treatise of ancient Ceremonies <hi>Lond.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>275 <hi>Deering</hi>'s Sermons and Lectures on the <hi>Hebrews</hi>
               </item>
               <item>276 Directions for plain Christians to Pray 1674</item>
               <item>277 Declaration how near we may come to the present Church of <hi>Rome Cambr.</hi> 1598</item>
               <item>278 Declaration of Ecclesiastical Discipline <hi>Genev.</hi> 1580</item>
               <item>279 Discourse of the Knowledge of Jesus Christ, by <hi>Will. Sherlock Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>270 <hi>Doughtey</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Short Polemical Discussions 1652</item>
               <item>281 Divine Cordial, by <hi>Thomas Watson</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>282 Directions and Perswasions to a sound Conversion, by <hi>R. Baxter</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>283 Debt-Book, also the Civil debt of Love, by <hi>Henry Wilkinson</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>284 Discourse of the last Judgment, by <hi>Sam. Whiting Cambr.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>285 Discourse of Divels, <hi>Daemons</hi> &amp; Spirits <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>286 <hi>Danver</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Treatise of Baptism 1674</item>
               <item>287 Discourse of Gods Judgments, by <hi>Simon Ford</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>288 Discourse upon the First Decade of <hi>Livie,</hi> by <hi>N. Macchiavel,</hi> together with his Prince 1663</item>
               <item>289 Description of the present State of <hi>Samos, Nicaria, Patmos,</hi> &amp;c. 1678</item>
               <item>290 Description of the Islands and Inhabitants of <hi>Faeroe</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>291 <hi>Des<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ecolai</hi>'s Memoires, with the motives of his Conversion 1677</item>
               <item>292 Diatribes, or Discourses of Travel, Mony, and Measuring, by <hi>Edw. Leigh</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>293 Description of the Body of Man, with description of Instruments, by <hi>Alex. Read.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>294 Discourse and Defence of Arms and Armory, by <hi>Edw. Waterhouse</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>295 <hi>Dugdale</hi> (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) of the Office of a Lord Chancellor 1677</item>
               <item>296 <hi>Digby</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Ken.</hi>) Observations on <hi>Browns Religio Medici</hi> 1643</item>
               <item>297 — his Receipts in Physick and Chyrurgery 1675</item>
               <item>298 — his Treatise of the Vegetation of Plants 1661</item>
               <item>299 <hi>D'avenant</hi> (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Two Plays, <hi>viz.</hi> the Wits and the Platonick Lovers 1665</item>
               <item>300 Decimal Fractions, or the Scale of Interest, by <hi>Jo. Newton</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>301 — Another of the same, with their use of Measuring 1668</item>
               <item>302 Danger of Enthusiasm discovered, in an Epistle to the Quakers 1674</item>
               <item>303 <hi>Dod</hi> and <hi>Cleavers</hi> Ten Sermons on the Sacrament 1661</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Doolittle</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> young Mans Instructer, and old Mans Remembrancer 1673</item>
               <item>305 <hi>D'Espagne</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Essay of the wonders of God 1662</item>
               <item>306 <hi>Drake</hi>'s <hi>(Rog.)</hi> Boundary to the Holy Mount 1653</item>
               <item>307 Discourse of Local Motion 1670</item>
               <item>308 —Of Brutes, against <hi>Des Cartes</hi> 1670</item>
               <pb n="25" facs="tcp:42445:15"/>
               <item>309 <hi>Dary</hi>'s <hi>(Mich.)</hi> Compleat <hi>Gauger,</hi> in two parrts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>310 <hi>Dugdale</hi>'s Catalogue of the present Nobility 1685</item>
               <item>311 <hi>Dodwell</hi>'s Two Letters of Advise to the Clergy 1680</item>
               <item>312 Divine Goodness Vindicated and Cleared 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>8</item>
               <item>313 Drunkards Character, or a true Drunkard set forth in his Colours</item>
               <item>314 <hi>D'avanant</hi>'s Wits, a Comedie 1685</item>
               <item>315 Danger of Enthusiasm Discovered 1674</item>
               <item>316 <hi>Dale</hi>'s Analysi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> of the Epistles <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>317 <hi>Davis</hi>'s Grammar <hi>Hebrew</hi> and <hi>English</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>318 <hi>D'espain</hi>'s Essays of the Wonders of God 1662</item>
               <item>319 — Popular Errors 1607</item>
               <item>320 Doctrine of Devils, about Demons and Spirits 1676</item>
               <item>321 <hi>Dike</hi>'s Righteous Mans Tower 1643</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Durant</hi>'s Love of Christ to Believers 1655</item>
               <item>323 <hi>Dutch</hi> Dispensatory, confirmed by the Physitians of <hi>Amsterdam</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>324 <hi>Digg</hi>'s <hi>(Dud.)</hi> of the unlawfulness of Subjects taking up Arms against the King 1662</item>
               <item>325 Drudg, or Jealous Extravagant 1673</item>
               <item>326 <hi>Dent</hi> on the <hi>Revelation</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>327 <hi>D'Avanant</hi>'s Gondibert, an Heroick Poem <hi>Lond.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>328 Domestick Devotions for Families 1683</item>
               <item>329 Dialogues about Sea-Services 1685</item>
               <item>330 Duty of Man, laid down in a Scriptural Catechism 1682</item>
               <item>331 Enter into thy Closet, or a Method for private Devotion 1676</item>
               <item>332 Explication of the Visions of the <hi>Revelations</hi>
               </item>
               <item>333 <hi>Elborough</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Exposition upon the latter part of the Common-Prayer Book 1672</item>
               <item>334 <hi>Eedes (Rich.)</hi> Christ Exalted and Wisdom Justified 1659</item>
               <item>335 — his great Salvation by Christ Jesus 1659</item>
               <item>336 Endeavour to Rectifie some prevailing Opinions 1671</item>
               <item>337 <hi>Eyre</hi>'s Exact Surveyor 1654</item>
               <item>338 Experienced Angler 1668</item>
               <item>339 <hi>Edlyn</hi>'s Observ. Astrol. on the Conjunction of <hi>Saturn</hi> and <hi>Mars</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>340 <hi>Aesop</hi>'s Fables, with <hi>Jo. Ogilby</hi>'s Notes and Sculptures, 2 parts, 1 volume 1675</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Electra</hi> of <hi>Sophocles,</hi> with a Poem of the Kings Restauration 1659</item>
               <item>342 Essay concerning the Immortality of the Soul, <hi>&amp;c. Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>343 Education of young Ladies and Gentlewomen <hi>Lond.</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>344 Excellency of the Heavenly Substance 1673</item>
               <item>345 Essays and Observations Theological and Moral 1654</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Evan</hi>'s <hi>(Arise)</hi> Eccho to the Voice from Heaven 1652</item>
               <item>347 <hi>England</hi>'s Imminent danger, and only Remedy 1671</item>
               <item>348 Essay about the Origine and Vertues of Gems 1672</item>
               <item>349 Essays on the First Book of <hi>Lucretius,</hi> by <hi>J. Evelyn</hi> 1636</item>
               <item>350 <hi>J. Evelyn</hi> of Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progress 1674</item>
               <item>351 — his Translation of <hi>Renatus, Rapinus</hi> of Gardens, 4 Books 1673</item>
               <item>352 <hi>England</hi>'s Imminent Danger and only Remedy considered 1671</item>
               <item>353 <hi>Elsholt</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Curious Distillatory, or the Art of Distilling Coloured Liquors, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>7</item>
               <item>354 Epigrams on several occasions, by <hi>Rich. Flecknoe</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>355 <hi>English</hi> Rogue, 2d part 1660</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Ephesian</hi> and <hi>Cimmerian</hi> Matrons, two notable Examples 1668</item>
               <item>357 Exposition upon Sir <hi>Geo. Ripley</hi>'s <hi>Hermetico</hi> Poetical Works 1678</item>
               <item>358 <hi>England</hi>'s Warning-piece, or the History of Gun-powder Treason 1659</item>
               <pb n="26" facs="tcp:42445:16"/>
               <item>359 Essays of Effluviums, with Experiments to make Flame and Air ponderable <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>360 Exact Survey of the United Provinces of the <hi>Netherlands</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>361 Dr. <hi>Everard</hi>'s Discovery of the wonderful Vertues of Tobacco 1659</item>
               <item>362 Experienced Angler, or Angling Improved 1662</item>
               <item>363 <hi>English</hi> Phlebotomy, or method of Letting Blood 1569</item>
               <item>364 — Travellers Companion 1679</item>
               <item>365 <hi>Evelya</hi>'s Instructions for Erecting a Library 1661</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Elborow</hi>'s Reasonableness of our Christian Service 1677</item>
               <item>367 <hi>E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>monson</hi>'s Natural Language of Languages 1658</item>
               <item>368 <hi>Enchiridion</hi> of Faith 1655</item>
               <item>369 Epitomie of Secrets of Physick and Chyrurgery 1651</item>
               <item>370 Elements of <hi>Euclid</hi> Explain'd, by Dr. <hi>Chales Oxon.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>371 <hi>Featley</hi>'s <hi>(Dan.)</hi> Hand-maid to private Devotion <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>372 Farewell Sermons of the <hi>London</hi> Ministers, 2d Collection 1663</item>
               <item>373 Another of the same, being the whole monthly Lectures 1663</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Fowler (Edw.)</hi> Discourse of Christian Liberty 1680</item>
               <item>375 Fresh Suit against Independency 1677</item>
               <item>376 <hi>Fletcher</hi>'s <hi>(Phin.)</hi> Fathers Testament to his Children, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>377 Fathers Legacy, or Counsels to his Children 1678</item>
               <item>378 — Another containing the Whole Duty of Man 1678</item>
               <item>379 Fort-Royal of the Holy Scriptures, or a new Concordance 1665</item>
               <item>380 <hi>Flavel</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Touchstone of Sincerity, or the Signs of Grace 1679</item>
               <item>381 — his Saint Indeed, or a good work of a Christian 1673</item>
               <item>382 — Navigation Spiritualized 1677</item>
               <item>383 <hi>Fern</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Discourse of the Case between the <hi>English</hi> and <hi>Romish</hi> Church 1655</item>
               <item>384 Faithfulness of God considered and cleared 1674</item>
               <item>385 First Principles of the Oracles of God. with several Hymns 1677</item>
               <item>386 Faithfulness of God considered and cleared 1674</item>
               <item>387 Friendly Conference between a Minister and his Parishioner 1676</item>
               <item>388 <hi>Falkner</hi>'s <hi>Libertus Ecclesiastica</hi>
               </item>
               <item>389 — Christian Loyalty</item>
               <item>390 Fortunate Fool, or Life of Dr. <hi>Cenudo</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>391 Folly in Print, a Book of Rimes 1665</item>
               <item>392 <hi>Ferrand</hi>'s Love-Melancholy <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>393 Friendly Conferance against Quakerism <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>394 Frequent Progress of Pains, Inflamatian and Tumours, by <hi>Edw. Mainwaring</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Fern</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Considerations touching the Reformed Church of <hi>England</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>396 <hi>Flecknoe</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Epigrams on several occasions 1670</item>
               <item>397 <hi>Fletcher</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Differences, Causes, and Judgments of Urine 1641</item>
               <item>398 <hi>Fournelli</hi>'s (Mr. <hi>Der.</hi>) Discourss of the <hi>Cartesian</hi> Philosophy 1670</item>
               <item>399 — Another with the Opinion concerning Brutes 1670</item>
               <item>400 <hi>V: Fairfax</hi>'s Treatise of the Bulk and Selvedge of the World 1674</item>
               <item>401 <hi>F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>jus</hi>'s <hi>(Roland)</hi> Relation of his Voyage into <hi>Mauritania</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>402 <hi>French</hi> Grammar and Syntax, by <hi>Charles Maupas</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>403 Famous <hi>Chinois,</hi> or the Love of several <hi>French</hi> Nobility 1669</item>
               <item>404 <hi>Fuller</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.) Andronicus,</hi> or the Unfortunate Politician 1686</item>
               <item>405 <hi>French</hi> Gardiner for all sorts of Fruit-Trees, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>406 — Another with the <hi>English</hi> Vineyard vindicated 1675</item>
               <item>407 <hi>French</hi> Grammar, published by the Academy at <hi>Paris</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>408 <hi>Fuller</hi>'s <hi>(Ignat.)</hi> Sermons 1672</item>
               <pb n="27" facs="tcp:42445:16"/>
               <item>409 <hi>Glossographia,</hi> or a Dictionary of hard Words, by <hi>Tho. Blount Lond.</hi> 1687</item>
               <item>410 Genuine Explication of the Visions of the <hi>Revelations</hi>
               </item>
               <item>411 <hi>Grynaeus</hi> (Dr. <hi>Jam.</hi>) his Commentary on <hi>Haggeus</hi> the Prophet 1586</item>
               <item>412 Grand Case of the present Ministry, with Cases of Conscience 1662</item>
               <item>413 <hi>Guild</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Only way to Salvation 1608</item>
               <item>414 <hi>Gifford</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Fifteen Sermons upon the Song of <hi>Solomon</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>415 <hi>Goodwin</hi>'s <hi>(Phil.)</hi> Evangelical Communicant in the Eucharist 1649</item>
               <item>416 <hi>Gregory</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Historical Anatomy of Christian Melancholy 1646</item>
               <item>417 Genuine Explication of the Visions of the <hi>Revelations</hi>
               </item>
               <item>418 Guide to Glory, or a Path to Providence, in a Discourse of Mans Felicity 1658</item>
               <item>419 Growth and Original of the <hi>Spanish</hi> Monarchy, by <hi>Tho. Philipot</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>420 Great Work of Redemption, delivered in Five Sermons 1660</item>
               <item>421 <hi>Giffard</hi>'s <hi>(James) French</hi> School-Master 1636</item>
               <item>422 Garden of <hi>Eden,</hi> 2 parts compleat, by Sir <hi>Hugh Plat<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> 1660</item>
               <item>423 Guide to Glory, in a Discourse of Mans Felicity 1658</item>
               <item>424 <hi>Gea<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ing</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Treatise of Prayer with the Efficients thereof 1662</item>
               <item>425 <hi>Greenhill</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Treatise of the Soundness of the Heart 1672</item>
               <item>426 <hi>Gouge</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Word to Sinners, and a Word to Saints 1673</item>
               <item>427 <hi>Glanvill</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.) Phil<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>sophia Pia,</hi> with a defence of Reason in Religion 1671</item>
               <item>428 <hi>Gearing</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Mount of Holy Meditation 1662</item>
               <item>439 <hi>Glanvill</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Philosophical Considerations abour Witchcraft 1668</item>
               <item>430 <hi>Grelot</hi>'s <hi>(Will. Joseph.)</hi> late Vayage to <hi>Constantinople</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>431 <hi>Griffith</hi>'s <hi>(Matth.)</hi> Fear God and the King, in a Sermon 1660</item>
               <item>432 <hi>Gage</hi>'s History of the <hi>West-Indies</hi>
               </item>
               <item>433 <hi>Goff</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Three excellent Tragedies, <hi>viz.</hi> the Raging <hi>Turk,</hi> &amp;c. 1656</item>
               <item>434 <hi>Glanius</hi>'s (Mr.) Relation of an unfortunate Voyage to <hi>Bengala</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>435 Gallantry <hi>a-la-mode,</hi> a Satyrical Poem, in 3 parts 1674</item>
               <item>436 Gentlewomans Companion, or a Guide to the Female Sex 1673</item>
               <item>437 <hi>Groeneveldt</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise of the Stone and Gravel 1677</item>
               <item>438 <hi>Gibson</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Anatomy of Humane Bodies Epitomized 1684</item>
               <item>449 Gentleman's Jockey and approved Farrier 1683</item>
               <item>440 Of Gardens, four Books, by <hi>Renatus Rapinus</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>441 Gentlemans's Companion, or a Character of True Nobility 1676</item>
               <item>442 Golden Chain, or a Miscellany of Divine Sentences 1657</item>
               <item>443 Gentile Sinner, or <hi>England</hi>'s brave Gentleman <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>444 <hi>Grew</hi>'s <hi>(Nehem.)</hi> Anatomy of Vegetables <hi>Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>445 — his Anatomy of Trunks, in two parts 1675</item>
               <item>446 <hi>Gibson</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Mathematical Syntax 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>5</item>
               <item>447 Grand Case of the present Ministry considered 1663</item>
               <item>448 Golden Mean, or Considerations on the Sacrament, by <hi>Steph. Geree</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>449 — Another of the same 1656</item>
               <item>450 Gentlemans Jockey and Approved Farrier 1676</item>
               <item>451 <hi>Gafferel</hi>'s unheard-of Curiosities 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>0</item>
               <item>452 <hi>Guthrie</hi>'s Christians Great Interest 1673</item>
               <item>453 <hi>Goodwin (Ph.)</hi> On the Lord's-Day 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4</item>
               <item>454 <hi>Grotius</hi> of the Truth of Christian Religion, by Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>3</item>
               <item>455 <hi>Gee</hi>'s Divine Right and Original of the Civil Magistrate 1658</item>
               <item>456 <hi>Gurnal</hi>'s Christians Labour and Reward 1672</item>
               <item>457 <hi>Greenhill</hi>'s Soundness of Heart 1671</item>
               <item>458 <hi>Gouge</hi>'s Word to Saints and Sinners 1673</item>
               <pb n="28" facs="tcp:42445:17"/>
               <item>459 <hi>Gregory</hi>'s Anatomy of Christian Melancholy <hi>Lond.</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>460 <hi>Gadbury</hi>'s Astrological Treasury 1684</item>
               <item>461 Hand-maid to private Devotion, by <hi>Daniel Featly</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>462 Harmony of Natural and Positive Divine Laws 1682</item>
               <item>463 Husbandman's Companion, by <hi>Edmund Bury</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>464 <hi>Hoard</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Souls Misery and Recovery 1636</item>
               <item>465 <hi>Harwood</hi>'s <hi>(Jam.)</hi> Plea for the C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>mmon-Prayer Book 1654</item>
               <item>466 <hi>How</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Treatise of delighting in God, in two parts 1674</item>
               <item>467 — of the Blessedness of the Righteous 1668</item>
               <item>468 <hi>Hall</hi>'s Bp. <hi>Jos.</hi>) Remedy of Prophaness, and his Epistles, 2 volumes 1637</item>
               <item>469 — his Christian Moderation 1640</item>
               <item>470 <hi>Hammond</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Practical Catechism, with his reasonableness of Christian Relig. 1683</item>
               <item>471 Heavenly mindedness, and Earthly mindedness, with an Append x 1672</item>
               <item>472 <hi>Horneck</hi>'s <hi>(Ant.)</hi> Discourse of the great Law of Consideration 1684</item>
               <item>473 <hi>Hardcastle</hi>'s <hi>(Thom.)</hi> Christian <hi>Geography</hi> and <hi>Arithmetick</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>474 <hi>Hodges</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Scripture Catechism for the confuting of Errors <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>475 <hi>Hogwill</hi>'s <hi>(Franc.)</hi> Glory of the True Church <hi>Lond.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>476 <hi>Hutcheson</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Exposition of the Prophesies of <hi>Obadiah,</hi> &amp;c. 1654</item>
               <item>477 <hi>Hartlibb</hi>'s Key of the Mysteries in the <hi>Revelations,</hi> and in <hi>Daniel</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>478 <hi>Hull (Will.)</hi> his Sinners entertainment of Harbourless Christ 1672</item>
               <item>479 <hi>Hall</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Treatise of the Loathsomness of long Hair 1654</item>
               <item>480 <hi>How</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Works of Salvation 1637</item>
               <item>481 Highest End and Chiefest Work of a Christian 1673</item>
               <item>482 Hymns and Songs of the Church, divided in two parts 1623</item>
               <item>483 <hi>Hermanus</hi> Archbishop of <hi>Colen</hi> his Consultation about Religion 1640</item>
               <item>484 <hi>Hughe</hi>'s <hi>(Geor.)</hi> Aphorisms, or Select Propositions of the Scripture 1670</item>
               <item>485 Heaven taken by Storm or Holy Violence, by <hi>Tho. Watson</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>486 <hi>Hyde's (Edw.)</hi> Christian Legacy, consisting in two parts 1675</item>
               <item>487 <hi>Haiward</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Strong Helper 1637</item>
               <item>488 <hi>Hanson</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Sabbatarian confuted by the new Covenant 1658</item>
               <item>489 <hi>Hooks</hi>'s <hi>(Ri.)</hi> Non-Conformists Champion and Challenge accepted 1682</item>
               <item>490 — his Answer to Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Petition for Peace 1682</item>
               <item>491 <hi>Humes</hi>'s <hi>(Anna)</hi> Triumphs of Love, Chastity and Death <hi>Edinburch.</hi> 1644</item>
               <item>492 <hi>Hanes</hi>'s <hi>(D.)</hi> Church-cases cleared <hi>Lond.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>493 <hi>Hacon</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Review of a late Heterodox Catechism 1668</item>
               <item>494 <hi>Hesketh</hi> on the Sacrament</item>
               <item>495 <hi>Hicks</hi>'s <hi>Jerian</hi> in Answer to <hi>Julian</hi>
               </item>
               <item>496 <hi>Hotchkie</hi>'s Imputation of Christs Righteousness to us 1675</item>
               <item>497 <hi>Hoard</hi>'s Souls Misery and Recovery 1658</item>
               <item>498 <hi>Hildersham</hi>'s Song of <hi>Solomon</hi> Paraphrased 1672</item>
               <item>499 <hi>Hallywell</hi> against the Quakers 1673</item>
               <item>500 Heroick Education 1657</item>
               <item>501 <hi>Hickman</hi>'s Justification of Fathers and Schoolmen 1659</item>
               <item>502 <hi>Hugh</hi>'s Compleat Vineyard 1670</item>
               <item>503 <hi>Henderson</hi> of the Promises 1667</item>
               <item>504 H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>story of <hi>Gesta Romanorum</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>505 — of <hi>Justin</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>506 <hi>Hobbs</hi>'s Art of <hi>Rhetorick,</hi> with a Discourse of the Laws of <hi>England</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>507 <hi>Hudibras,</hi> 3 parts, 1 volume 1684</item>
               <item>508 <hi>Hierocles</hi> upon the Golden Verses of the <hi>Pythagoreans</hi> 1682</item>
               <pb n="29" facs="tcp:42445:17"/>
               <item>509 <hi>Hanmar</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> View of Antiquity, in account of some Fathers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>510 <hi>Hoptan</hi>'s <hi>(Arth.)</hi> Concordancy of Words</item>
               <item>511 Ld <hi>Hales</hi>'s Observations touching the Torricellian experiment 1674</item>
               <item>512 — of Natural motions 1777</item>
               <item>513 — his Pleas of the Crown 1682</item>
               <item>514 — his Contemplations Moral and Divine 1682</item>
               <item>515 — his several Tracts of providing for the Poor, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>516 — Essay touching the Gravitation of fluid Bod es 1675</item>
               <item>517 — his Life, by Dr. <hi>Burnet</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>518 <hi>Howel</hi>'s <hi>(James)</hi> Twelve several Treatises of the late Revolutions 1661</item>
               <item>519 — his Discourse of the Empire 1658</item>
               <item>520 — <hi>Dodonas</hi> Grove, or Vocal Forrest, part 2d. 1653</item>
               <item>521 History of <hi>Tamerlain</hi> the Great 1679</item>
               <item>522 — of the Rebellion in <hi>Naples,</hi> fi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>st part 1650</item>
               <item>523 — of the Council of <hi>Trent</hi> in Eight Books, by <hi>Pet. Jurieu</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>524 — History of the House of <hi>Este</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>525 — History of the Revolutions of the Empire of the Great <hi>Mogul,</hi> 1st. vol. 1676</item>
               <item>526 — of a late Pilgrimage to the <hi>Holy Land</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>527 — of Fevers, with the uses of the Spleen 1674</item>
               <item>528 — of the Conquest of <hi>China</hi> by the <hi>Tartars</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>529 — History of the Tragick Loves of <hi>Hippolito</hi> and <hi>Isabella</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>530 — Historical Relation of the <hi>Hungarian</hi> Rebellion 1672</item>
               <item>531 <hi>Hemmingius (Nic.)</hi> Exposition of the 25th <hi>Psalm</hi> 1580</item>
               <item>532 History of the Preparation and Improvement of Vegetables <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>533 <hi>Hughs</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> his Troubled Mans Medicine <hi>Lond.</hi> 1567</item>
               <item>534 <hi>Horace</hi>'s <hi>Lyricks</hi> and his Book of <hi>Epodes</hi> englished 1653</item>
               <item>535 <hi>Holyday</hi>'s <hi>(Barken)</hi> Survey of the World, in Ten Books <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>536 <hi>Home</hi>'s <hi>(Nath.)</hi> Essay concerning the Sabbath <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>537 <hi>Hannay</hi>'s <hi>(Patrick)</hi> Nightingale, Sheretine and Mariana 1622</item>
               <item>538 Lord <hi>Herbert</hi>'s occasional Verses 1665</item>
               <item>539 <hi>Hood</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Use of both the Globes, Celestial and Terrestial 1592</item>
               <item>540 <hi>Harris (Walth.)</hi> Rational Discourse of Remedies both Chymical and Gulenical 1683</item>
               <item>541 <hi>Harvey</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Anatomical Exercises of the Heart and Blood 1673</item>
               <item>542 Harmony of the Muses, containing excellent Poems 1654</item>
               <item>543 <hi>Herbert</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Life by <hi>Is. Watton,</hi> with the Life of St. <hi>Agnes</hi> 1670 &amp; 1677</item>
               <item>544 <hi>Hunt</hi>'s <hi>(Nich.)</hi> Hand-Maid to <hi>Arithmetick</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>545 <hi>Harvey</hi>'s <hi>(Gid.)</hi> New discovery of the Scurvy 1675</item>
               <item>546 <hi>Horace</hi> in <hi>English,</hi> by <hi>Broome</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>547 <hi>Hilton</hi>'s Catch that Catch can, a Song-Book set to Musick 1658</item>
               <item>548 Image of both Churches, <hi>Jerusalem</hi> and <hi>Babel Tornay</hi> 1623</item>
               <item>549 <hi>Junius</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Drunkards Character <hi>Lond.</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>550 K. <hi>James</hi> his Translation of the <hi>Psalms,</hi> Prose and Verse 1637</item>
               <item>551 — Another of the same 1637</item>
               <item>552 Image of both Churches, compiled by <hi>Jo. Bale</hi>
               </item>
               <item>553 Infant-Baptism plainly proved, in a Discourse by <hi>Jos. Whiston</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>554 <hi>Joselyn</hi>'s <hi>(John) New-England</hi> Rarities discovered 1672</item>
               <item>555 Journal of the late Siege of <hi>Vienna</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>556 <hi>Juvenal</hi>'s Satyrs, with Arguments and Notes, by Sir <hi>Rob. Stapleton</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>557 — Another of the same 1673</item>
               <item>558 <hi>Jenison</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Cities safety, a fruitful Treatise 1630</item>
               <pb n="30" facs="tcp:42445:18"/>
               <item>559 <hi>Indagine</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Introduction to Chiromancy, Palmistry, <hi>&amp;c. Lond.</hi> 1578</item>
               <item>560 Infernal Sin of Murther punished, or Hell opened 1676</item>
               <item>561 <hi>Jurien</hi>'s <hi>(Pet.)</hi> History of the Council of <hi>Trent,</hi> Eight Books 1687</item>
               <item>562 <hi>Josephus</hi>'s <hi>Ben Gorion</hi> History of the latter Times of the <hi>Jews</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>563 Image of the Age represented in Four Characters, by <hi>N Williams Oxon.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>564 Journal-Book for the House of Commons for the Sessions of Parliament <hi>Lond.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>565 Justice of Peace his Calling, a Moral Essay 1684</item>
               <item>566 <hi>Jus Regium,</hi> or the Foundation of Monarchy maintained, by Sir <hi>G. Mockenzie</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>567 Introduction into the Learning of the <hi>Latin</hi> Tongue 1683</item>
               <item>568 Instructions concerning the A t of Oratory <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>569 Interest of <hi>Ireland</hi> in its Trade and Wealth stated; in two parts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>570 <hi>Johnson</hi>'s <hi>(W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ll.)</hi> Narrative of a great Deliverance at Sea 1672</item>
               <item>571 <hi>Indiculus Ʋniversalis,</hi> or the Universe in Epitome, <hi>Engl. Lat. French</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>572 J<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>st Apology for the Peoples Judgment 1667</item>
               <item>573 <hi>Johnson</hi>'s Manual of Physick 1684</item>
               <item>574 <hi>Josephus</hi> Wars of the <hi>Jews</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>575 <hi>Kidder</hi>'s Demonstration of the Messias 1684</item>
               <item>576 <hi>Kingstone (R.)</hi> of the Cause and Cure of Offences 1682</item>
               <item>577 <hi>Knox (John)</hi> of Predestination, in Answer to the <hi>Anabaptists</hi> 1591</item>
               <item>578 Light in the way to Paradice, with other Occasionals 1682</item>
               <item>579 <hi>Long</hi> against <hi>Johnson</hi>'s <hi>Julian,</hi> in Defence of Dr. <hi>Hicks</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>580 — his Dissenters Plot discovered and defeated 1671</item>
               <item>581 <hi>Love</hi>'s <hi>(Chr.)</hi> Heavens Glory, Hell's Terror 1671</item>
               <item>582 <hi>Lloyd</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Paraphrase on the <hi>Canticles,</hi> in a Pindarique Poem 1682</item>
               <item>583 <hi>Larkin</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Looking-Glass of the Fathers, Philosophers, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>584 <hi>Lockier</hi>'s Memorial of Gods Judgments, or Sermons 1671</item>
               <item>585 — his useful Instructions for the People of God 1671</item>
               <item>586 <hi>London</hi>'s Resurrection, or the Re-building of <hi>London,</hi> by <hi>Sam. Rolls</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>587 <hi>Latham</hi>'s <hi>(Paul)</hi> Christian Religion asserted against <hi>Pelagians</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>588 <hi>Laud</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Seven Sermons on several Occasions 1651</item>
               <item>589 <hi>Linch</hi>'s <hi>(Sim.)</hi> Three Sermons of Rebellion painted to the Life 1662</item>
               <item>590 <hi>Lukins</hi>'s <hi>(N.)</hi> Introduct<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>on to the Holy Scripture 1669</item>
               <item>591 <hi>Lokyer</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Balm for bleeding <hi>England</hi> and <hi>Ireland</hi> 1643</item>
               <item>592 — his Memorials of Gods Judgments, in several Sermons 1671</item>
               <item>593 <hi>Larkham</hi>'s <hi>(Thom.)</hi> Wedd<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ng-Supper, in 12 Sermons 1652</item>
               <item>594 <hi>Ley</hi>'s <hi>(Jo)</hi> Life and Death of Mrs. <hi>Jane Ratcliff</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>595 <hi>Lowth</hi>'s <hi>(Simon)</hi> Cathechetical Questions 1674</item>
               <item>596 <hi>Lavater (Lewis)</hi> Book of <hi>Ruth</hi> expounded 1586</item>
               <item>597 <hi>London</hi>'s Resurrection, or the Re-building of <hi>London</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>598 Letter to a Deist, in Answer to several Objections, by <hi>Edw. Stillingfleet</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>599 Local Motion against Descartes 1670</item>
               <item>600 <hi>Lye</hi>'s Catechism 1675</item>
               <item>601 <hi>Lurancey</hi> against Irreligion</item>
               <item>602 <hi>Long</hi> against <hi>Hales</hi> of Schism 1678</item>
               <item>603 <hi>Lovel</hi>'s H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>story of Animals and Minerals <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>604 Bp. <hi>Lloyd</hi>'s Historical Account of Church-Government 1684</item>
               <item>605 Lively Oracles, by the Author of the Duty of Man <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>606 <hi>L'Estrange</hi>'s <hi>(Ham.)</hi> Observations on the History of K. <hi>Charles</hi> the First <hi>Lond.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>607 <hi>Leigh's (Edw.)</hi> Observations concerning the <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Greek</hi> Emperours 1670</item>
               <item>608 — his Three Discourses of Travel, Mony and Measuring 1671</item>
               <pb n="31" facs="tcp:42445:18"/>
               <item>609 <hi>Lawrence</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Interest of <hi>Ireland</hi> in its Trade and Wealth stated <hi>Lond.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>610 <hi>Lucian</hi>'s Works, with his Life, Translated by <hi>Fer. Spence</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>611 <hi>Luc etius</hi> Engl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>sh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>d by Mr. <hi>Cretoh</hi> with Notes <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>612 — The First Book Englished by <hi>J. Evelyn</hi> with Annotations <hi>Lond.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>613 <hi>Latham</hi>'s <hi>(Simon)</hi> Falconry, in two B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>oks 1658</item>
               <item>614 <hi>Lye</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Childs Delight, together with an <hi>English</hi> Grammar 1671</item>
               <item>615 — his method for Instructing the younger sort 1673</item>
               <item>616 Letters between Bp. <hi>Jewel</hi> and Dr. <hi>Cole</hi> 1560</item>
               <item>617 <hi>London</hi> Dispensatory enlarged, by <hi>Nich. Culpepper</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>618 Ladies Dispensatory. containing the vertues and qualities of Herbs and Simples 1652</item>
               <item>619 <hi>Latham</hi>'s Spaw in <hi>Lancashire</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>620 Loves of sundry Philosophers and other great Men 1673</item>
               <item>621 <hi>London</hi> Drollery, or the Wits Aoademy 1673</item>
               <item>622 <hi>Langford</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Instructions to raise Fruit-Trees in <hi>England</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>623 <hi>Latimer</hi>'s <hi>(Hugh)</hi> Sermons</item>
               <item>624 <hi>Luzancy</hi>'s Refl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ctions on the Councel of <hi>Trent Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>625 <hi>Lueius Florus</hi> Roman History 1669</item>
               <item>626 <hi>Legend</hi> of Captain <hi>Jones Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>627 <hi>Lucans</hi> Civil Wars of <hi>Rome,</hi> by <hi>Tho. May</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>628 <hi>L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>wrance</hi> Chri<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ts Power over Bodily Diseases 1672</item>
               <item>629 Life and Death of Captain <hi>William Bedlow</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>630 — Life and Death of the Earl of <hi>Rochester,</hi> by <hi>G. Burnet</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>631 — <hi>Is. Walton</hi>'s Life of Bishop <hi>Sanderson</hi> late Bishop of <hi>Lincoln</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>632 — <hi>Geo. Vernon</hi>'s Life of Dr. <hi>Peter Heylin</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>633 — Holy Life of Monsieur <hi>de Renty</hi> Noble Man of <hi>France</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>634 — Life of Mr. <hi>George Herbert,</hi> by <hi>Is. Walton</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>635 — <hi>L. Steerling</hi>'s Life of St. <hi>Agnes,</hi> Virgin and Martyr 1677</item>
               <item>636 — the Life of <hi>Mich. Adrian de Ruyter,</hi> Admiral of <hi>Holland</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>637 — Life and Death of the Virgin <hi>Mary</hi> 1620</item>
               <item>638 Life and Actions of General <hi>Monk,</hi> by <hi>Dav. Lloyd</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>639 — Life and Reign of King <hi>Edward</hi> the Third 1635</item>
               <item>640 — Life and Death of Dr. <hi>Andrew Rivett Hagh.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>641 — Life and Death of Bishop <hi>Cosins,</hi> by <hi>Is. Basire Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>642 — Life of Mr. <hi>Thomas Cauton</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>643 — Life of Mrs. <hi>Jane Ratcliff,</hi> by <hi>John Ley</hi> 1640</item>
               <item>644 — <hi>Gilb. Burnet</hi>'s Life and Death of Sir <hi>Matth. Hale</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>645 — of <hi>Galeacius</hi> Marquess of <hi>Vico</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>646 — of <hi>Sarah Wight</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>647 <hi>Morice</hi>'s Vindication of the Primitive Church and Episcopacy against <hi>Baxter</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>648 <hi>Marterson</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Assertion of the Kings Power in Ecclesiastical Affairs 1661</item>
               <item>649 <hi>Mackam</hi>'s <hi>(N.)</hi> Vindication of Ordinary and Publick Preaching 1657</item>
               <item>650 <hi>Marey</hi>'s <hi>(Ant.)</hi> Sermons preached before King, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>651 Mystery of Iniquity unfolded 1675</item>
               <item>652 Mystery of the Lords Supper clearly manifested 1614</item>
               <item>653 Mystery of Spiritual Growth 1622</item>
               <item>654 Mystery of Popery and Iniquity unfolded 1675</item>
               <item>655 <hi>M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>son</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Three Treatises of the Cure of Cares, Cuntentments, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>656 <hi>Milburn</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Wisdom crying out to Sinners 1638</item>
               <item>657 Manual, or Three small Treatises, by the Archbishop of <hi>York</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>658 <hi>Marvel</hi>'s <hi>(Andr.)</hi> Rehearsal Transpros'd, First part 1672</item>
               <pb n="32" facs="tcp:42445:19"/>
               <item>659 <hi>Mouln</hi>'s <hi>(Petr. du)</hi> Waters of <hi>Siloe</hi> to quench the Fire of Purgatory <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1612</item>
               <item>660 <hi>Milton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> History of <hi>Britain</hi> from the Beginning to the Conquest 1677</item>
               <item>661 <hi>Molin</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Anatomical Administration of all the Muscles <hi>Lond.</hi> 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>80</item>
               <item>662 Miscellany Tracts, written by Sir <hi>Tho. Brown</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>663 Most Blessed new Change, or Divine Contemplations 1657</item>
               <item>664 <hi>More</hi>'s <hi>(H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n.)</hi> Remarques on Two Books of the Ld. <hi>Hales, viz.</hi> of Fluid Bodies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>665 — his Remarques on Ld. <hi>Hale</hi>'s Observation about the Torricellian Experiment 1676</item>
               <item>666 <hi>Mackenzie</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Geo.</hi>) his Just and Solid Foundations of Monarchy 1684</item>
               <item>667 Memoires of the Family of the <hi>STƲARTS</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>668 Memoires of Mr. <hi>Desecotais,</hi> or the Motives of his Conversion 1677</item>
               <item>669 — Another <hi>French</hi> and <hi>English</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>670 — Another <hi>French</hi> alone 1677</item>
               <item>671 Monuments of Antiquities, touching the great Councils of the Kingdom 1680</item>
               <item>672 <hi>Monumenta Westmonasteriensia,</hi> by <hi>Hen. Keepe</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>673 Method for the well-guiding of Reason and discovery of truth in Sciences 1649</item>
               <item>674 <hi>Mantuan</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Bucolicks in Ten Eclogues, <hi>Englished</hi> by <hi>Tho. Harvey</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>675 <hi>Markham</hi>'s <hi>(Gerv.)</hi> Perfect Horseman 1680</item>
               <item>676 <hi>Marius (Jo.)</hi> his advice concerning Bills of Exchange 1674</item>
               <item>677 <hi>Marshal</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> his Philosophy delineated 1678</item>
               <item>678 — his Answers upon several Heads in Philosophy 1670</item>
               <item>679 Men-miracles with other Poems 1658</item>
               <item>680 <hi>Mills</hi>'s Poems, occasioned by a Melancholy Vision 1639</item>
               <item>681 — his Night-search, in a Poem, 2 parts, 2 vol. 1652</item>
               <item>682 <hi>Majerus</hi>'s <hi>(Mich) Lusus serius,</hi> or serious Pass-time 1654</item>
               <item>683 <hi>Manchester-al mando,</hi> a Contemplation of Death and Immortality 1639</item>
               <item>684 <hi>Mountain</hi>'s <hi>(James) Rome</hi>'s Destruction 1641</item>
               <item>685 <hi>Mercury</hi>'s Gallant, containing many pleasant Relations 1673</item>
               <item>685 — Another with pleasant passages at <hi>Paris</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>687 Mirrour of Complements, <hi>English,</hi> by Sir <hi>Franc. Hawkins</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>688 Moral Philosophy of the Stoicks, <hi>Englished</hi> by Esquire <hi>Charles Cotton</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>689 Merchants Names living in and about the City of <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>690 Manners, Religion and Government of the <hi>Turks,</hi> by <hi>Tho. Smith</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>691 <hi>Maupas</hi>'s <hi>(Charles)</hi> his <hi>French</hi> Grammar and Syntax 1674</item>
               <item>692 Mannors of the <hi>Israelites,</hi> in three parts 1683</item>
               <item>693 <hi>Monk</hi> Unviel'd, or a Facetious Dialogue 1678</item>
               <item>694 Dutchess of <hi>Mazaiine</hi>'s Memoires 1676</item>
               <item>695 <hi>Machiavel</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Discourses upon the First Decade of <hi>Titus Livius</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>696 Melancholy Vision, upon divers Theams, enlarged by <hi>N. Mills</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>697 Modern Policies taken from <hi>N. Macchiavel</hi> and <hi>Caes. Borgia</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>698 Mystery of Rhetorick unveil'd, by <hi>John Smith</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>699 <hi>Massanello,</hi> or the History of the Revolutions in <hi>Naples</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>700 <hi>Miege</hi>'s Dictionary, <hi>French</hi> and <hi>English</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>701 <hi>Mosley</hi>'s Contemplations on the Passions of Man 1653</item>
               <item>702 <hi>Machiavel</hi>'s Works, vol. 2. 1674</item>
               <item>703 <hi>Minderus</hi>'s <hi>(Raym.)</hi> his Body of Military Medicines experienced 1674</item>
               <item>704 <hi>Maynwaring</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Progress of Pains, Inflammations, Tumors 1679</item>
               <item>705 — his Compleat Physitian qualified and dignified 1668</item>
               <item>706 — his Treatise of the Scurvy 1666</item>
               <item>707 — his Rise and Progress of Physick 1668</item>
               <item>708 Manuduction to the Philosophers Magical Gold 1659</item>
               <pb n="33" facs="tcp:42445:19"/>
               <item>709 <hi>Maronides,</hi> or <hi>Virgil Travestie,</hi> Fifth Book, by <hi>J. Phillips Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>710 <hi>Modena</hi> Rites and Customs of the <hi>Jews▪</hi> by <hi>Chilmead</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>711 Monuments of <hi>Westminster</hi>-Church 1672</item>
               <item>712 — of the Church of <hi>Durham</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>713 Manual of Millions, or Accounts ready cast up 1669</item>
               <item>714 Mock <hi>Clelia▪</hi> or Madam <hi>Q<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ixot</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>715 Dr. <hi>More</hi>'s Reply to a late Answer to his Antidote 1672</item>
               <item>716 — Exposition on the Seven Churches 1669</item>
               <item>717 — Divine Dialogues compleat, vol. 2. 1668</item>
               <item>718 — Two last Dialogues of the Kingdom of God 1668</item>
               <item>719 Monuments of <hi>Exeter</hi> 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>81</item>
               <item>720 <hi>Montagne</hi>'s Essays, with his Life 1685</item>
               <item>721 Nullity of the <hi>Romish</hi> Faith, by <hi>Matthew Pool</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>722 No Protestant Plot, but the Dissenters Plot discovered and defeated 1682</item>
               <item>723 Non-Conformists Vindicated from the abuses put on them by Mr. <hi>Durel</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>724 <hi>Netherland</hi> Historian, from 1671, to 1674. with Figures <hi>Amster.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>725 New way of curing the Gout, with <hi>Medico-Chyrurgical</hi> Observations <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>726 New light of Alchymy, with a Treatise of Sulphur 1674</item>
               <item>727 — Another with <hi>Paracelsus,</hi> nature of Times 1671</item>
               <item>728 <hi>Nichol</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Crying Voice of the Holy Spirit of Love</item>
               <item>729 <hi>Naudeus</hi>'s History of <hi>Magick</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>730 New Politick Lights, or Modern <hi>Romes</hi> Church Government 1678</item>
               <item>731 <hi>Newton</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Scale of Interest, or the use of Decimal Fractions 1668</item>
               <item>732 — Art of Gaging 1660</item>
               <item>733 <hi>Niremberg</hi>'s <hi>(Eus.)</hi> Treatise of the difference betwixt Temporals and Eternals 1672</item>
               <item>734 No Power but of God, or a Word in Season by <hi>Rob. Purnel</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>735 Narrative of the <hi>Spanish</hi> Invasion and the Powder Plot <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>671</item>
               <item>736 <hi>Nemcomb</hi>'s Best Acquaintance 1668</item>
               <item>737 Natural and Artificial Conclusions 1651</item>
               <item>738 Dr. <hi>Owen</hi> of Indwelling Sin in Believers 1675</item>
               <item>739 — Nature and Principles of Love 1673</item>
               <item>740 Only way to Salvation, by <hi>William Guild</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>741 Original and Growth of the <hi>Spanish</hi> Monarchy, by <hi>Thom. Philipot</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>742 <hi>Ovid</hi> in <hi>English</hi>
               </item>
               <item>743 Observations upon the Humour of writing Rehearsal Transpros'd <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>744 <hi>Ovid</hi>'s Five Books of mournful Elegies, or <hi>Tristia Lond.</hi> 1637</item>
               <item>745 Occasional Reflections on several Subjects, by Esquire <hi>Boyle</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>746 <hi>Osburn</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Tho.</hi>) Political Reflections upon the Government of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>747 Observations upon Dr. <hi>Brown</hi>'s <hi>Religio Medici,</hi> by Sir <hi>Kenelm Digby</hi> 1643</item>
               <item>748 Observations on the <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Greek</hi> Emperours, by <hi>Edw. Leigh</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>749 Observations touching the Principles of Natural motions, by Ld. <hi>Hale</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>750 <hi>Oughtred</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Circles of proportion, and the Horizantal Instrument, <hi>&amp;c Oxon.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>751 Optick-Glass of Humours, by <hi>T. W. Lond.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>752 Opinions of Mr. <hi>Hobb</hi>'s considered in a 2d Prologue, by Dr. <hi>Eccherd</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>753 Observations and Advices Oeconomical 1669</item>
               <item>754 — On the Mineral Waters of <hi>France</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>755 Primitive Chistianity, in Three parts, by Dr. <hi>Will. Cave</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>756 <hi>Psalms,</hi> Prose and Metre, translated by King <hi>James</hi>
               </item>
               <item>757 Principles of the Oracles of God 1677</item>
               <item>758 <hi>Parker</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Case of the Church of <hi>England</hi> truly stated 1681</item>
               <pb n="34" facs="tcp:42445:20"/>
               <item>759 — his Vindication of Bp. <hi>Bramhall</hi> and the Clergy from the Carge of Popery <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>760 — his Reproof to the Rehearsal Transpros'd 1673</item>
               <item>761 — his Discourse of Ecclesiastical Politie 1670</item>
               <item>762 <hi>Pool</hi>'s <hi>(Matth.)</hi> Nullity of the <hi>Romish</hi> Faith 1679</item>
               <item>763 Popery absolutely destructive to Monarchy 1673</item>
               <item>764 <hi>Purnel</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> No Power but of God 1657</item>
               <item>765 <hi>Powel</hi>'s <hi>(Walth.)</hi> Summons for Swearers 1645</item>
               <item>766 <hi>Potter</hi>'s <hi>(Christ.)</hi> want of Charity in <hi>Roman Catholicks</hi> 1635</item>
               <item>767 <hi>Patrick (Sym.)</hi> Book of <hi>Psalms</hi> Paraphras'd with Arguments, 2 vol. 1680</item>
               <item>768 — his Divine Arithmetick, or Art of numbring our Days 1679</item>
               <item>769 Publick Devotion of the Church of <hi>England</hi> justifyed and recommended 1675</item>
               <item>770 <hi>Polhill</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Answer to Dr. <hi>Sherlock</hi>'s Discourse of the Knowledge of Christ 1675</item>
               <item>771 — his Preparation for a suffering in a Evil Day 1682</item>
               <item>772 Perswasives to Prayer and Devotion, with Domestick Devotions 1683</item>
               <item>773 Plain and Familiar Method of Justifying the Younger sort 1673</item>
               <item>774 <hi>Penn</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Six several Tracts in Defence of the Quakers 167</item>
               <item>775 <hi>Proverbs</hi> of <hi>Solomon, English</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>776 <hi>Peganius</hi>'s Explication of the Visions of the <hi>Revelations</hi>
               </item>
               <item>777 Principal made Practical, or Directions for Christians 1674</item>
               <item>778 Power, Nature, Deceit, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Indwelling Sin in Believers 1677</item>
               <item>779 <hi>Price</hi>'s <hi>(Galv.)</hi> of Thoughts improved 1664</item>
               <item>780 Popery absolutely destructive to Monarchy 1673</item>
               <item>781 Pattern of universal Knowledge, by <hi>Jo. Am. Comenius</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>782 <hi>Polanus (Am.)</hi> his substance of the Christian Religion 1608</item>
               <item>783 Policy of the Clergy of <hi>France</hi> to destroy the Protestants of that Kingdom 1681</item>
               <item>784 <hi>Polygraphice,</hi> or the Arts of Drawing, Limning, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>W. Salmon</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>785 Prodromus to a Dissertation concerning Solids, by <hi>Nic. Steno</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>786 Period of Humane Life whether Mutable or Immutable 1678</item>
               <item>787 <hi>Phillips</hi>'s <hi>(Fabian)</hi> that King <hi>Charles</hi> the First was a Martyr 1680</item>
               <item>788 Pedegree and Peregrination of <hi>Israel</hi> 1649</item>
               <item>789 Preparation to the Holy Ministry 1598</item>
               <item>790 <hi>Powel</hi>'s <hi>(Gabr.)</hi> Resolution of the First Chapter of the <hi>Romans Oxon.</hi> 1602</item>
               <item>791 Practice of Piety, by <hi>Lewis Bayly Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>792 <hi>Par</hi>'s <hi>(Eln.)</hi> Grounds of Divinity 1619</item>
               <item>793 Publick Devotion and Common Service of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>794 <hi>Pearse</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Warning to a timely preparation for Death 1674</item>
               <item>795 <hi>Pierce</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Sinner impleaded in his own Court 1656</item>
               <item>796 <hi>Par Nobile,</hi> or Dr. <hi>Collins</hi>'s, Two Treatises on the Death of two Ladies 1669</item>
               <item>797 <hi>Plato</hi>'s Demon, in Answer to <hi>Plato Redevius</hi>
               </item>
               <item>798 <hi>Parnassus Bicips,</hi> or Choice Poems 1656</item>
               <item>799 <hi>Polhill</hi>'s Precious Faith considered 1675</item>
               <item>800 Philosophical Epitaph of <hi>W. C.</hi> for a <hi>Memento Mori</hi> on the Philosophers (Tomb) Stone 1673</item>
               <item>801 <hi>Plutarch</hi>'s Lives Abridg'd 1665</item>
               <item>802 <hi>Palmer</hi>'s Gospel New-Creature 1674</item>
               <item>803 Pleas of the Crown 1678</item>
               <item>804 <hi>Pool</hi>'s <hi>English Parnassus,</hi> or help to <hi>English</hi> Poesie 1677</item>
               <item>805 <hi>Prodromus</hi> to a Dissertation concerning Solids 1671</item>
               <item>806 <hi>Petyt</hi>'s Ancient Right of the Commons of <hi>England</hi> Asserted 1686</item>
               <item>807 <hi>Phillips</hi>'s <hi>(N.)</hi> Grandeure of the Law 1684</item>
               <pb n="35" facs="tcp:42445:20"/>
               <item>808 <hi>Plutarch</hi>'s Morals, translated by several Hands, 2 volumes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>809 <hi>Petyt</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Ancient Right of the Commons of <hi>England</hi> asserted 1680</item>
               <item>810 Presant State of <hi>Samos, Micarea, Patmos,</hi> and Mount <hi>Athos</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>811 Poetical Histories, by <hi>P. Galtruchius</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>812 — Another with the Curiosities of Old <hi>Rome,</hi> Fifth Edition 1683</item>
               <item>813 <hi>Problem</hi>'s of <hi>A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>istotle,</hi> with other Philosophers and Physitians 1683</item>
               <item>814 Prospect of the State of <hi>Ireland</hi> from <hi>An. Mundi</hi> 1756. to <hi>An. Chriwi</hi> 1652. 1682</item>
               <item>815 Period of Humane Life, whether Mutable or Immutable 1677</item>
               <item>816 Painters Voyage into <hi>Italy</hi> by <hi>Giacom. Berry</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>817 <hi>Porter</hi>'s <hi>Jachmas</hi> Prince of <hi>Persia,</hi> a Novel 1676</item>
               <item>818 Poems on several Occasions, by <hi>N. Tate</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>819 <hi>Philalethe</hi>'s <hi>(Eug.) Magia Adamica,</hi> or the Antiquity of Magick 1650</item>
               <item>820 — his Fame and Confession of the Fraternity of the Rosie-Cross 1652</item>
               <item>821 <hi>Plat</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Hugh</hi>) Garden of <hi>Eden,</hi> two parts compleat 1675</item>
               <item>822 Popery absolutely destructive to Monarchy 1673</item>
               <item>823 <hi>Philalethe</hi>'s <hi>(Eiren.)</hi> Exposition upon <hi>Geo. Ripley</hi>'s Hermetico-Poetical Works 1678</item>
               <item>824 Progress of Pains, Inflammations, Tumors, Aposthumes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Edw. Mainwaring</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>825 Perfect Horseman, or the experienced Secrets of Mr. <hi>Markham</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>826 Poems, Elegies, Paradoxes and Sonnets 1657</item>
               <item>827 Poems on several Occasions, and to several Persons 1675</item>
               <item>828 Poems occasioned by a Melancholy Vision, by <hi>H. Mills</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>829 <hi>Pub. Ovid</hi>'s Heroical Epistles, in <hi>English</hi> Verse 1600</item>
               <item>830 <hi>Polhill</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Answer to Dr. <hi>Sherlocks</hi> Knowledge of Christ 1675</item>
               <item>831 <hi>Philipot</hi>'s <hi>(Thom.)</hi> Original and Growth of the <hi>Spanish</hi> Monarchy 1664</item>
               <item>832 Philosophical Discourse of Fermentation, by <hi>Will. Symson</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>833 <hi>Partride</hi>'s <hi>(Seth)</hi> Description of the Instr. called the Double Scale of Proportion 1671</item>
               <item>834 Philosophical Essay of the Immortality of the Soul <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>835 <hi>Paracelsus</hi> his <hi>Aurora</hi> and Treasure of the Philosophers <hi>Lond.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>836 <hi>Quintus Curtius</hi>'s Life and Death of <hi>Alexander</hi> the Great 1674</item>
               <item>837 <hi>Quarles</hi>'s <hi>(Fran.)</hi> Emblems 1684</item>
               <item>838 — Another with Hieroglyphiks of the Life of Man 1684</item>
               <item>839 — his Divine Poems Revised and Corrected, with additions 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>840 <hi>Quevedo</hi>'s Visions, the Sixth Edition corrected 1678</item>
               <item>841 — his Hell Reformed, or a Glass for Favorites 1641</item>
               <item>842 Queen-Like Closet, or rich Closet of rare Receipts 1675</item>
               <item>843 Question of Witchcraft debated, a Discourse against Witches 1669</item>
               <item>844 Queens-Wells, or a Treatise of the Waters at <hi>Timbridge</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>845 Reproof to the Rehearsal Transpros'd, by <hi>Sam. Parker</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>846 <hi>Ross</hi>'s <hi>(Alex.)</hi> View of all Religions in the World 1613</item>
               <item>847 — his <hi>Mystagogus Poetieus,</hi> or the Muses Interpreter 1672</item>
               <item>848 <hi>Roll</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.) London</hi>'s Resurrection, or the Re-building of <hi>London</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>849 <hi>Ranew</hi>'s <hi>(Nath.)</hi> Solitude improved by Divine Meditation 1670</item>
               <item>850 <hi>Row</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Saints Temptations 1675</item>
               <item>851 Renunciation of several Popish Doctrines 1680</item>
               <item>852 <hi>Row (Jo.)</hi> of Heavenly mindedness, and Earthly mindedness 1672</item>
               <item>853 <hi>Ryther</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> best Friend standing at the Door 1672</item>
               <item>854 <hi>Robrough</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Balm from <hi>Gilead</hi> 1626</item>
               <item>855 <hi>Robotham</hi>'s <hi>(Charles)</hi> Sermons preached on several occasions 1681</item>
               <item>856 <hi>Rouse</hi>'s <hi>(Franc.)</hi> his Catholick Charity 1641</item>
               <item>857 <hi>Robert</hi>'s <hi>(Francis)</hi> Believers Evidence for Eternal Life 1655</item>
               <pb n="36" facs="tcp:42445:21"/>
               <item>858 Remarques upon a late disingenious Discourse, writ by one <hi>T. D.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>859 <hi>Regi Sacrum</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>860 <hi>Reynold</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Meditations on the fall and rising of S. <hi>Peter</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>861 <hi>Robertson</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Admonitory Epistle to Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi> and <hi>Tho. Hotcbkiss</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>862 <hi>Rome</hi> is no Rule, in Answer to Captain <hi>Robert Everard</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>863 Review of the Grand Case of the present Ministry 1663</item>
               <item>864 <hi>Robertson</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Key to the <hi>Hebrew</hi> Bible 1656</item>
               <item>865 <hi>Rall</hi>'s Burning of <hi>London</hi> 1666. commemorated 1667</item>
               <item>866 <hi>Reyner</hi>'s Precepts fot Christian Practice 1668</item>
               <item>867 Remarks on the Government of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>868 Rites of Funerals, Ancient and Modern, by Monsieur <hi>Murett</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>869 Right of Tythes re-asserted against Mr. <hi>Selden</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>870 Remembrancer of Excellent Men, <hi>viz. R. Hooker, Reynolds,</hi> &amp;c. 1670</item>
               <item>871 Reflection upon the Use of the Eloquence of these Times <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>872 Relation of divers main passages relating to these troublesome Times <hi>Lond.</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>873 — of the unfortunate Expedion of <hi>Kent, Essex,</hi> and <hi>Colchester</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>874 — of the Poysoning of an whole Family in <hi>Plymouth</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>875 — of the Siege of <hi>Candia</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>876 — of a Voyage made into <hi>Mauritania</hi> in <hi>Africk</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>877 — of a Conference held about Religion, <hi>April</hi> 3d. 1676 1676</item>
               <item>878 <hi>Rome</hi>'s Glory, or a Collection of Miracles wrought by Popish Saints 1673</item>
               <item>879 Remarques on the State of the Church of the first Centuries 1680</item>
               <item>880 <hi>Rome A la-mode,</hi> with the Sentiments of the Court and Cardinals 1678</item>
               <item>881 <hi>Ray</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> his Collection of <hi>English</hi> Proverbs, with Annotations <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>832 <hi>Ray</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Observations made in his Travels through Low-Countrys, <hi>Germany,</hi> &amp;c. 1673</item>
               <item>883 — Another with a Catalogue of Outlandish Plants 1673</item>
               <item>884 Remarks made on Ld. <hi>Hale</hi>'s of Fluid Bodies, and the Torricellian experiment 2676</item>
               <item>885 — made upon the Manners and Religion of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>886 <hi>Renatus Rapinus</hi> of Gardens, in Four Books, <hi>Englished</hi> by <hi>Jo. Evelyn</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>887 Relation of an unfortunate Voyage into <hi>Bengala</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>888 — Of the pleasant passages at <hi>Paris,</hi> or <hi>Mercury</hi> Gallant 1673</item>
               <item>889 — Of the River <hi>Nile</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>890 <hi>Read</hi>'s <hi>(Alexand.)</hi> Anatomy, with explanations of Chirurgical Instruments 1634</item>
               <item>891 — his Description of the Body of Man 1634</item>
               <item>892 <hi>Ripley</hi> Reviv'd, or an Exposition upon Sir <hi>Geo. Ripley</hi> Herm. poetical Works 1678</item>
               <item>893 <hi>Rob.</hi> Records, Urinal of Physick 1651</item>
               <item>894 <hi>Rabisha</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Whole Body of Cookery dissected 1673</item>
               <item>895 <hi>Ramsey</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Physical considerations of Worms 1668</item>
               <item>896 Rites and Monuments of the Cathedral Church of <hi>Durham</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>897 <hi>Rowzee</hi>'s <hi>(Franc.)</hi> Queens Wells, or Treatise of <hi>Tunbridge</hi> Water 1671</item>
               <item>898 <hi>Ross</hi>'s <hi>(Alex.)</hi> his Muses Interpreter 1672</item>
               <item>899 <hi>Roll</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.) London</hi>'s Resurrection, or the Re-building of <hi>London</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>900 Remarques on the Humours and Conversations of the Town 1675</item>
               <item>901 Remedies of the Distempers of the Times 1675</item>
               <item>902 Records, Arithmetick 1662</item>
               <item>903 Father <hi>Simonds</hi>'s Critical History of Religion of <hi>Eastern</hi> Nations 1685</item>
               <item>904 <hi>Scots</hi>'s Christian Life, 2 vol.</item>
               <item>905 — <hi>Idem,</hi> First volume</item>
               <item>906 — <hi>Item,</hi> Second volume</item>
               <item>907 <hi>Stillingfleet</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Relation of a Conference held about Religion 1676</item>
               <pb n="37" facs="tcp:42445:21"/>
               <item>908 — his Answer to several Treatises against his Discourse of Idolatry 2 vol. <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>909 — his Conference with Mr. <hi>Coleman</hi> about Religion 1679</item>
               <item>910 — his Second Discourse against the Infallibility of the <hi>Roman</hi> Church 1673</item>
               <item>911 — several Conferences against <hi>T. Goodwin</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>912 — his Defence of his Discourse of Idolatry of the Church of <hi>Rome</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>913 — his Letter to a Deist in Answer to several Objection, 1677</item>
               <item>914 — <hi>(John)</hi> his Demonstration of Divine Presence in Relig. places of worship. 1663</item>
               <item>915 Saint Indeed, by <hi>John Flavel</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>916 <hi>Steel</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Plain Discourse of Uprightness 1672</item>
               <item>917 Several — Sermons</item>
               <item>918 Situation of Paradice found out, or an History of a Pilgrimage to the <hi>Holy-Land</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>919 <hi>Stanwick</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Christian Warfare, or several Sermons 1657</item>
               <item>920 <hi>Seignior</hi>'s <hi>(Geor.)</hi> Eight Sermons of God, the King, and the Church 1670</item>
               <item>921 <hi>Sherlock</hi>'s (Dr.) Defence and Continuation of his disc. of the knowledge of Christ. 1675</item>
               <item>922 — his Continuation and Vindication of the def. of <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> of Separation 1682</item>
               <item>923 — his Discourse concerning the Knowledge of Christ 1674</item>
               <item>924 Soul-Reviving Influence, or the Son of Righteousness 1654</item>
               <item>925 <hi>Saywell (Will.)</hi> Of Evangelical Unity of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>926 Summons for Swearers, by <hi>Walth. Powel</hi> 1645</item>
               <item>927 <hi>Spark</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Primitive Devotion in the Feasts and Fasts of the Ch. of <hi>England</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>928 Substance of the Christian Religion, by <hi>Amandus Polamus</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>929 <hi>Slater</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Treatise of Groth in Grace, in sundry Sermons 1671</item>
               <item>930 <hi>Solomon</hi>'s <hi>Proverbs</hi> Methodized, <hi>English</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>931 <hi>Swinnock</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Sinners last Sentence to Eternal punishment 1675</item>
               <item>932 <hi>Sheppard</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Subjection to Christ in all his Ordinances 1657</item>
               <item>933 <hi>Sherlock</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Practical Christian, the second part 1675</item>
               <item>934 <hi>Sendivogius</hi>'s <hi>(Mich.)</hi> his new Light of Alchymy 1674</item>
               <item>935 — Another with a Treatise of Sulphur 1674</item>
               <item>936 <hi>Spelman</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Hen.</hi>) Churches not to be Violated <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>937 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Two Sermons at two publick Assizes in <hi>Suffolk Lond.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>938 <hi>Scudder</hi>'s <hi>(Henry)</hi> Christians Dayly-walk in Holy Security and Peace 1627</item>
               <item>939 <hi>Senauli</hi>'s <hi>(J. Fr.)</hi> Paraphrase upon <hi>Job</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>940 Sincerity and Hypocrisie, or the Sincere Christian <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>941 <hi>Sutton</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.) England</hi>'s Summons <hi>Lond.</hi> 1613</item>
               <item>942 <hi>Stocks</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Doctrine and Use of Repentance 1610</item>
               <item>943 <hi>Sqire</hi>'<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <hi>(Will.)</hi> Unreasonableness of the <hi>Romanists</hi> requiring our Commun. with them 1674</item>
               <item>944 <hi>Sheffield</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Rising Sun shining on a Theological-Dial 1654</item>
               <item>945 State of Christianity Examined, Unfolded and Character'd 1655</item>
               <item>946 <hi>Serranus</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> his Commentary on <hi>Ecclesiastes</hi> 1585</item>
               <item>947 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> King <hi>Solomon</hi>'s Pourtraicture of old Age 1666</item>
               <item>948 — <hi>Sam.</hi> his Great Assize, or Day of Jubilee, in four Sermons 1633</item>
               <item>949 <hi>Sheppard</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Sincere Convert, with the Saints Jewel 1672</item>
               <item>950 — his Subjection to Christ in all his Ordinances 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>57</item>
               <item>951 Bp. <hi>Sanderson</hi>'s Nine Cases of Conscience 1478</item>
               <item>952 <hi>Scortreth</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Warning-piece to the sl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>mbring Virgins 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>72</item>
               <item>953 <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lkeld</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Treatise of Paradise 1617</item>
               <item>954 — his Treatise of Angels, with all their Proprieties 1613</item>
               <item>955 <hi>Shelton</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Necessity of Morality among Christians 1667</item>
               <item>956 <hi>Sharrock</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> History of the Improvement of Vegetables 1672</item>
               <item>957 Survey of the United Provinces of the <hi>Netherlands</hi> 1673</item>
               <pb n="38" facs="tcp:42445:22"/>
               <item>958 <hi>Sprackling</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Vindication of <hi>Hippocrates</hi> and <hi>Galen Lond.</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>959 <hi>Seaman</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Reign of <hi>Sultan Orchain,</hi> 2d King of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>960 <hi>Sophoclis Electra,</hi> with Poems of the Kings Return 1649</item>
               <item>961 <hi>Stephen</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Essays and Characters 1615</item>
               <item>962 <hi>Starkey</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Natures Explication, and <hi>Helmoni</hi>'s Vindication 1657</item>
               <item>963 <hi>Sheppard</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Epigram, in Six Books 1651</item>
               <item>964 <hi>Struthy</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Christian Observation and Resolution 1629</item>
               <item>965 Sin the Plague of Plagues, by <hi>Ralph Venning</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>966 <hi>Sibbs</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> his Spiritual Mans Aim 1638</item>
               <item>967 Scism disarmed of defensive Weapons <hi>Paris</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>968 Substance of Christion Religion, by <hi>Will. Ames Lond.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>969 Sacriledge Arraigned and Condemned, by <hi>Is. Basire</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>970 <hi>Sermon</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Companion, or the <hi>English</hi> Midwife 1671</item>
               <item>971 <hi>Shotterel</hi>'s <hi>(Rob.)</hi> Archery Reviv'd, or the Bow-mans Excellence 1676</item>
               <item>972 <hi>Sall</hi>'s Catholick Religion maintained in the Church of <hi>England Oxon.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>973 Bp. <hi>Sanderson</hi>'s Life, with several Tracts <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>974 <hi>Shaw</hi>'s No Reformation of the Established Reformation 1685</item>
               <item>975 Some Instructions concerning the Art of Oratory <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>976 <hi>Stubb</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> his Arts of Grandeur and Submission <hi>Lond.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>977 <hi>Scot</hi>'s <hi>(Patrick)</hi> Table-Book for Princes 1611</item>
               <item>978 <hi>Saul</hi> and <hi>Samuel</hi> at <hi>Endor Oxon.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>979 <hi>Selden</hi>'s Office of Ld. Chancellor, by <hi>Dugdale</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>980 <hi>Smith (John)</hi> his Mystery of Rhetorick unveiled <hi>Lond.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>981 — his Steremetry or the Art of Practical Gauging 1673</item>
               <item>982 <hi>Scott</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Of the Language of the Bird and Beast 1616</item>
               <item>983 Survey of the united Provinces of the <hi>Netherlands</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>984 <hi>Stapleton</hi> (Sir <hi>Rob.</hi>) his Translation of <hi>Juvenals</hi> 16 Satyrs 1673</item>
               <item>985 <hi>Scudery</hi>'s (Mr.) Triumphant Arch consecrated to the glory of the Feminine Sex 1656</item>
               <item>986 <hi>Speed</hi> s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Abridgment of his Maps of <hi>England, Scotland</hi> and <hi>Ireland</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>987 — Another with the Foreign Maps 1696</item>
               <item>988 <hi>Selden</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Discourse of the Office of Ld. Chancellour of <hi>England</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>989 Sober Inspections into the Carriage of the long Parliament 1655</item>
               <item>990 <hi>Salmon</hi>'s <hi>(Will.) Polygraphicie,</hi> or the Arts of Drawing, Limning, Painting, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>991 — his Supplement to the New <hi>London</hi> Dispensatory 1683</item>
               <item>992 State-worthies, or the Statesmen and Favorites of <hi>Engl.</hi> since the Reformation 1670</item>
               <item>993 <hi>Shelton</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Method for Short-Writing 1668</item>
               <item>994 Scoffer Scoft, being some of <hi>Lucian</hi>'s Dialogues 1675</item>
               <item>995 <hi>Spencer</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Sheappa<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ds Calendar 1653</item>
               <item>996 Strappado for the Divel, <hi>viz.</hi> Epigrams, and Satyrs 1615</item>
               <item>997 Spaw of <hi>Latham</hi> in <hi>Lancashire,</hi> with the Effects and Cures of it 1670</item>
               <item>998 <hi>Sendivagius</hi>'s <hi>(Mich.)</hi> his new light of Alchymy, with a Treatise of Sulphur 1674</item>
               <item>999 <hi>Spadacrene Dunelme<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>sis,</hi> or a Treatise of the <hi>Vitrioline</hi> Spaw near <hi>Durham</hi>
               </item>
               <item>1000 <hi>Sympson</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Philosophical Discourse of Fermentation 1675</item>
               <item>1001 — his Hydrological Essays, being a discovery of <hi>Scarboroagh</hi>'s Spaw 1670</item>
               <item>1002 — his Chymical Anatomy of the Spaws in <hi>Yorkshire</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>1003 — his Hydrological Essays about <hi>Scarborough</hi>'s Spaw 1670</item>
               <item>1004 <hi>Sennertus (Dan.)</hi> Of the most predominant Diseases of these Times 1676</item>
               <item>1005 Scale of Interest, or the use of Decimal Fractions, by <hi>Jo. Newton</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>1006 <hi>Smith</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Remarks upon the Manners▪ Religion, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>1007 — his Account of the <hi>Greek</hi> Church 1680 &amp; 1676</item>
               <pb n="39" facs="tcp:42445:22"/>
               <item>1008 — <hi>(John)</hi> Art of Painting <hi>Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1009 Solids naturally contained within Solids, by <hi>Nic. Steno</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1010 <hi>Steno</hi>'s <hi>(Nic.)</hi> Prodromus to a Dissertation concerning Solids 1671</item>
               <item>1011 <hi>Schroder</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> History of Animals 1659</item>
               <item>1012 <hi>Sharp</hi>'s <hi>(Jane)</hi> Midwifes Book, or whole Art of Midwifry 1671</item>
               <item>1013 <hi>Sherley</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Curiosities of Scurvy-Grass 1676</item>
               <item>1014 <hi>Truman</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Great Propitiation, or Christs satisfaction 1672</item>
               <item>1015 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s (<hi>Jer.</hi> Bp.) Discourse of Confirmation 1664</item>
               <item>1016 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s (Bp. <hi>Jer.</hi>) Discourse of Confirmation 1665</item>
               <item>1017 — his Disswasive from Popery 1664</item>
               <item>1018 — his Measures of Friendship, with additional Tracts 1678</item>
               <item>1019 Treatise of delighting in God, by <hi>John How</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>1020 Three Ministers Notions and Collections 1675</item>
               <item>1021 <hi>Trahern</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Christian Ethicks, or Divine Morality 1675</item>
               <item>1022 <hi>Tower</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Four Sermons on several eminent Occasions 1660</item>
               <item>1023 <hi>Truman</hi>'s <hi>(Jos.)</hi> Great Propitiation, or Christs Satisfaction 1672</item>
               <item>1024 Treatise of Baptism 1672</item>
               <item>1025 <hi>Turner</hi>'s <hi>(J.)</hi> Choice Experiences toward Conversion 1653</item>
               <item>1026 <hi>Tallotson</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Sermons preached on several Occasions 1671</item>
               <item>1027 <hi>Taylor (Tho.)</hi> Treatise of Contentment 1641</item>
               <item>1028 — his Observations from the Baptism of Christ 1620</item>
               <item>1029 <hi>Theologica Germanica,</hi> or mystical Divinity 1648</item>
               <item>1030 Treatise of Indwelling Sin in Believers 1675</item>
               <item>1031 Treatise against Popery in Defence of the Reformed Churches <hi>Cambr.</hi> 1598</item>
               <item>1032 Transproser Rehears'd, or the Fifth Act of Mr. <hi>Bay</hi>'s Play <hi>Gxon.</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>1033 <hi>Thomas</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Country's sense of <hi>London</hi>'s sufferings <hi>Lond.</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>1034 Treatise of the Holy Communion 1677</item>
               <item>1035 Treatise of Sacramental Covenanting with Christ 1674</item>
               <item>1036 <hi>Thompson</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Manner of Dissecting pestilential Bodies 1666</item>
               <item>1037 Treatise of Gardens, in four Books, by <hi>Ren. Rapinus</hi> in Verse 1673</item>
               <item>1038 Treatise of the Principle Grounds of Christian Religion 1670</item>
               <item>1039 Treatise of Melancholy, by <hi>Tho. Bright</hi> 1586</item>
               <item>1040 Tracts about Cosmical Qualities of Things <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1041 <hi>Temple</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Observations upon the united Provinces <hi>Lond.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>1042 — his Miscellanea, the 2d Edition augmented 1681</item>
               <item>1043 <hi>Tuke</hi>'s <hi>(Thom.)</hi> Treasure of true Love 1608</item>
               <item>1044 Touchstone for Gold and Silver Wares, or a Manual for Goldsmiths 1677</item>
               <item>1045 <hi>Tate</hi>'s <hi>(Nich.)</hi> Poems written on several Occasions 1684</item>
               <item>1046 Three Discourses of Travel, of Mony, and Measuring 1671</item>
               <item>1047 Triumphant Lady, or the Crowned Innocence 1656</item>
               <item>1048 Treatise of the Scurvey, by <hi>Everard Mainwaring</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>1049 Touchstone of a Golden Temper, or the Optick-Glass of Humours 1639</item>
               <item>1050 <hi>Tachmas</hi> Prince of <hi>Persia,</hi> an Historical Novel 1676</item>
               <item>1051 Tragical Loves of <hi>Hippolito</hi> and <hi>Isabella</hi> Neapolitans 1628</item>
               <item>1052 Treatise of Ancient CeremonIes, or the Degenerate Plant 1668</item>
               <item>1053 <hi>Theocritus Idylliums,</hi> with <hi>Rapin</hi>'s Discourse of Pastorals 1684</item>
               <item>1054 Thousand notable Things 1650</item>
               <item>1055 <hi>Tate</hi>'s <hi>(Nich.)</hi> Poems on several occasions 1677</item>
               <item>1056 Touchstone of Gold and Silver Wares, or a Manual for Goldsmiths 1677</item>
               <item>1057 <hi>Thrasher</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Marrow of Chymical Physick 1679</item>
               <pb n="40" facs="tcp:42445:23"/>
               <item>1058 Vanity of Arts and Sciences, dy <hi>Hen. Corn. Agrippa Lond.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>1059 Unreasonableness of Separation, the second part, with Remarks on <hi>R. Baxter</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>1060 Vindication of the Primitive Church and Diocesan Episcopacy against <hi>Baxter</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>1061 — Another against Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Church-History 1682</item>
               <item>1062 Unreasonableness of the <hi>Romanists</hi> in requiring our Communion with them. 1674</item>
               <item>1063 Visions of the <hi>Revelations</hi> explained, by <hi>A. B. Peganius</hi>
               </item>
               <item>1064 <hi>Velitationes Polemicae,</hi> or Polemical Discussions, by <hi>J. Doughty</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>1065 <hi>Virel</hi>'s <hi>(Pet.)</hi> Principal Grounds of the Christian Religion 1620</item>
               <item>1366 Vindication of <hi>Clement Writer</hi> against <hi>Rich. Baxter</hi>'s Forefold Charge 16</item>
               <item>1067 — of Infant-Baptism against <hi>Her. D. Anvers,</hi> by <hi>Ob. Wills</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1068 <hi>Ʋrsinus (Zach.)</hi> Summ of Christian Religion <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1580</item>
               <item>1069 <hi>Venning</hi>'s <hi>(Ralph)</hi> Sin the Plague of Plagues <hi>Lond.</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>1070 <hi>Virgil</hi>'s Works Translated, by <hi>John Ogilby</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>1071 <hi>Va<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>x</hi> (Monsieur <hi>du</hi>) of the Moral Philosophy of the <hi>Stoicks</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1072 Voyage lately made to <hi>Constantinople,</hi> with an account of the <hi>Greek</hi> Church 1683</item>
               <item>1073 — made into <hi>Mauri<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ania</hi> and <hi>Fez</hi> in <hi>Africa</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1074 — made to <hi>Taffileta</hi> in <hi>Barbary</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>1075 <hi>Vern<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n</hi>'s <hi>(Goo.)</hi> Life of Dr. <hi>Peter Heylin</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>1076 <hi>Virgil</hi>'s Travestie, being a Paraphrase on the 5th and 6th Books of <hi>Aeneids</hi> 2 vol. 1672</item>
               <item>1077 Vindication of the Conversations of the Town 1673</item>
               <item>1378 Use of Decimal Fractions, or Seale of Interest, by <hi>Jo. Newton</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>1079 <hi>Vindiciae Senectutis,</hi> or a Plea for old Age 1639</item>
               <item>1080 <hi>Vaughan</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Church Militant 1640</item>
               <item>1081 Urinal of Physick, by <hi>Rob. Record</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>1082 <hi>Vaughan</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Select Poems and Translations 1651</item>
               <item>1083 <hi>Walker</hi>'s <hi>(Ob.)</hi> Paraphrase on the Epistles of St. <hi>Paul Oxon.</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>1084 — Additions alone</item>
               <item>1085 <hi>Ward</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Divine vertue epitomized <hi>Lond.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>1086 <hi>Will</hi>'s <hi>(Ob.)</hi> Vindication of his Treatise of Baptism against <hi>H. D' Anvers</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1087 — his Assertion of Infant-Baptism by Scripture 1674</item>
               <item>1088 <hi>Watson</hi>'s Divine Cordial 1663</item>
               <item>1089 — Art of Divine Contentment 1672</item>
               <item>1090 <hi>Wilkinson</hi>'s <hi>(Hen.)</hi> Debt-Book, also the Sacred Debt of Love 1625</item>
               <item>1091 — his Characters of a sincere Heart <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>1092 <hi>Weaver</hi>'s Pocket-Book, or Weaving Spiritualized <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1093 <hi>Wilson</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Scriptures Genuine Interpreter asserted <hi>Lond.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>1094 — Vanity of Mans present State 1676</item>
               <item>1095 <hi>Worthington</hi> of Resignation to the Divine Will 1675</item>
               <item>1096 <hi>Warner</hi> of Justifying Faith <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>1097 <hi>Whitby</hi>'s Answer to Sure-footing 1666</item>
               <item>1098 <hi>Watson</hi> on the Beatitudes <hi>Lond.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1099 <hi>Whiston</hi> of Infant-Baptism, against <hi>Danvers</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1100 Wakening for Worldlings 1621</item>
               <item>1101 <hi>White</hi>'s Dejection and Reason 1661</item>
               <item>1102 — Apology for <hi>Rushworth</hi>'s Dialogues 1654</item>
               <item>1103 <hi>Walker (Jo.)</hi> of Subjection to the Higher Powers 1684</item>
               <item>1104 <hi>Wybard (John) Tetagmenometria,</hi> or the Geometry of Regulars 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>0</item>
               <item>1105 Wits Academy, or the Muses Delight 1677</item>
               <item>1106 <hi>Ward</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Wonders of the Loadstone, with a Book of Cookery 1640</item>
               <item>1107 <hi>Westminster</hi> Quibbles in Verse 1672</item>
               <pb n="41" facs="tcp:42445:23"/>
               <item>1108 <hi>Wolley</hi>'s Guide for the Female Sex <hi>Lond.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1109 <hi>Wells</hi> of Infants-Baptism, with its vindication 1675</item>
               <item>1110 Winter-Evenings Conference between two Neighbours 1684</item>
               <item>1111 <hi>Whare</hi>'s Method of Reading History 1685</item>
               <item>1112 <hi>Wilkins (Jo.)</hi> Of the Principles and Duties of Natural Religion 2 Books 1683</item>
               <item>1113 —His Discovery concerning a new World in the Moon 1683</item>
               <item>1114 —his Sermons on several occasions 1682</item>
               <item>1115 —his Eclesiastes, or Gift of Preaching 1669</item>
               <item>1116 Whole Duty of Man 1685</item>
               <item>1117 <hi>Watson</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> his practical notes on the 3d Chapter of Melachy 1682</item>
               <item>1118 <hi>Wyvill</hi>'s (Sir <hi>Christ.</hi>) Pretentions of the Triple Crown Examined 1672</item>
               <item>1119 <hi>Whitston</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Infant Baptism plainly proved 1678</item>
               <item>1120 <hi>Wills (Ob.)</hi> Infant-Baptism asserted and vindicated 1674</item>
               <item>1121 <hi>Worthington</hi>'s (<hi>John</hi> Great Duty of self Resignation to the Divine Will 1675</item>
               <item>1122 Whole Duty of Man, of the Large Letter 1659</item>
               <item>1123 Weaving spiritualized or the Weavers Pocket-book 1675</item>
               <item>1124 Wits Recreation 1662</item>
               <item>1125 Wakning to Wordlings, or a Monument of Mortality</item>
               <item>1126 <hi>Wolley' (Edw.)</hi> Parents blessing their Children 1661</item>
               <item>1127 <hi>Watchman</hi>'s Lanthoran, being a sum of Divinity 1655</item>
               <item>1128 Dr. <hi>Womock</hi>'s Verdict upon the Dissenters plea occasioned by <hi>Melius Inquirendum</hi> 1688</item>
               <item>1129 <hi>Whiting</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Discourse of the last Judgment 1661</item>
               <item>1130 —his Meditations on the 18th Chapter of <hi>Genesis</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>1131 <hi>Warmstry</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Narrative of a Baptized Turk 1658</item>
               <item>1132 Wonderful mysterie of growing in Grace 1634</item>
               <item>1133 <hi>Willsford</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Secrets of Nature 1658</item>
               <item>1134 <hi>Watson</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Heaven taken by Storm, or Holy violence 1670</item>
               <item>1135 —his Divine Cordial 1663</item>
               <item>1136 <hi>Ward</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Two theological Treatises of Wit and Wisdom 1673</item>
               <item>1137 <hi>Whiting</hi>'s <hi>(Sam.)</hi> Discourse of the Last Judgment <hi>Camb.</hi> 1664</item>
               <item>1138 Weeks work; shewing the whole Duty of a Christian <hi>Lond.</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>1139 <hi>Wasse</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Reason for obeying the Government of <hi>England</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>1140 <hi>Webb</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> That the <hi>China</hi> Langue is the Primitive Language 1669</item>
               <item>1141 <hi>Wynell</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Treatise of the <hi>Lues Venera,</hi> or <hi>French Pox</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>1142 <hi>Walker</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Country Gaugers <hi>Vade mecum</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>1143 <hi>Webster</hi>'s <hi>(Will.)</hi> Principles of Arithmetick 1638</item>
               <item>1144 <hi>Waterhouse (Edw.)</hi> His Discourse and Defence of Arms and Armory 1660</item>
               <item>1145 Winter-Evenings Conference between Neighbours 1684</item>
               <item>1146 <hi>E. Winter</hi>'s Treatise of the Vitrioline Spaw near the City of <hi>Durham</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>1147 <hi>P. Walsh</hi>'s prospect of the State of <hi>Ireland</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>1148 Wit at a Venture, containing Songs and Poems on several Occasions 1674</item>
               <item>1149 <hi>Witaker</hi>'s <hi>(Tobias)</hi> Tree of Life, or the Blood of the Grape 1638</item>
               <item>1150 <hi>Wase</hi>'s Considerations concerring Free Schools, as setled in <hi>England Oxon.</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>1151 <hi>Waterhouse</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Discourse and Defence of Armes and Armory <hi>Lond.</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>1152 —his Nature, and Rise of Arms and Armory in <hi>England</hi> 1660</item>
               <item>1153 —his Apology for Learning and Learned men 1653</item>
               <item>1154 <hi>Whitlack</hi>'s <hi>(Rich.)</hi> Observations on the present manners of the English 1654</item>
               <item>1155 <hi>Wolley (Hannah)</hi> Cooks Guide, or rare recepts for Coockery 1664</item>
               <item>1156 <hi>Wingate</hi>'s <hi>(Edm.)</hi> Two Tables of Logarithmes 1633</item>
               <item>1157 <hi>Wagstaffe</hi>'s <hi>(Jo.)</hi> Question about Witchcraft Debated 1671</item>
               <pb n="42" facs="tcp:42445:24"/>
               <item>1158 <hi>Wither</hi>'s <hi>(Geo.)</hi> Plea for the Publick-faith of these Nations 1660</item>
               <item>1159 <hi>Ward</hi> (Bp. <hi>Seth</hi>) Of the Attributes of Gods; Immortality of mens Souls <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>1160 <hi>Waller</hi>'s <hi>(Edw.)</hi> Poems, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> on several occasions 1645</item>
               <item>1161 Bishop of <hi>York</hi>'s Manual of Prayers, Principles, and Resolutions <hi>Lond.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>1162 <hi>Young (James)</hi> Of the admiral Vertues of the Oyl of Turpentine 1679</item>
               <item>1163 Youths Behaviour, or Decency in Conversation amongst men 1668</item>
               <item>1164 <hi>Xenophon</hi>'s Institution and Life of <hi>Cyrus</hi> 1685</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>English in <hi>Quarto.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>1165 <hi>Perkins</hi> On the Galatians 1617</item>
               <item>1166 —Cases of Consciences 1642</item>
               <item>1167 Dr. <hi>Perce</hi>'s Sermons <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>1168 —Concerning Gods Decrees 1671</item>
               <item>1169 <hi>Plat</hi>'s Jewel House of Art and Nature 1653</item>
               <item>1170 <hi>Phelps</hi>'s needful Counsels for Lukwarm Christians 1671</item>
               <item>1171 Dr. <hi>Prideaux</hi>'s nine Sermons 1641</item>
               <item>1172 <hi>Parker</hi> on Daniel 1646</item>
               <item>1173 <hi>Prynnes</hi> Power of Parliaments Compleat 1643</item>
               <item>1174 Bishop <hi>Ʋsher</hi>'s Power of the Prince 1680</item>
               <item>1175 Posing of the Parts 1665</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>English in <hi>Twelves.</hi>
               </head>
               <item>1 <hi>Arvizagus</hi> and <hi>Philicia,</hi> A Play <hi>Lond.</hi> 1639</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Agripina</hi> and <hi>Cleopatra</hi> Two Tragedies, by <hi>Tho. May</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>3 Anatomy of Popery, or Catalogue of Popish Errors 1671</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Artimedorus</hi> his Exposition of Dream. 1673</item>
               <item>5 New Accademy of Complements 1672</item>
               <item>6 Apostolick Institution of Imposition of Hands 1649</item>
               <item>7 Accomplished Woman 1672</item>
               <item>8 Approved Receipts in Cookery, by Sir <hi>Thod. Mayerne</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Amsworth</hi>'s Communion of Saints 1641</item>
               <item>10 —Psalms in Meeter 1654</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Allington</hi>'s Grand Conspiracy in four Sermons 1654</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Angier</hi>'s Help to Better Hearts in several Sermons 1647</item>
               <item>13 Bp. <hi>Andrews</hi> Pattern of Catechistical Doctrine 1630</item>
               <item>14 Adamite, or the Love of Father <hi>Rock,</hi> with the Nuns 1683</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Austin</hi>'s Presumptious Mans mirrour 1641</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Annand</hi>'s Mysterie of Godliness 1671</item>
               <item>17 Art of weighing Vanity 1672</item>
               <item>18 Apophthegms of King <hi>James, Charles,</hi> &amp;c. 1671</item>
               <item>19 Antidote against Error about Adoration Alms, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1647</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Augustus,</hi> or Essays about <hi>Reme</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>21 Advice of <hi>Charles</hi> the 5th to his Son <hi>Philip</hi> 2d 1660</item>
               <item>22 Assemblys Works 1671</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Atherton</hi>'s Penitent Death 1642</item>
               <item>24 Bp. <hi>Andrew</hi>'s Manual of Private Divotions 1682</item>
               <item>25 Antiquity, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the Parliaments in <hi>England</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>26 Acconts Ready Cast up 1670</item>
               <item>27 Abbots Geography 1664</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Bifields</hi> Marrow of the Oracles of God 1660</item>
               <pb n="43" facs="tcp:42445:24"/>
               <item>29 —Principals or Patern of wholesome words 1671</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Brook</hi>'s String of Pearls 1674</item>
               <item>31 —Apples of Gold 1675</item>
               <item>32 —Making light of Christ and Salvation 1655</item>
               <item>33 <hi>Baxter</hi>'s Call to the Unconverted 1674</item>
               <item>34 —Vain Religion of the Hypocrite 1660</item>
               <item>35 Twelve Sermons of Judgment 1668</item>
               <item>36 —<hi>Idem Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>37 <hi>Basil</hi> Valentin with <hi>Suchten</hi> of Antimony 1670</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Becon</hi>'s Displaying the Romish Mass 1637</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Bristow</hi>'s Happiness of the union of <hi>England</hi> and <hi>Scotland</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Banister</hi>'s Chyrurgery 1685</item>
               <item>41 Lord <hi>Brooks</hi>'s Nature of Truth 1646</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Bunworth</hi> of Curing Diseases by Signature 1657</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Baker</hi>'s wicked Mans Plot Defeated 1656</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Borel</hi> of the Multiplicity of Worlds 1658</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Baker</hi>'s Apology fo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Lay mens writing in Divinity 1641</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Bramhal</hi> against <hi>Miltier</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Barclay</hi>'s Mirror of Minds 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>3</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Bradford</hi>'s Meditations 1622</item>
               <item>49 <hi>Brinsley</hi>'s True Watch, the 4th Part 1624</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Bayne</hi>'s Directions to a Godly Life 1681</item>
               <item>51 Bundle of Myrrhe, Three meditations of Tears 1610</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Barton</hi>'s Psalms 1654</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Brinsley</hi>'s Saints Communion w<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>th Christ 1654</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Balzac</hi>'s Prince 1648</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Ball</hi>'s Mirror of Pure Devotion 1635</item>
               <item>56 <hi>Bernard</hi>'s Ready way to Good Works 1635</item>
               <item>57 —Bible Battles 1627</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Bristol</hi> Drollery 1674</item>
               <item>59 <hi>Burton</hi>'s Apprentices Companion 1681</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Bolton</hi>'s Death of Mr. <hi>Peacock</hi> 1646</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Brathwait</hi>'s Essays 1635</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Brough</hi>'s Sacred Principles 1659</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Bosworth</hi>'s Chast and Lost Lovers 1651</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Boyle</hi>'s Discourse of things above Reason 1681</item>
               <item>65 <hi>Burrough</hi>'s Spots of the Godly and the Wicked 1668</item>
               <item>66 Book of Palmistry and Physiognomy 1666</item>
               <item>67 <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Christ Mighty in himself and Members 1646</item>
               <item>68 Bloody Inquisition of <hi>Spain</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Brathwait</hi>'s Golden Fleece 1611</item>
               <item>70 <hi>Barrow</hi>'s Duty and Reward of Bounty to the Poor 1680</item>
               <item>71 <hi>Brevis Demonstratio,</hi> or Truth of Christian Religion 1679</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Beraldus</hi> Prince of <hi>Savoy</hi> a Novel 1675</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Calvinist</hi> Cabinet unlock'd, in an Apology for <hi>Tilenus,</hi> by Bp. <hi>Womock</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>74 Carpenters Rule made Easie, by <hi>Jo. Darling</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>75 <hi>Case</hi>'s Correction and Instruction 1671</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Callymy</hi>'s Godly mans Ark 1669</item>
               <item>77 <hi>Croft</hi>'s Way to Happiness on Earth 1641</item>
               <item>78 <hi>Corbet</hi>'s Poems 1672</item>
               <pb n="44" facs="tcp:42445:25"/>
               <item>77 Chymists Key to shut and to open 1657</item>
               <item>78 Confession of Faith and Chatechism 1671</item>
               <item>79 Common Prayer large Letter <hi>Oxon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>80 —<hi>Idem</hi> Small Letter <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>81 —<hi>Idem</hi> 24. <hi>ib.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>82 Clergy in their Colors, or the Pride of the Presbyterian Clergy 1651</item>
               <item>83 Covenant between God and Man 1616</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Cleaver</hi> on the Sabbath 1625</item>
               <item>85 Character of a Christian 1627</item>
               <item>86 <hi>Clarke</hi>'s Looking-Glass for Good Women 1677</item>
               <item>87 <hi>Cunaeus</hi>'s Common wealth of the <hi>Jews</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>88 Collection of Prayers 1649</item>
               <item>89 St. <hi>Chrysostome</hi>'s Exortation for desperate Sinners 1654</item>
               <item>90 —of Education of Children 1653</item>
               <item>91 Cases of Conscience about things Indifferent 1661</item>
               <item>92 <hi>Castara</hi> A Poem 1640</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Colet</hi>'s Daily Devotions 1674</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Chetwina</hi>'s Suppliment to <hi>Godwind</hi>'s Catalogue of Bishops 1653</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Crashaw</hi>'s Steps to the Temple 1648</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Crompton</hi> on the Catechism of the Church 1633</item>
               <item>97 <hi>Cornwallis</hi>'s Essays 1606</item>
               <item>98 Changing of Church Discipline 1653</item>
               <item>99 Compleat Courtier or Cupids Accademy 1683</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Clifford</hi>'s Anthems Sung in Cathedrals 1664</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Culverwel</hi>'s Time well Spent 1634</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Caio</hi>'s Major, or Book of Old Age 1648</item>
               <item>103 Collection of Popish Miracles 1673</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Calymy</hi>'s Citys Remembrancer 1657</item>
               <item>105 Coral and Steel a methord for Preserving Health</item>
               <item>106 Compendious method for Attaining Siences 1654</item>
               <item>107 Comparison between the Eloquence of <hi>Demosthenes</hi> and <hi>Cicero</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>108 Bp. <hi>Corbet</hi>'s Poem 1672</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Coeffeteon</hi> of Humane Passions 1621</item>
               <item>110 Compleat Servant Maid 1680</item>
               <item>111 Combet betwixt Man and Death 1621</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Catastrophe Mundi,</hi> or <hi>Merlin</hi> Revived 1683</item>
               <item>113 Country Captain and the Variety 1646</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Dykes</hi>'s Worthy Communicant 1672</item>
               <item>115 A Philosophical Discourse conccrning Speech 1668</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Doolitel</hi> on the Lords Supper 1672</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Duppas</hi>'s Devotions 1672</item>
               <item>118 Daily Devotions 1673</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Digby</hi>'s Vegitation of Plants 1661</item>
               <item>120 Doctrine of the Bible 1668</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Davinant</hi>'s Discourse upon <hi>Gondibert,</hi> with <hi>Hobbs</hi>'s Answer 1650</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Dowel</hi>'s Leviathan Heretical 1683</item>
               <item>123 Description of the Islands of <hi>F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>eroc</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>124 Displaying of the Popish Mass 1637</item>
               <item>125 Discourse of Baptism and the Lords Supper 1672</item>
               <item>126 Divine Meditations 1641</item>
               <pb n="45" facs="tcp:42445:25"/>
               <item>127 <hi>Drexelius</hi> of Predestination 1656</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Davanant</hi>'s <hi>Madagascar</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>129 Divine Meditations 1606</item>
               <item>130 Devotions and Prayers for the use of a Christian Life 1676</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Dingly</hi>'s Divine Opticks 1655</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Daniel</hi>'s Poems 1611</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Dyer</hi>'s Works 1662</item>
               <item>134 Domestick devotions for the use of Families 1683</item>
               <item>135 Devout Communicant Exemplified 1682</item>
               <item>136 —Entertainment of a Christian Soul 1648</item>
               <item>137 Defence of the Liturgy of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>138 <hi>Dugar</hi>'s Change, or Blind Eye opened 1641</item>
               <item>139 <hi>David</hi>'s Troubles Remembred 1638</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Digby</hi> of Sympathetical Powder 1664</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Enoch Ap. Evans</hi> Murders of his Mother and Bother</item>
               <item>142 Exelent Remedies and Medicines for most Diseases 1652</item>
               <item>143 Essay in Morality 1682</item>
               <item>144 <hi>Elius Sejanus</hi> unhappy Prosperity 1639</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Ellis</hi>'s Christianity in short 1684</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Evelyn</hi> of Liberty and Servitude 1649</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Englands</hi> Reprover and Monitour 1653</item>
               <item>148 English Dictionary or Expositor 1670</item>
               <item>149 Education of a Prince 1678</item>
               <item>150 Exposition on <hi>Daniel</hi> 1545</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Elenchus Motuum</hi> by Dr. <hi>Bates</hi> Engl. 1652</item>
               <item>152 Epitome of the Bible in Metre 1678</item>
               <item>153 —of the Lives of the French Kings 1639</item>
               <item>154 Enigmatical Characters 1669</item>
               <item>155 <hi>Fenner</hi>'s Four select Sermons 1668</item>
               <item>156 Female Prince or Frederick of <hi>Sicily</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>157 <hi>Floyd</hi>'s Picture of a Common-wealth 1660</item>
               <item>158 <hi>Flavel</hi>'s Sacramental Meditations 1679</item>
               <item>159 —Saint Indeed 1684</item>
               <item>160 Five Love Letters from a Nun to a Cavalier 1678</item>
               <item>161 <hi>Forbe</hi>'s Arithmetick 1676</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Fletcher</hi>'s Restauration of <hi>Israel</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>163 Faithful Shephard 1633</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Fettiplace</hi>'s Christian Monitor 1672</item>
               <item>165 —Celestial Lamp 1.</item>
               <item>166 <hi>Fleming</hi>'s Royal Progeny Deleneated 1660</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Fox</hi>'s Door of Heaven opened and Shut 1676</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Filmer</hi> of Usury 1678</item>
               <item>169 <hi>Fuller</hi>'s Good thoughts in bad times 1669</item>
               <item>170 Epigrams of <hi>Virgil</hi> and others 1624</item>
               <item>171 Forbidden Fruit 1642</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Featley</hi>'s Handmaid to Devotion 1656</item>
               <item>173 <hi>Fortescus</hi>'s Commendation of the Laws of <hi>England</hi> 1567</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Ferrand</hi>'s Love Melancholy 1640</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Ford</hi>'s Evil Tongue Tryed and found Gilty 1672</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Gunton</hi> of Bodily worship 1661</item>
               <pb n="46" facs="tcp:42445:26"/>
               <item>178 Golden Book of St. <hi>Jo. Chrysostom</hi> of Education of Children 1659</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Garbut</hi>'s Demonstration of the Resurection 1669</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Grebner</hi>'s Visions and Prophesies 1661</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Gale</hi>'s Distractions or Holy Madoess 1629</item>
               <item>182 <hi>Grew</hi> of Menstruums and of Mixture 1678</item>
               <item>183 —of Menstrums 1678</item>
               <item>184 <hi>Gaule</hi>'s Votine Speculations 1630</item>
               <item>185 <hi>Gendre</hi>'s Manner of ordering Fruit Trees 1662</item>
               <item>186 <hi>Gouge</hi>'s Gods Call to <hi>England</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>187 Golden Mean 1638</item>
               <item>188 <hi>Goodwin</hi>'s <hi>(Tho.)</hi> Return of Prayer 1659</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Gree</hi>'s Golden Mean 1656</item>
               <item>190 Groans of the Spirit 1639</item>
               <item>191 Game of Chess Play 1656</item>
               <item>192 <hi>Griffith</hi>'s God and the King 1660</item>
               <item>193 Golden Cabinet of true Treasure 1612</item>
               <item>194 <hi>Gurney</hi>'s <hi>Corpus Christi</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>195 Groans of the Spirit 1639</item>
               <item>196 <hi>Godwin</hi>'s <hi>(John)</hi> Saints interest in God 1643</item>
               <item>197 —God a Good Master and Protector 1641</item>
               <item>198 —<hi>(Tho.)</hi> Happiness of the Saints in Glory 1638</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Garbut</hi> Against Drunkards and Whoremongers</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Gaule</hi>'s Cases of Conscience touching Witches 1645</item>
               <item>201 —Vindication of the fifth of the <hi>Romans</hi>
               </item>
               <item>202 <hi>Granada</hi> of Prayer and Meditation 1602</item>
               <item>203 —Devotions 1598</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Grotius</hi> of God and his Providence 1658</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Gifford</hi>'s French Schoolmaster 1668</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Gerhard</hi>'s sum of Christian Doctrine 1640</item>
               <item>207 <hi>Grebner</hi>'s Visions and Prophecies 1661</item>
               <item>208 Guide of Honour 1634</item>
               <item>209 Geographical Dictionary 1678</item>
               <item>210 <hi>Gee</hi>'s Steps of Assention 1671</item>
               <item>211 Happy Minde, or the Paradise within us 1640</item>
               <item>212 <hi>Hayward</hi>'s Life and Reign of <hi>Edward</hi> the 6th 1636</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Harvey</hi>'s Little Venus unmask'd 1671</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Hickman</hi>'s Danger of the House of Feasting 1666</item>
               <item>215 <hi>Herbert</hi>'s Temple 1667</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Hinckley</hi>'s Four Sermons 1657</item>
               <item>217 Heroine Musquatier, or the Female Warrier 1678</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Herle</hi>'s Wisdoms <hi>Tripos</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>219 <hi>Howard</hi>'s (Duke of <hi>Norfolk</hi>) Journey to <hi>Vienna</hi> and <hi>Constantinople</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>220 <hi>Harris</hi>'s <hi>Peters</hi> Enlargement on the Prayers of the Church 1651</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Howe</hi>'s Vanity of this mortal Life 1672</item>
               <item>222 <hi>Horneck</hi>'s Fire of the Altar 1683</item>
               <item>223 Humaine Prudence or Act of Grandure 1682</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Haynes</hi>'s Equal ways of God 1639</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Hobson</hi>'s Practical Divinity 1646</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Hall</hi>'s Divine Soul 1658</item>
               <item>227 —Select Toughts 1653</item>
               <pb n="47" facs="tcp:42445:26"/>
               <item>228 Heaven of the Mind 1603</item>
               <item>229 Holy Sinner 1639</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Hodges</hi>'s Wholesome Repast for the Soul 1638</item>
               <item>231 Honest Man or the Art to please in Court 1632</item>
               <item>232 History of the Kingdom of <hi>Portugal</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>233 <hi>Hattige,</hi> or the Amours of the King of <hi>Tamaran</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Hamond</hi>'s <hi>Parnasis</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>235 Sir <hi>Ch. Heydons</hi> Discourse 1650</item>
               <item>236 Bp. <hi>Hall</hi>'s Morners in <hi>Syon</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>237 <hi>Homer</hi>'s Odysses, by <hi>Tho. Hobbs</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Harwood</hi>'s Ministers Office 1659</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Hall</hi>'s <hi>Jacobs</hi> Ladder 1676</item>
               <item>240 Heavenly Accademy 1638</item>
               <item>241 <hi>Hooker</hi>'s Souls preparation for Christ 1643</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Harris</hi>'s <hi>Peters</hi> Enlargement on the Prayers of the Church 1651</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Hayes</hi>'s Trades mans Companion 1652</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Herbert</hi>'s Temple 1674</item>
               <item>245 <hi>Hobbs</hi> of Liberty and Necessity 1677</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Hayward</hi>'s Life of <hi>Edward</hi> the 6th 1636</item>
               <item>247 <hi>Homer</hi>'s <hi>Illiads,</hi> by <hi>Tho. Hobbs</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Herle</hi>'s Wisdoms <hi>Tripos</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>249 History of the Palais-Royal, or the Amours of Mad. <hi>de la Valliere</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>250 —of the Late Revolutions in <hi>Naples</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>251 —of <hi>Charles</hi> the 2d 1660</item>
               <item>252 —of Valentines 1643</item>
               <item>253 <hi>Jackson</hi>'s Evangelical Temper 1641</item>
               <item>254 —Key of Knowledge 1640</item>
               <item>255 <hi>Johnson</hi>'s Arithmetick 1671</item>
               <item>256 Jesuits Powder discovered for Fevours and Agues 1681</item>
               <item>257 Instructions for Oratory 1682</item>
               <item>258 Idiot' of Wisdom, of the Minde, and Statick Experments 1650</item>
               <item>259 Isle of <hi>Man</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>260 Journey to Jerusalem 1672</item>
               <item>261 <hi>Jewel</hi>'s Apology of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>5</item>
               <item>262 Immortality of the King. 1649</item>
               <item>263 <hi>Jacob</hi>'s Wrestling with God 1607</item>
               <item>294 <hi>Janoway</hi>'s Legacy 1674</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Jamaica</hi> viewed 1661</item>
               <item>256 <hi>Jenison</hi>'s Two Treatises 1641</item>
               <item>257 Juniper Lecture 1652</item>
               <item>258 Jesuites Displayed 1650</item>
               <item>259 <hi>Jones</hi>'s Cure of Blood Against Arests for Debt 1651</item>
               <item>260 <hi>Johnson</hi>'s History of <hi>Scotland</hi> during King <hi>James</hi> Minority</item>
               <item>261 Introduction to the Skill of Musick 1658</item>
               <item>262 <hi>Kedder</hi>'s Young mans Duty 1671</item>
               <item>263 Key of Faith 1669</item>
               <item>264 <hi>Kemp</hi>'s Institution of Christ 1672</item>
               <item>265 King <hi>James</hi> Psalms 1631</item>
               <item>266 <hi>Kents</hi> (Countise) Manual 1667</item>
               <item>267 Arch-Bp. <hi>Lauds</hi> Seven Sermons 1657</item>
               <pb n="48" facs="tcp:42445:27"/>
               <item>268 — Summary of Devotions 1667</item>
               <item>269 <hi>Linesey</hi> s Spirit of the Lord in Power and Liberty 1674</item>
               <item>270 <hi>Louth</hi>'s Catechetical Questions 1673</item>
               <item>271 <hi>Lermus Lermius</hi> Discourse of Generation 1664</item>
               <item>272 <hi>Lukins</hi>'s Practise of Godliness 1659</item>
               <item>273 — Cheif Interest of Man 1619</item>
               <item>274 <hi>Loes</hi> Mysterie of Mankind 1670</item>
               <item>275 <hi>Laydy</hi>'s Cabinet Enlarged and Opened 1667</item>
               <item>276 <hi>Loyd</hi>'s Fair warning to a Careless World 1682</item>
               <item>277 <hi>Leach</hi>'s Grammar Questions 1650</item>
               <item>278 <hi>Latham</hi>'s Spaw with Cases and Cures 1670</item>
               <item>279 <hi>Lower</hi>'s Triumphant Lady 1656</item>
               <item>280 Letter to a Non-Conformist Minister of the Kirk 1677</item>
               <item>281 <hi>Leybourn</hi>'s Arithmetical Recreations 1667</item>
               <item>282 <hi>London</hi> Drollery 1673</item>
               <item>283 Light and Life of a Man in Christ 1646</item>
               <item>284 <hi>Lucius Florus,</hi> Roman History 1667</item>
               <item>285 <hi>Lumen de Lumine,</hi> or a new Magical Light Discovered 1651</item>
               <item>286 <hi>Lyndes</hi>'s By-way, and Safeway 1629</item>
               <item>287 Lives of sundry Notorious Villains 1678</item>
               <item>288 —of Admiral <hi>De Ruyter</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>289 —of the German Princes 1679</item>
               <item>290 —of Mr. <hi>George Herbert, Jz. Walton</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>291 —of <hi>Ignatius Jurdain</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>292 —of Sir <hi>Tho. More</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>293 —of a Satyrical Puppy called Nim 1657</item>
               <item>294 —of Pope <hi>Innocent</hi> 11th 1683</item>
               <item>295 —of <hi>Tho. Wilson</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>296 Legend of Captain <hi>Jones</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>297 Marrow of Chymical Physick 1669</item>
               <item>298 Manual for True Catholicks 1611</item>
               <item>299 <hi>Malvezzi Romulus</hi> and <hi>Tarquin</hi>
               </item>
               <item>300 Manual of Moral Discourses 1611</item>
               <item>301 <hi>Mayerus Lucius Serius,</hi> a Discourse of the Superiority of Creatures 1656</item>
               <item>302 <hi>Mantuan</hi>'s Bucolicks 1654</item>
               <item>303 <hi>Marianus,</hi> or Loves Heroical Champion 1654</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Machiavel</hi>'s Discourse on <hi>Livey</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>305 <hi>Malvezzi</hi>'s Politick Christian Favourite 1647</item>
               <item>306 <hi>Meriton</hi>'s Geographical Description of the World 1674</item>
               <item>307 <hi>Miscellanea,</hi> or a Mixture of Observations 1669</item>
               <item>308 <hi>Morton</hi>'s Touchstone of Conversion 1647</item>
               <item>309 <hi>Margariton,</hi> A Rich Treasure of Problems and their Resolves 1640</item>
               <item>310 <hi>Manchester</hi>'s <hi>al Mondo,</hi> Contemplation of death and Immortality 1667</item>
               <item>311 Sir <hi>Jonas More</hi>'s Mathematical Compendium 1681</item>
               <item>312 <hi>Mead</hi>'s Almost Christian Discovered 1675</item>
               <item>313 <hi>Malvezzi</hi>'s Consideration on the Lives of <hi>Alcibiades</hi> and <hi>Coriolanus</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>314 Manners of the Israelites 1683</item>
               <item>315 <hi>Markham</hi>'s Perfect Horseman 1684</item>
               <item>316 Modern Politicks taken from <hi>Machavel,</hi> &amp;c. 1657</item>
               <item>317 <hi>Manywaring</hi> of the Scurvey 1665</item>
               <pb n="49" facs="tcp:42445:27"/>
               <item>318 —of Consumptions 1668</item>
               <item>319 <hi>Morton</hi>'s Threefold State of Man 1629</item>
               <item>320 Moral Philosophy of the <hi>Stoicks</hi> 1698</item>
               <item>321 <hi>Du Moulin</hi>'s Antibarbarian, and praise of Divinity 1630</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Mason</hi>'s Three Treatises, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1634</item>
               <item>323 <hi>Medela Medicorum</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>324 <hi>Mayne</hi>'s Practical Gauger 1676</item>
               <item>325 <hi>Mason</hi>'s Handful of Essaies 1621</item>
               <item>326 <hi>Nazianzen</hi>'s Oration Against the Emperor <hi>Julian</hi> 1662</item>
               <item>327 <hi>Newton</hi>'s Art of Logick 1671</item>
               <item>328 <hi>Noy</hi>'s Grounds and Maxims of the Laws 1677</item>
               <item>329 New Help to Discourse 1671</item>
               <item>330 <hi>Nomenclator</hi> for the use of <hi>Westminster</hi> School, Engl. Gr. Lat.</item>
               <item>331 Names of the Merchants of <hi>London</hi> 1677</item>
               <item>332 <hi>Nemesius</hi> of the Nature of Man 1636</item>
               <item>333 <hi>Neal</hi>'s Directions to Travel 1643</item>
               <item>334 None but Christ 1655</item>
               <item>335 <hi>Newton</hi>'s Geometrical Trigonometry 1669</item>
               <item>336 <hi>Norice</hi> of Temporal Blessings 1636</item>
               <item>337 <hi>Osborn</hi>'s Advice to a Son 1658</item>
               <item>338 —Memoirs on Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi> and King <hi>James</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>339 —Politick Reflections on the Government of the <hi>Turks</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>340 —Miscellany of sundry Essays, Paradoxes 1659</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Owen</hi>'s Epigrams 1678</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Oedipus,</hi> or the Resolver 1650</item>
               <item>343 Old Religion Demonstrated in its Principles 1684</item>
               <item>344 <hi>Preston</hi>'s Fulness of Christ for us 1639</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Pool</hi>'s Dialogue between A Papist and Protestant 1672</item>
               <item>346 Paston's Plea for Peace 1640</item>
               <item>347 <hi>Philpot</hi>'s Original of Churches 1670</item>
               <item>348 Pensive Mans Practice</item>
               <item>349 Politicks of <hi>France</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>450 Psalm of mercy, or Meditations on 51 Psalm 1625</item>
               <item>351 Popery Absolutely distructive to Monarchy 1673</item>
               <item>352 Prayers of Intercession 1659</item>
               <item>353 Pricture of a Christian mans Conscience 1646</item>
               <item>354 <hi>Parr</hi>'s Grounds of Divinity 1636</item>
               <item>355 <hi>Paracelsus</hi>'s Dispensatory and Chyrurgery 1656</item>
               <item>356 Bp. <hi>Parry</hi>'s Meditations and Prayers 1672</item>
               <item>357 Practise of the Faithful 1664</item>
               <item>358 <hi>Peacham</hi>'s Valley of Variety 1638</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Patrick</hi>'s Devout Christian 1684</item>
               <item>360 —Book for young Communicants 1683</item>
               <item>361 <hi>Peganus</hi> on the Revelations</item>
               <item>362 <hi>Plaifere</hi> of Predestination 1651</item>
               <item>363 Paradise of Prayer, by <hi>Lewis</hi> of <hi>Granada</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Price</hi>'s Souls Porter 1638</item>
               <item>365 Plots of <hi>Lucifer</hi> against the Children of men 1656</item>
               <item>366 Prudential Reflections, Moral Considerations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>367 Present State <hi>England</hi> 1679</item>
               <pb n="50" facs="tcp:42445:28"/>
               <item>368 Present State of <hi>Tanger</hi> and Algiers 1676</item>
               <item>369 —of <hi>Italy</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>370 Publick Devotions and Common service of the Church Justified 1675</item>
               <item>371 Present State of <hi>England</hi> first Part 1669</item>
               <item>372 —<hi>Idem</hi> 2d Part 1671</item>
               <item>373 Plea for Old Age 1639</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Plaford</hi>'s <hi>Vade Mecum</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>375 <hi>Phillips</hi>'s Purchacers Pattern 1677</item>
               <item>376 Practice of the Faithful 1675</item>
               <item>377 Pathway to Health 1664</item>
               <item>378 Philosophers Banquet 1633</item>
               <item>379 Psalms of <hi>David</hi> in Meeter 1673</item>
               <item>380 <hi>Pinke'</hi> Tryal of a Christians Love to Christ 1659</item>
               <item>381 Paradise of Delights, or a Elixer of Comfort 1672</item>
               <item>382 <hi>Palmer</hi>'s Memorials of Goodliness 1670</item>
               <item>383 —Christians freedom by Christ 1646</item>
               <item>384 <hi>Powel</hi>'s Concordence to the Bible 1671</item>
               <item>385 Postscript to Mr. <hi>Hunts</hi> Arguments for the Bishops Right 1682</item>
               <item>386 Patriarchs Triumphs of Love, Chastity, Death</item>
               <item>387 Pious Mans practise in Parliament time</item>
               <item>388 <hi>Peter</hi>'s Legacy to his Daughter</item>
               <item>389 <hi>Quarl</hi>'s <hi>Bonarges</hi> and <hi>Barnabas</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>390 — <hi>Agalus</hi> and <hi>Parthenia</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>391 Queen-like Closet by <hi>H. Wolley</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>392 <hi>Quevedo</hi>'s Visions 1678</item>
               <item>393 <hi>Richards</hi>'s Tragedy of Messalana 1640</item>
               <item>394 Relation of the Country of <hi>Jansenia</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>395 <hi>R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>cord</hi>'s Urinal of Physick 1651</item>
               <item>396 Romances and their Orignal 1672</item>
               <item>397 <hi>Rous</hi>'s Oyle of Scorpions 1623</item>
               <item>398 Rules of Civility 1678</item>
               <item>399 <hi>Robinson</hi>'s Essays, Divine and Moral 1638</item>
               <item>400 <hi>Religio Medici</hi>
               </item>
               <item>401 <hi>Read</hi> of the Muscules of the Body 1637</item>
               <item>402 <hi>Ram</hi>'s Countrymans Catechism 1655</item>
               <item>403 Relation of the French Kings Expedition into the <hi>Spanish Netherlands</hi> 1669</item>
               <item>404 Rich Treasure at an easie Rate 1673</item>
               <item>405 <hi>Reyn<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lls</hi>'s Word of Caution to the present Times 1658</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Ross</hi>'s Observations on <hi>Rawleighs</hi> History</item>
               <item>407 <hi>Rogers</hi>'s <hi>(Tim.)</hi> Saving Belief 1644</item>
               <item>408 —Good news from Heaven 1651</item>
               <item>409 Remarques on the Humours of the Gallants of the Town 1673</item>
               <item>410 Bp. <hi>Reynolds</hi>'s on Ecclesiastes 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>411 Relation of <hi>Francis Spira</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>412 <hi>Rawleigh</hi>'s Essays and Observations 1650</item>
               <item>413 <hi>Ray</hi>'s Collection of English words 1674</item>
               <item>414 Relation of Defeating of <hi>Cromwel</hi> and <hi>Mazarins</hi> design against <hi>Ostend</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>415 <hi>Sadler</hi>'s Sick Womans private Looking Glass 1636</item>
               <item>416 <hi>Soloman</hi>'s Remembrancer to Transgressors of both Sexes 1672</item>
               <item>417 <hi>Stuart</hi>'s Three Sermons 1658</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:42445:28"/>
               <item>418 <hi>Stafford</hi>'s <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>42<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>424 <hi>Sh<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> Grammar <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>6</item>
               <item>425 <hi>San<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ealth <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>70</item>
               <item>426 State o<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> 1652</item>
               <item>427 School of Wisdom 1664</item>
               <item>428 Skilful Physitian, or Directions for Health 1656</item>
               <item>429 <hi>Strong</hi>'s Worm that Dyeth not 1672</item>
               <item>430 <hi>Studley</hi> of Schism 1635</item>
               <item>431 <hi>Sheppard</hi>'s Parsons Guide 1670</item>
               <item>432 —<hi>Englands</hi> Blame 1657</item>
               <item>433 Spiritual Alms 1625</item>
               <item>434 <hi>Smith Joseph</hi> and his Mistress 1635</item>
               <item>435 —<hi>David</hi>'s Repentance on the 51 <hi>Psalm</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>436 <hi>Stuart</hi>'s Three Sermons 1673</item>
               <item>437 <hi>Sprint</hi> of the Sabbath 1635</item>
               <item>438 <hi>Swadlin</hi>'s Manual of Devotions 1643</item>
               <item>439 <hi>Sandis</hi> (Sir <hi>Miles</hi>) Of Prudence</item>
               <item>440 Scriptures self-evidence 1667</item>
               <item>441 School of the Heart, in 47 Emblems 1676</item>
               <item>442 <hi>Savage</hi>'s Institution of the Church 1646</item>
               <item>443 <hi>Sherring</hi>'s Hearts Happiness 1659</item>
               <item>444 <hi>Sandbrook</hi> Of the Church 1646</item>
               <item>445 <hi>Sibs</hi>'s Christ's Exaltation 1639</item>
               <item>446 <hi>Stafford'</hi> Day of Salvation 1635</item>
               <item>447 Siege of <hi>Stetin</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>448 <hi>Thevenaw</hi>'s Common Notions and Advice 1662</item>
               <item>449 Triumph of Love over Fortune 1678</item>
               <item>450 <hi>Temple</hi> (Sir <hi>Pet.</hi>) Mans Master Piece 1658</item>
               <item>451 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s <hi>(Jer.)</hi> Guide to Devotion 1677</item>
               <item>452 <hi>Tuckney</hi>'s Works 1654</item>
               <item>453 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s Pearl of the Gospel, and Circumspect Walking 1633</item>
               <item>454 <hi>Torshel</hi> Of Justification 1632</item>
               <item>455 <hi>Tozer</hi>'s Directions to a Good Life 1671</item>
               <item>456 <hi>Taylor</hi>'s Practice of Repentance 1635</item>
               <item>457 <hi>Tompson</hi>'s Souls Alarm Bell 1618</item>
               <item>458 Voyage to <hi>Tafiletta</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>469 <hi>Virgil</hi>'s Works, by <hi>Ogilsby</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>460 <hi>Vane</hi>'s Wisdom and Innocence 1642</item>
               <item>461 <hi>Ʋsher</hi>'s Princples of Christian Religion 1658</item>
               <item>462 <hi>Vernulius Nomenclator</hi> of Tracts or Sermons on the Scripture 1642</item>
               <item>463 Sir <hi>Ch. Wolseley</hi>'s On Divorce in the Case of the Lord <hi>Rosse</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>464 Wits Accademy or the Muses Delight 1677</item>
               <item>465 —Recreation 1663</item>
               <item>466 <hi>White</hi>'s Book for Little Children 1672</item>
               <item>467 <hi>Whately</hi>'s Redemption of Time 1673</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:42445:29"/>
               <item>468 <hi>White</hi>'<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
                  <hi>a Bun<gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>,</hi>) <gap reason="illegible" resp="#keyers" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <item>BIbles in Folio, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#murp" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>, Octavo, Twelves, Twenty fours, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#murp" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> of Divers Bindings.</item>
               <item>Common Prayers Folio, Quarto, Octavo, Twelves, Twenty fours, Bound of Divers Binding.</item>
               <item>Testaments, Octavo, Twelves, both great and small Letter.</item>
               <item>Book of Homilies; fol. with 39 Articles; of the large Paper.</item>
               <item>Idem, ordinary Paper.</item>
            </list>
            <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>